As O
a O
vocalist O
, O
songwriter O
, O
and O
experimental O
pop O
recording O
artist O
, O
Mirah B-PERSON
typically O
works O
independently O
while O
songwriting O
, O
though O
frequently O
collaborates O
as O
a O
recording O
artist O
. O

Hoffman B-PERSON
repeated O
the O
cover O
illustration O
as O
a O
smaller O
line O
drawing O
on O
the O
title O
page O
. O

Courtney B-PERSON
experienced O
a O
strange O
sensation O
of O
being O
too O
hot O
, O
and O
then O
, O
too O
cold O
. O

Wiseman B-PERSON
was O
an O
exempt O
player O
for O
the O
2010 O
- O
11 O
PBA O
season O
. O

Clarke B-PERSON
also O
trained O
an O
SOE O
agent O
Harry O
Rée O
for O
his O
activities O
in O
occupied O
France O
. O

His O
family O
continued O
its O
Jewish O
tradition O
, O
sending O
young O
Mandel B-PERSON
to O
an O
afternoon O
Hebrew O
school O
. O

On O
30 O
May O
2009 O
, O
Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
reached O
the O
semi O
- O
finals O
of O
the O
Rugby O
League O
Challenge O
Cup O
, O
beating O
Hull O
Kingston O
Rovers O
24–25 O
via O
a O
drop O
goal O
from O
Lee O
Briers O
in O
golden O
point O
extra O
time O
to O
earn O
a O
place O
in O
the O
last O
four O
. O

Brady B-PERSON
first O
gained O
critical O
acclaim O
right O
after O
leaving O
school O
, O
when O
he O
caught O
the O
attention O
of O
some O
well O
- O
known O
art O
collectors O
during O
his O
first O
solo O
show O
. O

After O
independently O
releasing O
three O
EPs O
, O
Roy B-PERSON
signed O
to O
Fueled O
by O
Ramen O
and O
released O
their O
Matt O
Bayles O
- O
produced O
debut O
studio O
album O
" O
Big O
City O
Sin O
and O
Small O
Town O
Redemption O
" O
in O
2004 O
. O

Arguably O
the O
greatest O
asset O
of O
the O
Mansfield B-LOCATION
area O
is O
its O
remaining O
pockets O
of O
bushland O
and O
parklands O
. O

Ellis B-PERSON
garnered O
a O
reputation O
as O
a O
loner O
with O
a O
fiery O
temper O
, O
earning O
him O
the O
nickname O
" O
Die O
Rooi O
Duiwel O
" O
( O
The O
Red O
Devil O
) O
. O

In O
1997 O
, O
Cunningham B-PERSON
had O
pushed O
the O
Pentagon O
into O
buying O
a O
$ O
20 O
million O
document O
- O
digitization O
system O
created O
by O
ADCS O
Inc. O
, O
one O
of O
several O
defense O
companies O
owned O
by O
Wilkes O
. O

Soon O
after O
Eliza O
had O
received O
a O
pardon O
, O
Fawkner B-PERSON
obtained O
a O
licence O
to O
run O
the O
Cornwall O
Hotel O
in O
1826 O
. O

Wright O
was O
inducted O
into O
the O
Louisiana O
Hayride O
Hall O
Of O
Fame O
in O
2003 O
; O
and O
a O
year O
later O
, O
Bear O
Family O
released O
a O
CD O
containing O
most O
of O
Wright B-PERSON
and O
Tom O
Tall O
's O
Fabor O
recordings O
. O

In O
1785 O
, O
when O
China O
opened O
the O
port O
of O
Canton O
to O
foreign O
businesses O
, O
Perkins B-PERSON
became O
one O
of O
the O
first O
Boston O
merchants O
to O
engage O
in O
the O
China O
trade O
. O

Jericho B-LOCATION
is O
a O
former O
settlement O
in O
Nevada O
County O
, O
California O
. O

In O
England O
's O
first O
group O
game O
, O
Roy B-PERSON
scored O
1 O
run O
and O
took O
a O
catch O
off O
of O
Liam O
Plunkett O
's O
bowling O
. O

Liberty B-ORGANIZATION
announced O
plans O
in O
April O
2011 O
to O
sell O
WFRV O
and O
WJMN O
to O
Nexstar O
Broadcasting O
Group O
for O
$ O
20 O
million O
. O

Born O
into O
a O
prominent O
, O
slave O
- O
holding O
family O
in O
Frankfort O
, O
Kentucky O
, O
Harlan B-PERSON
experienced O
a O
quick O
rise O
to O
political O
prominence O
. O

Started O
in O
1990 O
, O
Kropp B-PERSON
continues O
the O
Pillow O
Talk O
program O
today O
in O
private O
, O
one O
- O
on O
- O
one O
classes O
. O

Burke B-PERSON
continues O
to O
tour O
throughout O
the O
world O
, O
including O
performances O
in O
Australia O
in O
2013 O
. O

California B-LOCATION
is O
small O
suburban O
area O
of O
Birmingham O
, O
England O
. O

Brady B-PERSON
is O
a O
former O
civil O
servant O
who O
for O
20 O
years O
, O
ran O
the O
constituency O
office O
of O
the O
former O
Taoiseach O
Bertie O
Ahern O
. O

Lester B-PERSON
finished O
the O
season O
T-4th O
in O
wins O
( O
19 O
) O
and O
in O
4th O
place O
in O
strikeouts O
( O
225 O
) O
in O
the O
Majors O
( O
AL O
and O
NL O
combined O
) O
in O
2010 O
. O

Huber B-PERSON
lead O
the O
Storm O
in O
wins O
; O
was O
second O
in O
strikeouts O
, O
home O
runs O
allowed O
( O
9 O
) O
, O
and O
walks O
allowed O
( O
44 O
) O
; O
and O
was O
third O
in O
innings O
pitched O
( O
107 O
) O
, O
hits O
allowed O
( O
107 O
) O
, O
losses O
, O
games O
started O
, O
and O
runs O
allowed O
( O
44 O
) O
. O

On O
March O
23 O
, O
2017 O
, O
it O
was O
rumored O
that O
Fife B-PERSON
was O
close O
to O
accepting O
the O
head O
coaching O
position O
at O
Duquesne O
, O
but O
shortly O
thereafter O
it O
was O
reported O
that O
he O
had O
declined O
the O
position O
. O

Curtis B-PERSON
built O
" O
Lyndon O
" O
, O
a O
Renaissance O
revival O
estate O
in O
Wyncote O
, O
Pennsylvania O
, O
with O
landscaping O
designed O
by O
Frederick O
Law O
Olmsted O
. O

Charles B-PERSON
then O
opened O
negotiations O
with O
the O
Viking O
chiefs O
Godfrid O
and O
Sigfred O
. O

Blair B-PERSON
started O
filming O
just O
after O
she O
graduated O
from O
school O
. O

Exeter B-ORGANIZATION
participated O
in O
the O
Chinese O
Educational O
Mission O
, O
hosting O
seven O
students O
from O
Qing O
China O
, O
starting O
in O
1879 O
. O

This O
second O
line O
runs O
through O
Eschweiler B-LOCATION
about O
500 O
m O
north O
of O
and O
parallel O
with O
the O
main O
line O
and O
passes O
under O
it O
at O
the O
Dreibogenbrücke O
( O
“ O
three O
- O
arch O
bridge O
” O
) O
in O
the O
district O
of O
Aue O
. O

Sharkey B-PERSON
however O
would O
n't O
play O
another O
AFL O
game O
and O
saw O
out O
the O
decade O
at O
the O
Bendigo O
Bombers O
. O

While O
Essex B-ORGANIZATION
added O
an O
enclosed O
sedan O
in O
1920 O
, O
it O
was O
the O
introduction O
of O
the O
1922 O
closed O
coach O
, O
priced O
at O
$ O
1,495 O
( O
which O
in O
early O
2015 O
would O
be O
between O
$ O
15,917 O
and O
$ O
21,015 O
, O
depending O
on O
the O
inflation O
calculator O
used O
) O
, O
$ O
300 O
above O
that O
of O
the O
touring O
car O
. O

AUGUST O
- O
LoveFest O
II O
Saturday O
, O
August O
12 O
at O
11 O
AM O
, O
West O
Harvey O
Ave O
, O
Dorset B-LOCATION
- O
Promoting O
Community O
Cohesion O
. O

The O
DVD O
was O
filmed O
in O
Ballybunion O
, O
Co. O
Kerry O
and O
Kenny B-PERSON
is O
joined O
by O
the O
fiddler O
Ivor O
Ottley O
and O
double O
bassist O
Damien O
Evans O
. O

In O
March O
2012 O
, O
the O
final O
report O
of O
the O
Mahon O
Tribunal O
found O
that O
Wright B-PERSON
received O
a O
£ O
5,000 O
" O
corrupt O
" O
payment O
from O
Christopher O
Jones O
in O
November O
1992 O
in O
relation O
to O
the O
Ballycullen O
/ O
Beechill O
rezoning O
projects O
. O

Yasuda B-PERSON
has O
played O
in O
the O
bands O
The O
Lapse O
and O
The O
Van O
Pelt O
before O
their O
disbandment O
, O
and O
had O
a O
brief O
stint O
in O
Blonde O
Redhead O
. O

On O
8 O
February O
2019 O
Tamm B-PERSON
joined O
Ekstraklasa O
club O
Korona O
Kielce O
on O
a O
six O
- O
month O
loan O
deal O
. O

After O
Lacson O
's O
term O
in O
the O
1950s O
, O
Manila B-LOCATION
was O
led O
by O
Antonio O
Villegas O
for O
most O
of O
the O
1960s O
. O

Chalke B-PERSON
claims O
that O
; O
" O
Intolerance O
and O
are O
more O
to O
do O
with O
fundamentalism O
, O
than O
faith O
. O

Meier O
told O
Donald B-PERSON
that O
he O
was O
sure O
the O
Democrats O
would O
win O
the O
election O
, O
since O
they O
had O
a O
lot O
of O
information O
on O
Richard O
Nixon O
's O
illicit O
dealings O
with O
Howard O
Hughes O
which O
had O
never O
been O
released O
, O
and O
that O
Larry O
O'Brien O
had O
the O
information O

Gormley B-PERSON
has O
avoided O
the O
spotlight O
and O
is O
notoriously O
reclusive O
. O

Killarney B-LOCATION
is O
a O
neighbourhood O
in O
East O
Vancouver O
, O
British O
Columbia O
with O
a O
population O
of O
over O
28,000 O
in O
2011 O
and O
lies O
in O
the O
far O
southeast O
corner O
of O
the O
city O
. O

Humphrey B-PERSON
presented O
the O
2011 O
& O
2012 O
" O
New O
Year O
Live O
" O
countdown O
programme O
. O

Paris B-LOCATION
is O
now O
a O
small O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Fauquier O
County O
, O
Virginia O
, O
United O
States O
. O

In O
the O
same O
year O
John O
declared O
England O
a O
Papal O
fief O
, O
and O
Pope O
Innocent O
III O
thus O
claimed O
to O
be O
guardian O
of O
Eleanor B-PERSON
. O

In O
2004 O
, O
Fagan B-PERSON
filed O
a O
federal O
lawsuit O
in O
Manhattan O
for O
a O
non O
- O
existent O
group O
called O
the O
Association O
of O
Holocaust O
Victims O
for O
Restitution O
of O
Artwork O
& O
Masterpieces O
( O
AHVRAM O
) O
against O
Bank O
Austria O
Creditanstalt O
AG O
and O
other O
European O
corporate O
, O
governmental O
and O
financial O
institutions O
for O
$ O
6.8 O
billion O
. O

Tripoli B-LOCATION
has O
a O
post O
office O
with O
ZIP O
code O
54564 O
. O

Keter B-ORGANIZATION
has O
a O
large O
book O
marketing O
and O
distribution O
network O
, O
as O
well O
print O
services O
and O
book O
production O
for O
the O
Israeli O
domestic O
and O
export O
market O
. O

Wythe B-PERSON
also O
designed O
the O
Chancery O
Court O
seal O
to O
illustrate O
the O
punishment O
of O
the O
Persian O
judge O
Sisamnes O
, O
killed O
and O
skinned O
after O
taking O
a O
bribe O
. O

Warburg B-PERSON
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Advisory O
Committee O
on O
Religious O
Denominations O
which O
reports O
to O
Denmark O
's O
Ministry O
of O
Ecclesiastical O
Affairs O
, O
and O
she O
has O
co O
- O
chaired O
the O
Research O
Network O
on O
New O
Religions O
( O
RENNER O
) O
. O

Cunningham B-PERSON
finished O
3rd O
in O
class O
and O
17th O
overall O
in O
his O
Aston O
Martin O
DB2 O
Vantage O
LML/50/21 O
, O
the O
first O
produced O
. O

Leonard B-PERSON
focuses O
on O
the O
problem O
of O
simultaneous O
localization O
and O
mapping O
( O
SLAM O
) O
, O
particularly O
for O
autonomous O
underwater O
vehicles O
. O

The O
decision O
to O
let O
him O
go O
was O
rescinded O
shortly O
thereafter O
, O
as O
the O
circumstances O
of O
his O
alleged O
comments O
were O
unclear O
, O
but O
Baden B-PERSON
chose O
to O
leave O
the O
position O
nonetheless O
. O

Other O
universities O
that O
lie O
within O
Athens B-LOCATION
are O
the O
Athens O
University O
of O
Economics O
and O
Business O
, O
the O
Panteion O
University O
, O
the O
Agricultural O
University O
of O
Athens O
and O
the O
University O
of O
Piraeus O
. O

At O
Ivanhoe B-LOCATION
in O
1961 O
, O
90 O
Aboriginal O
people O
were O
living O
in O
three O
huts O
. O

Putney B-LOCATION
is O
also O
home O
to O
St O
Chad O
's O
Anglican O
Church O
, O
Delange O
Road O
, O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1912 O
and O
whose O
building O
is O
of O
historical O
significance O
. O

On O
August O
31 O
, O
2017 O
, O
Malone B-PERSON
attempted O
a O
comeback O
to O
professional O
ice O
hockey O
after O
signing O
a O
professional O
try O
- O
out O
( O
PTO O
) O
contract O
with O
the O
Minnesota O
Wild O
to O
attend O
their O
training O
camp O
. O

The O
highlights O
being O
in O
Round O
1 O
when O
Parramatta B-ORGANIZATION
defeated O
Manly O
42 O
- O
12 O
and O
Semi O
Radradra O
scoring O
24 O
tries O
in O
18 O
matches O
. O

Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
fell O
to O
a O
6 O
- O
12 O
defeat O
, O
with O
Declan O
Patton O
scoring O
all O
the O
Wires O
' O
points O
, O
despite O
leading O
6 O
- O
2 O
at O
half O
- O
time O
. O

Bullard B-PERSON
also O
serves O
on O
the O
board O
of O
the O
St. O
Louis O
Regional O
Chamber O
and O
on O
the O
senior O
council O
of O
the O
Central O
Bank O
Research O
Association O
. O

Flynn B-PERSON
released O
several O
studio O
albums O
and O
plays O
folk O
- O
influenced O
songs O
of O
his O
own O
composition O
. O

Wright B-PERSON
now O
does O
public O
relations O
for O
the O
Angels O
. O

Donaldson B-PERSON
has O
been O
working O
in O
comics O
since O
2004 O
. O

Elmer B-PERSON
previously O
held O
faculty O
appointments O
in O
the O
Department O
of O
Communication O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Pittsburgh O
( O
1999–2000 O
) O
, O
Boston O
College O
( O
2000–2003 O
) O
, O
and O
Florida O
State O
University O
( O
2003–2004 O
) O
. O

At O
an O
amateur O
level O
, O
McKay B-PERSON
defeated O
John O
Duddy O
to O
become O
Ulster O
senior O
light O
middleweight O
champion O
. O

Satin B-PERSON
has O
long O
been O
faulted O
for O
mixing O
views O
from O
different O
parts O
of O
his O
political O
odyssey O
. O

The O
lawsuit O
alleged O
that O
Jennings B-PERSON
collected O
but O
failed O
to O
file O
and O
submit O
payroll O
taxes O
collected O
from O
her O
campaign O
staff O
during O
the O
2006 O
election O
. O

Even O
with O
the O
weight O
disadvantage O
, O
Courtney B-PERSON
won O
the O
race O
by O
nearly O
half O
a O
mile O
. O

During O
a O
game O
after O
the O
rule O
change O
, O
Weber B-PERSON
reportedly O
scrambled O
after O
a O
fumble O
out O
- O
of O
- O
bounds O
, O
across O
the O
track O
surrounding O
the O
gridiron O
at O
Ferry O
Field O
. O

Annopol B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
administrative O
district O
of O
Gmina O
Żmudź O
, O
within O
Chełm O
County O
, O
Lublin O
Voivodeship O
, O
in O
eastern O
Poland O
. O

Perelman B-PERSON
had O
a O
problematic O
relationship O
with O
Groucho O
Marx O
, O
who O
once O
said O
of O
the O
writer O
, O
" O
I O
hated O
the O
son O
of O
a O
bitch O
, O
and O
he O
had O
a O
head O
as O
big O
as O
my O
desk O
. O
" O

Boyle B-PERSON
also O
serves O
as O
a O
part O
- O
time O
faculty O
member O
at O
Drexel O
University O
's O
Center O
for O
Public O
Policy O
, O
teaching O
courses O
in O
policy O
and O
campaign O
management O
. O

Hoskins B-PERSON
has O
encouraged O
the O
South O
African O
Super O
14 O
teams O
, O
and O
the O
national O
team O
, O
to O
involve O
a O
higher O
number O
of O
black O
players O
. O

Plagued O
by O
health O
problems O
, O
by O
1901 O
Rollins B-PERSON
had O
hired O
trainer O
Robert O
Healey O
to O
assist O
him O
and O
then O
retired O
in O
1903 O
at O
age O
forty O
- O
six O
. O

Stanmore B-LOCATION
is O
a O
suburb O
in O
the O
Inner O
West O
of O
Sydney O
, O
in O
New O
South O
Wales O
, O
Australia O
6 O
kilometres O
south O
west O
of O
the O
Sydney O
central O
business O
district O
. O

Ultimately O
, O
Stephens B-PERSON
decided O
to O
withdraw O
from O
the O
race O
altogether O
, O
instead O
taking O
a O
nomination O
for O
Supreme O
Court O
Justice O
in O
Queens O
. O

Paris B-LOCATION
was O
laid O
out O
in O
1813 O
on O
a O
stagecoach O
turnpike O
. O

With O
the O
Dumfries O
club O
, O
Malone B-PERSON
won O
promotion O
from O
the O
Scottish O
Second O
Division O
. O

Colleague O
Peter O
Fisher O
began O
working O
in O
1994 O
with O
Yamamoto B-PERSON
. O

Clinton B-PERSON
received O
50 O
electoral O
votes O
to O
77 O
for O
Adams O
. O

As O
an O
ally O
of O
RFC O
Chairman O
Jesse O
H. O
Jones O
, O
Corcoran B-PERSON
exercised O
power O
far O
beyond O
the O
authority O
of O
his O
office O
. O

As O
a O
result O
of O
Spanish O
cultural O
influence O
, O
Manila B-LOCATION
is O
a O
predominantly O
Christian O
city O
. O
, O
Roman O
Catholics O
were O
93.5 O
% O
of O
the O
population O
, O
followed O
by O
adherents O
of O
the O
Philippine O
Independent O
Church O
( O
2.4 O
% O
) O
; O
Iglesia O
ni O
Cristo O
( O
1.9 O
% O
) O
; O
various O
Protestant O
churches O
( O
1.8 O
% O
) O
; O
and O
Buddhists O
( O
1.1 O
% O
) O
. O

Clydesdale B-ORGANIZATION
reached O
the O
first O
Scottish O
Cup O
final O
, O
in O
1874 O
, O
but O
lost O
2–0 O
to O
Queen O
's O
Park O
. O

Clinton B-PERSON
works O
extensively O
with O
social O
justice O
and O
nonprofit O
organizations O
and O
has O
been O
a O
regular O
[ O
emcee O
] O
at O
major O
fundraising O
events O
and O
dinners O
for O
groups O
like O
the O
NYC O
LGBT O
Center O
( O
at O
its O
Annual O
Garden O
Party O
) O
; O
the O
National O
Center O
for O
Lesbian O
Rights O
; O
the O
ACLU O
; O
Out O
& O
Equal O
, O
among O
others O
. O

Calgary O
signed O
Raymond B-PERSON
to O
a O
three O
- O
year O
contract O
worth O
$ O
9.5 O
million O
. O

This O
reason O
led O
to O
more O
difficulties O
finding O
a O
steady O
job O
, O
and O
as O
a O
result O
, O
Schumacher B-PERSON
had O
to O
freelance O
. O

In O
June O
2009 O
, O
Gatehouse B-ORGANIZATION
established O
the O
" O
Milestone O
Capital O
PCC O
programme O
" O
a O
US$ O
1bn O
Sukuk O
issuance O
platform O
that O
enables O
a O
bank O
to O
raise O
funds O
for O
itself O
and O
clients O
from O
Islamic O
capital O
markets O
. O

After O
the O
Champions O
Trophy O
, O
England O
played O
South O
Africa O
in O
3 O
T20Is O
, O
with O
Roy B-PERSON
scoring O
28 O
, O
67 O
and O
8 O
runs O
respectively O
. O

Burke B-PERSON
won O
an O
alternate O
appointment O
to O
the O
United O
States O
Naval O
Academy O
given O
by O
his O
local O
congressman O
. O

The O
following O
season O
saw O
Gormley B-PERSON
move O
into O
central O
midfield O
and O
his O
performances O
there O
saw O
him O
selected O
on O
the O
League O
's O
All O
Star O
team O
. O

Exeter B-ORGANIZATION
uses O
an O
11-point O
grading O
system O
, O
in O
which O
an O
A O
is O
worth O
11 O
points O
and O
an O
E O
is O
worth O
0 O
points O
. O

After O
complaints O
about O
the O
documentary O
titled O
" O
The O
Hereditarily O
Diseased O
" O
, O
the O
Carnegie O
Institution O
of O
Washington O
appointed O
Jennings B-PERSON
to O
review O
the O
work O
of O
Harry O
H. O
Laughlin O
at O
the O
Institution O
's O
Eugenics O
Record O
Office O
, O
then O
part O
of O
what O
has O
become O
the O
Cold O
Spring O
Harbor O
Laboratory O
. O

McKinnon B-PERSON
is O
most O
famous O
for O
her O
interrogation O
of O
Corey O
Worthington O
in O
2008 O
. O

Barnard B-PERSON
is O
a O
Melbourne O
based O
musician O
. O

As O
part O
of O
the O
GAA O
125 O
celebrations O
in O
2009 O
, O
Doyle B-PERSON
was O
chosen O
as O
the O
Tipperary O
representative O
to O
be O
part O
of O
a O
commemorative O
torch O
parade O
through O
Thurles O
on O
the O
day O
of O
the O
Munster O
final O
. O

Malta B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
administrative O
district O
of O
Gmina O
Krzeszyce O
, O
within O
Sulęcin O
County O
, O
Lubusz O
Voivodeship O
, O
in O
western O
Poland O
. O

The O
first O
written O
reference O
to O
Scotland B-LOCATION
was O
in O
320 O
BC O
by O
Greek O
sailor O
Pytheas O
, O
who O
called O
the O
northern O
tip O
of O
Britain O
" O
Orcas O
" O
, O
the O
source O
of O
the O
name O
of O
the O
Orkney O
islands O
. O

The O
city O
government O
did O
little O
to O
publicize O
or O
celebrate O
its O
place O
in O
the O
history O
of O
aviation O
, O
and O
Sharkey B-PERSON
wished O
to O
change O
that O
. O

By O
1910 O
, O
James O
Buchanan O
Duke O
controlled O
Lorillard B-ORGANIZATION
and O
the O
American O
Tobacco O
Company O
even O
as O
it O
kept O
its O
original O
name O
. O

Wright B-PERSON
also O
published O
half O
a O
dozen O
pieces O
of O
his O
own O
fiction O
, O
but O
his O
stories O
are O
considered O
unmemorable O
. O

Tweed B-PERSON
has O
been O
accused O
of O
unethical O
behaviour O
and O
of O
taking O
advantage O
of O
unsophisticated O
shareholders O
. O

McKay B-PERSON
successfully O
appealed O
this O
judgement O
, O
but O
it O
became O
the O
basis O
of O
the O
basic O
wage O
, O
which O
dominated O
Australian O
economic O
life O
for O
the O
next O
60 O
to O
80 O
years O
. O

Accepting O
any O
records O
of O
these O
as O
correct O
, O
however O
, O
shows O
the O
great O
success O
that O
Cooke B-PERSON
had O
at O
the O
program O
, O
and O
he O
is O
by O
far O
the O
winningest O
coach O
in O
Gophers O
basketball O
history O
. O

Townley B-PERSON
finished O
11th O
in O
Truck O
points O
. O

Burke B-PERSON
was O
a O
real O
estate O
salesman O
, O
and O
served O
in O
appointive O
positions O
including O
registrar O
of O
vital O
statistics O
for O
the O
city O
of O
Boston O
. O

Blackett B-PERSON
has O
been O
involved O
in O
politics O
in O
varying O
capacities O
for O
many O
years O
. O

Aurora B-ORGANIZATION
acquired O
a O
license O
from O
Universal O
Studios O
to O
create O
a O
line O
of O
kits O
based O
on O
the O
Universal O
monsters O
, O
which O
became O
the O
company O
’s O
most O
popular O
offerings O
. O

On O
31 O
December O
2013 O
, O
Reid B-PERSON
presented O
the O
" O
New O
Year O
Live O
" O
programme O
on O
BBC O
One O
. O

On O
10 O
August O
2007 O
, O
Lute B-PERSON
stated O
that O
the O
United O
States O
should O
" O
consider O
" O
reinstating O
the O
military O
draft O
to O
relieve O
the O
" O
stressed O
" O
volunteer O
service O
from O
multiple O
tours O
of O
duty O
. O

In O
1969 O
, O
Wright B-PERSON
won O
only O
one O
game O
with O
eight O
losses O
and O
a O
4.10 O
earned O
run O
average O
; O
after O
the O
season O
, O
the O
Angels O
waived O
him O
. O

Also O
in O
2015 O
, O
Adventures O
by O
Disney B-ORGANIZATION
introduced O
several O
shorter O
four- O
and O
five O
- O
day O
" O
Long O
Weekend O
" O
itineraries O
in O
New O
York O
City O
, O
Nashville O
, O
San O
Francisco O
and O
Wyoming O
. O

Doyle B-PERSON
made O
a O
tryout O
, O
and O
later O
became O
one O
of O
two O
hundred O
players O
to O
attend O
the O
first O
AAGPBL O
spring O
training O
outside O
the O
United O
States O
, O
which O
was O
held O
in O
Cuba O
at O
Gran O
Stadium O
de O
La O
Habana O
before O
the O
1947 O
season O
. O

William B-PERSON
also O
benefited O
from O
his O
campaign O
in O
Brittany O
by O
securing O
the O
support O
of O
some O
Breton O
nobles O
who O
went O
on O
to O
support O
the O
invasion O
of O
England O
in O
1066 O
. O

In O
1991 O
, O
Gormley B-PERSON
became O
a O
Professor O
of O
Government O
and O
Public O
Policy O
at O
Georgetown O
University O
, O
where O
he O
still O
teaches O
. O

Blake B-PERSON
reached O
the O
40-point O
plateau O
once O
more O
with O
the O
Sharks O
, O
tallying O
10 O
goals O
and O
35 O
assists O
in O
his O
first O
season O
in O
San O
Jose O
. O

In O
1906 O
, O
J. O
P. O
Morgan O
provided O
Curtis B-PERSON
with O
$ O
75,000 O
to O
produce O
a O
series O
on O
Native O
Americans O
. O

As O
a O
result O
, O
Perkins B-PERSON
developed O
shows O
for O
both O
performers O
, O
in O
the O
form O
of O
Elton O
's O
hosted O
" O
Saturday O
Live O
" O
and O
sketch O
show O
" O
The O
Man O
from O
Auntie O
; O
" O
and O
Enfield O
's O
" O
Harry O
Enfield O
's O
Television O
Programme O
. O
" O

His O
advocacy O
of O
the O
French O
Revolution O
was O
expressed O
through O
an O
odd O
political O
action O
: O
after O
a O
three O
- O
day O
- O
long O
informative O
meeting O
, O
Lux B-PERSON
held O
a O
referendum O
, O
about O
whether O
his O
homeland O
should O
enter O
the O
French O
First O
Republic O
, O
on O
2 O
November O
1792 O
in O
Kostheim O
. O

Cambridge B-LOCATION
is O
a O
Canadian O
parish O
in O
Queens O
County O
, O
New O
Brunswick O
. O

Yasuda B-PERSON
was O
among O
the O
best O
financiers O
that O
Japan O
had O
; O
however O
he O
was O
not O
adventurous O
and O
hardly O
expanded O
the O
business O
beyond O
finance O
. O

The O
allegations O
caused O
the O
other O
judges O
of O
the O
Court O
to O
condemn O
Douglas O
and O
lend O
their O
support O
to O
Blair B-PERSON
. O

The O
struggles O
of O
Steve O
Blass O
kept O
Ellis B-PERSON
in O
the O
starting O
rotation O
, O
as O
Blass O
was O
moved O
to O
the O
bullpen O
. O

In O
February O
2001 O
, O
the O
Columbus O
Crew O
selected O
Tennyson B-PERSON
in O
the O
fourth O
round O
( O
39th O
overall O
) O
in O
the O
2001 O
MLS O
SuperDraft O
. O

Roy B-PERSON
announced O
in O
January O
2014 O
that O
he O
would O
retire O
at O
the O
. O

Ellis B-PERSON
has O
a O
USSF O
Pro O
coaching O
licence O
; O
with O
coaching O
experiences O
that O
includes O
multiple O
stints O
for O
the O
under-20 O
and O
under-21 O
national O
teams O
, O
and O
an O
impressive O
record O
as O
a O
UCLA O
Bruins O
coach O
. O

In O
1952 O
, O
Cunningham B-PERSON
introduced O
the O
Continental O
C3 O
road O
car O
. O

During O
the O
2012–13 O
season O
, O
Yeo B-PERSON
accused O
the O
San O
Jose O
Sharks O
players O
of O
embellishing O
penalties O
, O
and O
had O
to O
call O
Todd O
McLellan O
to O
apologize O
. O

Here O
, O
in O
the O
period O
before O
Pearl O
Harbor O
, O
Ellis B-PERSON
briefed O
J O
Edgar O
Hoover O
in O
counter O
- O
espionage O
techniques O
. O

By O
1958 O
Clarke B-PERSON
shifted O
to O
the O
flourishing O
rhythm O
and O
blues O
, O
and O
rock O
scene O
, O
joining O
Vince O
Eager O
's O
Beat O
Boys O
, O
composed O
of O
Tony O
Belcher O
( O
guitar O
) O
, O
Alan O
Le O
Claire O
( O
born O
Alan O
Cocks O
, O
26 O
August O
1938 O
; O
piano O
) O
, O
and O
Tex O
Makins O
( O
born O
Anthony O
Paul O
Makins O
, O
3 O
July O
1940 O
; O
bass O
) O
, O
who O
performed O
at O
a O
London O
coffee O
bar O
. O

Wyatt B-PERSON
then O
produced O
a O
set O
of O
working O
drawings O
, O
which O
included O
detailed O
instructions O
for O
the O
Neoclassical O
decoration O
. O

Tiller B-PERSON
was O
released O
August O
30 O
, O
2014 O
. O

There O
is O
a O
monument O
to O
McKay B-PERSON
in O
South O
Boston O
, O
near O
Fort O
Independence O
, O
overlooking O
the O
channel O
, O
that O
lists O
all O
his O
ships O
. O

Two O
months O
later O
, O
it O
was O
announced O
that O
Ruby B-PERSON
would O
be O
raped O
as O
part O
of O
a O
sexual O
consent O
storyline O
. O

The O
jury O
in O
that O
case O
found O
that O
the O
article O
in O
question O
did O
contain O
" O
an O
imputation O
" O
that O
Cairns B-PERSON
was O
" O
improperly O
involved O
with O
his O
assistant O
, O
Junie O
Morosi O
, O
in O
a O
romantic O
or O
sexual O
association O
" O
, O
but O
that O
this O
statement O
was O
not O
defamatory O
. O

Bradford B-ORGANIZATION
lost O
8–3 O
to O
Wigan O
and O
Frank O
Whitcombe O
became O
the O
first O
player O
to O
win O
the O
Lance O
Todd O
trophy O
on O
the O
losing O
side O
. O

Koren B-PERSON
began O
work O
on O
a O
new O
prayerbook O
in O
the O
1970s O
. O

Curtis B-PERSON
chose O
the O
Kwakiutl O
tribe O
, O
of O
the O
Queen O
Charlotte O
Strait O
region O
of O
the O
Central O
Coast O
of O
British O
Columbia O
, O
Canada O
, O
for O
his O
subject O
. O

Despite O
his O
size O
, O
however O
, O
Huber B-PERSON
was O
primarily O
an O
offensive O
defender O
. O

Raymond B-PERSON
advocates O
the O
use O
of O
intelligence O
by O
human O
rights O
groups O
and O
other O
non O
- O
governmental O
organizations O
. O

Later O
in O
the O
over O
, O
another O
leg O
side O
ball O
hit O
his O
pads O
, O
rolled O
between O
his O
legs O
and O
onto O
the O
stumps O
, O
meaning O
that O
Waugh B-PERSON
missed O
out O
on O
his O
century O
. O

Apart O
from O
one O
year O
working O
for O
the O
Food O
and O
Drug O
Administration O
, O
Ellis B-PERSON
remained O
at O
Caltech O
until O
World O
War O
II O
. O

In O
1951 O
, O
Cooke B-PERSON
ventured O
into O
sports O
, O
acquiring O
the O
minor O
league O
Toronto O
Maple O
Leafs O
baseball O
club O
. O

Jericho B-LOCATION
in O
1887 O
is O
described O
( O
probably O
inaccurately O
) O
as O
" O
haunted O
by O
drunkards O
, O
thieves O
, O
and O
the O
lowest O
sort O
of O
brazen O
female O
as O
ever O
lifted O
her O
petticoats O
" O
. O

With O
players O
such O
as O
Ieuan O
Evans O
amongst O
the O
squad O
, O
Llanelli B-ORGANIZATION
won O
the O
Welsh O
Cup O
five O
times O
in O
eight O
years O
between O
1985 O
and O
1993 O
including O
in O
consecutive O
seasons O
in O
1991,1992 O
and O
1993 O
. O

Lutz B-PERSON
earned O
six O
battle O
stars O
: O
Tunisia O
, O
Sicily O
, O
Rome O
- O
Arno O
, O
Southern O
France O
, O
and O
North O
Apennines O
. O

This O
was O
later O
to O
become O
a O
major O
part O
of O
the O
Otago B-LOCATION
fishing O
industry O
. O

Additionally O
, O
Wolfson B-PERSON
has O
been O
the O
recipient O
of O
several O
academic O
honors O
and O
awards O
: O

Rennie B-PERSON
introduced O
several O
innovative O
concepts O
to O
goalkeeping O
in O
Scottish O
football O
. O

The O
school O
's O
music O
curriculum O
consisted O
of O
marches O
, O
waltzes O
and O
classical O
pieces O
which O
gave O
Ellis B-PERSON
an O
extensive O
knowledge O
of O
timing O
, O
harmony O
and O
form O
. O

From O
February O
to O
April O
2004 O
, O
Donaldson B-PERSON
completed O
the O
SASR O
selection O
course O
, O
and O
was O
posted O
to O
3 O
Squadron O
in O
May O
2004 O
. O

For O
his O
work O
at O
the O
Army O
War O
College O
, O
Clarke B-PERSON
was O
awarded O
the O
General O
Dwight O
D. O
Eisenhower O
Chair O
in O
National O
Security O
in O
1994 O
. O

Andreas B-PERSON
also O
maintained O
a O
family O
residence O
on O
Sydney O
Harbour O
at O
Elamang O
Avenue O
, O
Kirribilli O
. O

Vidal B-PERSON
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Catholic O
Writers O
Guild O
and O
the O
Eastern O
Shore O
Writers O
Association O
. O

In O
1927 O
, O
Weber B-PERSON
scored O
two O
touchdowns O
against O
Wisconsin O
in O
Fielding O
H. O
Yost O
's O
last O
game O
as O
Michigan O
's O
football O
coach O
( O
also O
the O
last O
Michigan O
football O
game O
played O
at O
Ferry O
Field O
) O
. O

Other O
companies O
based O
in O
Austin B-LOCATION
include O
NXP O
Semiconductors O
, O
GoodPop O
, O
Temple O
- O
Inland O
, O
Sweet O
Leaf O
Tea O
Company O
, O
Keller O
Williams O
Realty O
, O
National O
Western O
Life O
, O
GSD&M O
, O
Dimensional O
Fund O
Advisors O
, O
Golfsmith O
, O
Forestar O
Group O
, O
EZCorp O
, O
Outdoor O
Voices O
, O
Tito O
's O
Vodka O
, O
Indeed O
, O
Speak O
Social O
, O
and O
YETI O
. O

Bullard B-PERSON
launched O
a O
legal O
action O
for O
defamation O
in O
August O
2018 O
against O
" O
Chatelaine O
" O
magazine O
, O
one O
of O
its O
writers O
, O
and O
its O
publisher O
, O
Rogers O
Media O
, O
asking O
for O
$ O
6 O
million O
in O
damages O
after O
it O
published O
an O
interview O
with O
Cynthia O
Mulligan O
. O

Barnard B-PERSON
has O
indicated O
that O
the O
album O
was O
inspired O
by O
" O
" O
the O
power O
of O
nature O
, O
love O
, O
the O
fragile O
beauty O
of O
planet O
Earth O
" O
" O
, O
and O
that O
this O
is O
reflected O
in O
the O
lyrics O
. O

Poor O
league O
performance O
continued O
in O
1977–78 O
but O
Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
again O
made O
it O
to O
the O
Regal O
trophy O
final O
. O

Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
won O
the O
Lancashire O
Cup O
Final O
a O
year O
later O
in O
1989 O
. O

Barnard B-PERSON
is O
known O
for O
being O
very O
reclusive O
, O
refusing O
virtually O
all O
media O
interviews O
and O
rarely O
making O
public O
appearances O
. O

Born O
in O
Bari O
, O
graduated O
in O
law O
, O
Noto B-PERSON
became O
first O
known O
as O
radio O
- O
host O
after O
the O
first O
World O
War O
. O

Hank B-PERSON
also O
created O
the O
Cuauhtémoc O
Hank O
Foundation O
to O
give O
scholarships O
to O
students O
of O
all O
grades O
including O
studies O
in O
foreign O
schools O
. O

In O
2005 O
, O
Ellis B-PERSON
began O
teaching O
weekly O
classes O
for O
individuals O
convicted O
of O
driving O
under O
the O
influence O
. O

Rowett O
suggested O
the O
damage O
could O
have O
been O
less O
serious O
had O
Donaldson O
not O
played O
the O
whole O
match O
despite O
being O
obviously O
unfit O
, O
but O
Jamaica O
coach O
Winfried O
Schäfer O
denied O
the O
accusations O
, O
stating O
that O
he O
had O
wanted O
to O
substitute O
Donaldson B-PERSON
but O
the O
player O
insisted O
on O
continuing O
. O

However O
, O
the O
geologist O
Henry O
Faul O
has O
criticized O
Corliss B-PERSON
. O

The O
" O
Washington O
Post O
" O
referred O
to O
Rasmussen B-PERSON
as O
" O
a O
driving O
force O
in O
American O
politics O
" O
and O
" O
an O
articulate O
and O
frequent O
guest O
on O
Fox O
News O
and O
other O
outlets O
, O
where O
his O
nominally O
nonpartisan O
data O
is O
often O
cited O
to O
support O
Republican O
talking O
points O
. O
" O

Tennyson O
had O
reworked O
the O
romance O
tales O
of O
Arthur B-PERSON
to O
suit O
and O
comment O
upon O
the O
issues O
of O
his O
day O
, O
and O
the O
same O
is O
often O
the O
case O
with O
modern O
treatments O
too O
. O

Rennie B-PERSON
is O
also O
the O
marketer O
for O
condominiums O
at O
the O
former O
2010 O
Olympic O
Village O
, O
a O
project O
that O
has O
been O
the O
subject O
of O
controversy O
and O
extensive O
media O
attention O
around O
the O
project O
's O
financial O
challenges O
for O
several O
years O
. O

In O
2011 O
, O
Atlas B-ORGANIZATION
purchased O
the O
tooling O
and O
inventory O
of O
Branchline O
Trains O
, O
including O
their O
line O
of O
HO O
scale O
" O
Blueprint O
Series O
" O
and O
" O
Yardmaster O
" O
freight O
cars O
and O
passenger O
cars O
. O

Unfortunately O
for O
the O
Yankees O
, O
because O
the O
trade O
came O
after O
August O
31 O
, O
Ramos B-PERSON
was O
not O
eligible O
to O
pitch O
in O
the O
World O
Series O
, O
which O
New O
York O
lost O
in O
seven O
games O
to O
the O
Bob O
Gibson O
- O
led O
St. O
Louis O
Cardinals O
. O

Unusually O
, O
two O
years O
prior O
to O
his O
graduating O
with O
and O
possessing O
a O
law O
degree O
, O
Murphy B-PERSON
passed O
the O
Barristers O
' O
Admission O
Board O
examination O
and O
was O
admitted O
to O
the O
New O
South O
Wales O
Bar O
Association O
in O
1947 O
. O

Initially O
under O
Turkish O
rule O
from O
Algiers O
, O
soon O
the O
Ottoman O
Porte O
appointed O
directly O
for O
Tunis B-LOCATION
a O
governor O
called O
the O
Pasha O
supported O
by O
janissary O
forces O
. O

Atlas B-ORGANIZATION
also O
assists O
personnel O
who O
self O
- O
move O
. O

Roy B-PERSON
scored O
just O
4 O
runs O
in O
the O
final O
and O
deciding O
match O
of O
the O
series O
as O
England O
collapsed O
to O
138 O
all O
out O
. O

In O
early O
October O
1845 O
, O
in O
Cincinnati O
, O
Ohio O
, O
Blanchard B-PERSON
debated O
the O
morality O
of O
slavery O
with O
fellow O
Presbyterian O
minister O
Nathan O
Lewis O
Rice O
( O
December O
29 O
, O
1807 O
- O
June O
11 O
, O
1877 O
) O
. O

In O
September O
2011 O
, O
Fudge B-PERSON
was O
one O
of O
six O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
honorees O
named O
in O
advance O
of O
the O
National O
Association O
of O
Corporate O
Directors O
November O
gala O
in O
New O
York O
City O
. O

The O
stone O
- O
lined O
palisades O
and O
ditches O
built O
at O
Bedford B-LOCATION
were O
very O
unusual O
in O
England O
– O
their O
closest O
equivalent O
are O
those O
found O
at O
Skenfrith O
Castle O
in O
Wales O
. O

Adams O
- O
Schneider O
was O
succeeded O
by O
National O
's O
Simon O
Upton O
, O
who O
won O
the O
and O
started O
his O
long O
parliamentary O
career O
with O
one O
term O
in O
Waikato B-LOCATION
. O

Corm B-PERSON
is O
considered O
one O
of O
the O
most O
influential O
and O
awarded O
Middle O
Eastern O
writers O
. O

Bradley B-PERSON
entered O
into O
obstetrics O
in O
1947 O
; O
at O
the O
time O
mothers O
were O
restrained O
in O
large O
cribs O
and O
wore O
protective O
helmets O
to O
protect O
their O
heads O
from O
hitting O
the O
sides O
of O
the O
crib O
due O
to O
the O
effect O
of O
the O
medication O
they O
were O
given O
. O

Historical O
subdivisions O
of O
Scotland B-LOCATION
included O
the O
mormaerdom O
, O
stewartry O
, O
earldom O
, O
burgh O
, O
parish O
, O
county O
and O
regions O
and O
districts O
. O

In O
response O
, O
Cunningham B-PERSON
said O
in O
an O
interview O
with O
CNN O
following O
the O
rally O
: O
" O
John O
McCain O
threw O
me O
under O
a O
bus O
... O

Wright B-PERSON
was O
listed O
as O
a O
co O
- O
starter O
with O
Starling O
on O
the O
official O
end O
- O
of O
- O
spring O
depth O
chart O
that O
was O
released O
on O
April O
16 O
, O
2012 O
. O

Dover B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
within O
Guysborough O
County O
in O
Nova O
Scotia O
, O
Canada O
. O

On O
20 O
September O
2016 O
, O
BBC O
Northern O
Ireland O
's O
" O
Spotlight O
" O
aired O
a O
programme O
in O
which O
a O
British O
spy O
( O
known O
only O
as O
" O
Martin O
" O
) O
who O
had O
infiltrated O
the O
IRA O
claimed O
that O
Murphy O
and O
other O
leading O
South O
Armagh O
Republicans O
had O
demanded O
the O
killing O
of O
Donaldson B-PERSON
and O
that O
it O
would O
have O
been O
sanctioned O
by O
Gerry O
Adams O
. O

Escobar B-PERSON
had O
a O
very O
strong O
spring O
training O
for O
the O
Braves O
in O
2007 O
before O
being O
sent O
down O
to O
Triple O
- O
A O
Richmond O
to O
start O
the O
season O
. O

Oxford B-LOCATION
is O
a O
small O
town O
of O
around O
2,100 O
people O
serving O
the O
farming O
community O
of O
North O
Canterbury O
, O
New O
Zealand O
. O

Although O
reviews O
of O
the O
product O
line O
were O
very O
favorable O
, O
Calico B-ORGANIZATION
is O
working O
to O
secure O
military O
and O
law O
enforcement O
and O
export O
contracts O
. O

Raymond B-PERSON
has O
recommended O
that O
Congress O
modify O
the O
War O
Crimes O
Act O
to O
strengthen O
its O
prohibition O
against O
human O
experimentation O
, O
and O
that O
state O
governments O
specifically O
prohibit O
health O
care O
professionals O
from O
participating O
in O
torture O
or O
the O
improper O
treatment O
of O
prisoners O
. O

Calico B-ORGANIZATION
remains O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
manufacturers O
of O
large O
magazines O
for O
automatic O
and O
semi O
- O
automatic O
weapons O
( O
50 O
and O
100 O
rounds O
) O
. O

Cunningham B-PERSON
emerged O
as O
the O
victor O
with O
a O
majority O
of O
1,311 O
votes O
over O
the O
Conservative O
candidate O
Martine O
Hyams O
; O
Nellist O
finished O
third O
but O
only O
by O
a O
further O
40 O
votes O
. O

Quinn B-PERSON
set O
a O
record O
for O
the O
Cleveland O
Browns O
that O
day O
being O
the O
only O
QB O
in O
franchise O
history O
to O
throw O
3 O
touchdowns O
in O
one O
quarter O
. O

Darryl O
van O
der O
Velde O
took O
Castleford B-ORGANIZATION
to O
the O
Challenge O
Cup O
final O
at O
Wembley O
in O
1992 O
where O
they O
were O
defeated O
by O
Wigan O
. O

Stoke O
had O
an O
awful O
1997–98 O
campaign O
which O
saw O
them O
relegated O
to O
the O
third O
tier O
with O
Tweed B-PERSON
playing O
in O
44 O
matches O
that O
season O
. O

At O
the O
onset O
of O
the O
initial O
retirement O
dates O
of O
Generals O
Ashfaq O
Parvez O
Kayani O
and O
Tariq O
Majid O
at O
the O
end O
of O
2010 O
, O
Wynne B-PERSON
would O
have O
been O
the O
senior O
- O
most O
general O
in O
the O
Pakistan O
Army O
and O
thus O
a O
candidate O
for O
a O
four O
- O
star O
post O
. O

Sky B-ORGANIZATION
now O
has O
280 O
branches O
. O

The O
video O
artwork O
was O
perceived O
by O
some O
to O
be O
anti O
- O
Christian O
and O
Clough B-PERSON
believed O
it O
detracted O
from O
the O
entirety O
of O
the O
exhibition O
, O
which O
he O
said O
was O
" O
to O
be O
a O
powerful O
exhibit O
about O
the O
contributions O
of O
gay O
and O
lesbian O
artists O
" O
and O
not O
about O
" O
religious O
iconography O
" O
and O
" O
desecration O
" O
. O

Macdonald B-PERSON
sought O
Liberal O
Party O
nomination O
to O
run O
for O
election O
to O
the O
House O
of O
Commons O
of O
Canada O
for O
the O
1926 O
election O
, O
but O
lost O
the O
nomination O
by O
a O
single O
vote O
. O

Egbert B-PERSON
commissioned O
the O
compilation O
of O
the O
" O
Registrum O
Gregorii O
" O
from O
the O
letters O
of O
Pope O
Gregory O
the O
Great O
, O
and O
produced O
a O
magnificently O
illuminated O
copy O
. O

In O
1990 O
, O
Courtney B-PERSON
began O
purchasing O
pharmaceuticals O
on O
the O
gray O
market O
and O
using O
them O
to O
fill O
prescriptions O
at O
his O
pharmacy O
. O

With O
his O
third O
show O
cancelled O
and O
his O
work O
confiscated O
by O
the O
police O
because O
of O
its O
content O
, O
Urquiza B-PERSON
left O
the O
country O
travelling O
to O
Paris O
, O
London O
, O
Berlin O
, O
Kenya O
and O
Egypt O
, O
moving O
then O
to O
Brasil O
on O
account O
of O
a O
lifelong O
fascination O
with O
bossa O
nova O
and O
tropicalismo O
. O

Zenith B-ORGANIZATION
held O
the O
motorcycle O
world O
speed O
record O
on O
two O
occasions O
, O
the O
first O
FIM O
record O
of O
set O
in O
1928 O
by O
Owen O
M. O
Baldwin O
at O
Arpajon O
, O
France O
, O
the O
site O
of O
the O
Autodrome O
de O
Linas O
- O
Montlhéry O
. O

The O
name O
of O
the O
original O
farm O
was O
therefore O
most O
likely O
changed O
to O
California B-LOCATION
at O
some O
point O
before O
1839 O
. O

Dunstall B-PERSON
has O
also O
hosted O
various O
television O
shows O
, O
including O
the O
Seven O
Network O
's O
" O
Live O
and O
Kicking O
" O
and O
Fox O
Footy O
's O
" O
Saturday O
Central O
" O
( O
with O
Wayne O
Carey O
) O
, O
" O
On O
the O
Couch O
" O
and O
" O
League O
Teams O
" O
. O

Together O
these O
two O
facilities O
employ O
a O
large O
number O
of O
engineers O
and O
Cummins B-ORGANIZATION
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
employers O
in O
Daventry O
. O

Trinity B-ORGANIZATION
voluntarily O
stopped O
shipping O
the O
ET O
Plus O
until O
the O
additional O
crash O
testing O
requested O
by O
the O
FHWA O
could O
be O
completed O
. O

Pierrot B-PERSON
has O
challenged O
himself O
in O
various O
fields O
of O
art O
. O

In O
2014 O
, O
McKinnon B-PERSON
launched O
Mayday O
PAC O
to O
force O
ethics O
reform O
in O
the O
United O
States O
Congress O
, O
along O
with O
Harvard O
Professor O
Larry O
Lessig O
-- O
who O
would O
later O
run O
for O
President O
on O
a O
related O
push O
for O
ethics O
and O
campaign O
finance O
reform O
-- O
and O
tech O
moguls O
Steve O
Wozniak O
, O
Fred O
Wilson O
, O
Peter O
Thiel O
, O
and O
Reid O
Hoffman O
. O

Surrey O
had O
strengthened O
their O
batting O
resources O
over O
the O
preceding O
winter O
, O
confirming O
the O
long O
term O
signing O
of O
Kevin O
Pietersen O
, O
as O
well O
as O
bringing O
in O
new O
batsmen O
Zander O
de O
Bruyn O
and O
Tom O
Maynard O
, O
and O
Roy B-PERSON
began O
the O
season O
in O
the O
Second O
XI O
. O

Heavily O
in O
debt O
, O
Clinton B-PERSON
lobbied O
the O
Duke O
of O
Newcastle O
for O
profitable O
employment O
as O
an O
American O
governor O
: O
he O
was O
appointed O
Governor O
of O
the O
Province O
of O
New O
York O
in O
July O
1741 O
and O
arrived O
in O
New O
York O
in O
September O
1743 O
to O
take O
up O
his O
position O
. O

Opperman B-PERSON
finished O
the O
Tour O
18th O
. O

Sharkey B-PERSON
holds O
degrees O
in O
Russian O
and O
Russian O
history O
from O
University O
College O
Dublin O
and O
Birmingham O
University O
. O

On O
14 O
July O
2008 O
Pilgrim B-PERSON
suffered O
a O
sudden O
and O
severe O
heart O
attack O
in O
his O
doctors O
office O
. O

Constantine B-PERSON
could O
be O
wasteful O
with O
the O
imperial O
treasury O
. O

Coyote B-PERSON
toured O
in O
2019 O
with O
musician O
Sarah O
MacDougall O
, O
performing O
selections O
from O
the O
book O
along O
with O
music O
. O

Devine B-PERSON
ended O
the O
season O
with O
1,316 O
all O
- O
purpose O
yards O
, O
the O
21st O
most O
in O
a O
single O
- O
season O
in O
school O
history O
. O

Raymond B-PERSON
developed O
a O
prospectus O
for O
aspiring O
architects O
to O
come O
and O
live O
and O
study O
at O
New O
Hope O
and O
he O
attracted O
at O
least O
20 O
. O

Coombs B-PERSON
began O
the O
2018 O
Toronto O
Argonauts O
season O
on O
the O
one O
- O
game O
injured O
list O
before O
being O
transferred O
to O
the O
six O
- O
game O
injured O
list O
as O
he O
recovered O
from O
an O
ankle O
injury O
. O

In O
the O
13th O
century O
, O
Manila B-LOCATION
consisted O
of O
a O
fortified O
settlement O
and O
trading O
quarter O
on O
the O
shore O
of O
the O
Pasig O
River O
. O

On O
6 O
August O
2013 O
, O
Nicastro B-PERSON
and O
Ameth O
Fall O
were O
signed O
by O
Rimini O
. O

Libby B-PERSON
sits O
on O
the O
Executive O
Committee O
of O
the O
Maine O
State O
Pomological O
Society O
. O

In O
1950 O
, O
Renault B-ORGANIZATION
was O
the O
largest O
tractor O
manufacturer O
within O
France O
, O
producing O
8,549 O
units O
, O
the O
58 O
% O
of O
the O
country O
's O
total O
production O
. O

Bavaria B-LOCATION
is O
a O
ward O
of O
the O
municipality O
of O
Nervesa O
della O
Battaglia O
in O
Treviso O
province O
. O

Though O
in O
actuality O
, O
Adam O
has O
rarely O
been O
seen O
in O
the O
stories O
after O
that O
story O
arc O
, O
and O
Betty B-PERSON
has O
continued O
to O
prefer O
Archie O
. O

Richard B-PERSON
donated O
a O
mill O
at O
Evreux O
to O
the O
abbey O
of O
Jumièges O
by O
charter O
dated O
[ O
26 O
Mar O
1038/14 O
Apr O
1039 O
] O
. O

In O
2014 O
, O
Cousin B-PERSON
was O
ranked O
number O
45th O
on O
the O
Forbes O
Magazine O
's O
List O
of O
The O
World O
's O
100 O
Most O
Powerful O
Women O
and O
she O
was O
named O
to O
the O
" O
TIME O
" O
100 O
most O
influential O
people O
in O
the O
world O
list O
. O

Chrysler B-ORGANIZATION
recruited O
both O
local O
men O
and O
young O
single O
men O
from O
interstate O
to O
staff O
the O
growth O
. O

In O
December O
2018 O
, O
Sugar B-PERSON
announced O
during O
a O
television O
interview O
that O
he O
would O
leave O
Britain O
if O
Corbyn O
became O
prime O
minister O
. O

Nolan B-PERSON
was O
censured O
by O
several O
white O
officers O
for O
allowing O
Flipper O
into O
his O
quarters O
for O
dinner O
, O
where O
his O
daughter O
Kate O
was O
present O
. O

Pye O
Records O
asked O
Curtis B-PERSON
to O
delay O
the O
release O
of O
the O
Ryans O
' O
version O
so O
that O
the O
Searchers O
could O
release O
it O
. O

In O
2008 O
, O
Townley B-PERSON
signed O
with O
Team O
Honda O
Red O
Bull O
Racing O
to O
contest O
the O
2008 O
Supercross O
/ O
Motocross O
season O
riding O
the O
Honda O
CR250F O
for O
the O
Supercross O
series O
and O
the O
CR450F O
for O
the O
Motocross O
series O
. O

Under O
coach O
Siri O
Lindley O
, O
Ellis B-PERSON
experienced O
some O
success O
in O
her O
first O
year O
of O
ITU O
racing O
in O
2006 O
. O

Cooke B-PERSON
was O
a O
coach O
through O
June O
30 O
, O
1952 O
, O
including O
service O
on O
the O
1950 O
" O
Whiz O
Kids O
" O
team O
, O
that O
won O
the O
National O
League O
pennant O
. O

Texas B-LOCATION
was O
composed O
by O
James O
Blundell O
and O
Doug O
Trevor O
, O
with O
Blundell O
and O
M. O
Hickson O
writing O
Cloncurry O
Cattle O
Song O
. O

While O
mayor O
of O
Dayton O
, O
Leonard B-PERSON
was O
known O
as O
outgoing O
and O
youth O
- O
oriented O
, O
sometimes O
called O
" O
the O
Rock O
' O
N O
' O
Roll O
Mayor O
of O
Dayton O
. O
" O

Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
beat O
24–9 O
Featherstone O
Rovers O
for O
the O
second O
time O
that O
season O
in O
a O
cup O
final O
to O
win O
the O
Challenge O
Cup O
. O

The O
two O
teams O
met O
again O
two O
weeks O
later O
, O
with O
Macdonald B-PERSON
once O
again O
captaining O
the O
New O
Zealand O
side O
. O

Hester B-PERSON
finished O
the O
season O
with O
six O
kicks O
returned O
for O
touchdowns O
, O
which O
set O
a O
league O
record O
. O

Burke B-PERSON
began O
the O
2007 O
season O
on O
the O
Astros O
' O
Opening O
Day O
roster O
, O
but O
was O
optioned O
to O
Round O
Rock O
on O
May O
11 O
. O

This O
was O
supported O
by O
the O
fact O
that O
Weir B-PERSON
purchased O
two O
paintings O
by O
Manet O
during O
the O
summers O
of O
1880 O
and O
1881 O
, O
" O
Woman O
with O
a O
Parrot O
" O
and O
" O
Boy O
with O
a O
Sword O
" O
, O
for O
the O
New O
York O
collector O
Erwin O
Davis O
. O

At O
the O
end O
of O
the O
2010/2011 O
Aviva O
Premiership O
campaign O
, O
Percival B-PERSON
left O
Harlequins O
and O
signed O
a O
2-year O
contract O
which O
saw O
him O
return O
to O
the O
newly O
promoted O
Worcester O
Warriors O
, O
and O
the O
club O
where O
he O
started O
his O
career O
. O

Born O
1846 O
in O
County O
Cavan O
and O
raised O
in O
Newark O
, O
New O
Jersey O
, O
Leonard B-PERSON
is O
commonly O
recognized O
as O
the O
first O
native O
of O
Ireland O
to O
play O
in O
the O
major O
leagues O
. O

Before O
the O
2010 O
- O
11 O
I O
- O
League O
season O
Santosh B-PERSON
signed O
for O
I O
- O
League O
club O
Air O
India O
FC O
. O

Two O
months O
later O
, O
although O
Beale B-PERSON
still O
suffered O
from O
the O
effects O
his O
adventure O
, O
Stockton O
again O
sent O
him O
east O
with O
dispatches O
. O

The O
former O
Brighton O
Municipal O
Offices O
, O
now O
the O
Brighton B-LOCATION
library O
and O
council O
chamber O
, O
were O
designed O
by O
K. O
F. O
Knight O
in O
1959 O
- O
60 O
are O
a O
red O
brick O
miniature O
of O
Frank O
Lloyd O
Wright O
's O
Guggenheim O
Museum O
in O
New O
York O
City O
. O

Doyle B-PERSON
was O
now O
in O
the O
twilight O
of O
his O
career O
, O
however O
, O
he O
was O
picked O
for O
the O
Munster O
team O
for O
the O
twelfth O
time O
in O
thirteen O
years O
in O
1970 O
. O

Ellis B-PERSON
sold O
a O
number O
of O
his O
shares O
at O
flotation O
, O
reducing O
his O
shareholding O
to O
around O
39 O
% O
of O
the O
total O
shares O
. O

In O
the O
spring O
of O
2009 O
, O
Meyers B-PERSON
re O
- O
introduced O
the O
shortened O
wheelbase O
. O

Australia O
proceeded O
to O
Zimbabwe O
, O
where O
Waugh B-PERSON
scored O
90 O
in O
a O
ten O
- O
wicket O
win O
. O

Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
secured O
Super O
League O
status O
with O
seven O
wins O
out O
of O
seven O
. O

Malone B-PERSON
was O
the O
longtime O
president O
of O
the O
Pennsylvania O
Manufacturers O
Association O
after O
he O
retired O
from O
his O
District O
Attorney O
Duties O
. O

In O
addition O
, O
Cunningham B-PERSON
provided O
financial O
backing O
to O
Otis O
B. O
Moorehead O
late O
in O
1915 O
, O
to O
start O
a O
new O
vacuum O
tube O
company O
, O
called O
Moorehead O
Laboratories O
also O
based O
in O
San O
Francisco O
, O
CA O
. O

The O
concluding O
message O
suggested O
that O
Kay B-PERSON
would O
be O
releasing O
new O
material O
in O
September O
2012 O
, O
but O
no O
further O
detail O
was O
given O
. O

Packard O
F.C. O
of O
Detroit O
, O
Michigan O
, O
was O
an O
early O
twentieth O
century O
U.S. O
soccer O
team O
sponsored O
by O
the O
Packard B-ORGANIZATION
automobile O
corporation O
. O

Devine B-PERSON
founded O
Trilobyte O
in O
December O
1990 O
with O
Rob O
Landeros O
. O

In O
1996 O
Raymond B-PERSON
took O
over O
development O
of O
the O
open O
- O
source O
email O
software O
" O
popclient O
" O
, O
renaming O
it O
to O
Fetchmail O
. O

Toronto B-LOCATION
was O
originally O
the O
site O
of O
an O
Aboriginal O
mission O
called O
Ebenezer O
, O
established O
in O
1829 O
by O
Reverend O
Threlkeld O
. O

Almora B-LOCATION
had O
a O
population O
of O
32,358 O
according O
to O
the O
2001 O
Census O
of O
India O
. O

Westmount B-LOCATION
was O
a O
former O
provincial O
electoral O
district O
located O
in O
the O
Montreal O
region O
of O
Quebec O
, O
Canada O
. O

During O
the O
2009 O
close O
season O
, O
Tweed B-PERSON
introduced O
12 O
new O
players O
, O
with O
Jim O
Moffatt O
( O
assistant O
) O
and O
Tony O
Bullock O
( O
goalkeeping O
) O
helping O
with O
coaching O
. O

Ismail B-PERSON
also O
appointed O
Najm O
- O
e O
Sani O
as O
the O
new O
" O
vakil O
" O
of O
the O
empire O
due O
to O
the O
death O
of O
Mas'ud O
Gilani O
. O

Kraśnik B-LOCATION
is O
a O
town O
in O
eastern O
Poland O
with O
35,602 O
inhabitants O
( O
2012 O
) O
, O
situated O
in O
the O
Lublin O
Voivodeship O
, O
historic O
Lesser O
Poland O
. O

After O
their O
own O
house O
was O
destroyed O
in O
the O
Great O
Kantō O
earthquake O
, O
Raymond B-PERSON
designed O
a O
new O
one O
, O
the O
Reinanzaka O
House O
, O
in O
Azabu O
, O
Tokyo O
. O

In O
later O
years O
after O
the O
court O
decision O
, O
Cunningham B-PERSON
played O
a O
bigger O
part O
in O
RCA O
's O
business O
activities O
. O

The O
Dublin B-LOCATION
community O
slowly O
withered O
away O
after O
1900 O
, O
and O
in O
the O
1960s O
the O
townsite O
was O
bisected O
by O
a O
realignment O
of O
U.S. O
Route O
71 O
, O
which O
included O
construction O
of O
a O
larger O
, O
modern O
viaduct O
across O
the O
railroad O
and O
Coon O
Creek O
. O

From O
2008 O
to O
2012 O
, O
Dover B-ORGANIZATION
acquired O
almost O
twenty O
- O
five O
companies O
. O

Cory B-PERSON
was O
a O
grand O
finalist O
and O
runner O
- O
up O
in O
season O
one O
of O
NBC O
's O
" O
Last O
Comic O
Standing O
" O
. O

Established O
in O
1753 O
, O
the O
town O
of O
Portsmouth B-LOCATION
functioned O
as O
a O
lightering O
port O
, O
where O
cargo O
from O
ocean O
- O
going O
vessels O
could O
be O
transferred O
to O
shallow O
- O
draft O
vessels O
capable O
of O
traversing O
Pamlico O
and O
Core O
Sounds O
. O

Athens B-LOCATION
is O
located O
at O
, O
six O
miles O
east O
of O
Rochester O
along O
Indiana O
State O
Road O
14 O
. O

Brampton B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
Eden O
district O
, O
in O
the O
county O
of O
Cumbria O
, O
England O
. O

In O
October O
2011 O
, O
Spangler B-PERSON
was O
selected O
as O
one O
of O
100 O
initial O
partners O
for O
the O
YouTube O
Original O
Channel O
Initiative O
and O
received O
funding O
for O
the O
production O
of O
new O
original O
programming O
. O

Moscow B-LOCATION
is O
located O
at O
. O

In O
1986–87 O
, O
Kulak B-PERSON
would O
crack O
the O
Canucks O
' O
roster O
out O
of O
training O
camp O
, O
appearing O
in O
21 O
games O
before O
being O
waived O
and O
claimed O
by O
the O
Edmonton O
Oilers O
. O

Boyle B-PERSON
started O
starring O
in O
commercials O
for O
the O
company O
in O
1984 O
. O

Santiago B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Taylor O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
. O

In O
March O
2010 O
, O
Hill B-PERSON
released O
a O
single O
exclusively O
for O
his O
Bruneian O
fanbase O
entitled O
" O
Buat O
Selamanya O
" O
. O

Midway O
through O
his O
last O
season O
as O
Packers O
head O
coach O
in O
1974 O
, O
Devine B-PERSON
traded O
two O
1st O
round O
picks O
, O
two O
2nd O
round O
picks O
, O
and O
a O
3rd O
round O
pick O
for O
34-year O
- O
old O
quarterback O
John O
Hadl O
from O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Rams O
. O

Dover B-LOCATION
is O
home O
to O
Delaware O
State O
University O
, O
a O
land O
- O
grant O
university O
and O
Delaware O
's O
only O
historically O
black O
university O
, O
and O
Wesley O
College O
. O

Sunbeam O
built O
their O
own O
bodies O
but O
also O
supplied O
to O
the O
coachbuilder O
trade O
; O
many O
limousines O
were O
built O
on O
Sunbeam B-ORGANIZATION
chassis O
. O

Opperman B-PERSON
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Advisory O
Board O
of O
the O
High O
Pay O
Centre O
and O
has O
co O
- O
authored O
an O
essay O
with O
Green O
Party O
MP O
Caroline O
Lucas O
and O
TUC O
General O
Secretary O
Frances O
O'Grady O
entitled O
" O
Better O
Business O
: O
Moral O
Matters O
" O
. O

On O
16 O
May O
2012 O
, O
Malone B-PERSON
signed O
a O
pre O
contract O
agreement O
with O
Raith O
Rovers O
after O
impressing O
then O
manager O
John O
McGlynn O
. O

In O
the O
1980s O
Perkins B-PERSON
built O
her O
own O
glass O
studio O
in O
Pojoaque O
, O
New O
Mexico O
where O
she O
worked O
on O
learning O
Venetian O
glassblowing O
techniques O
. O

In O
the O
first O
Sheffield O
Shield O
match O
of O
the O
season O
, O
Waugh B-PERSON
scored O
172 O
from O
301 O
balls O
, O
his O
highest O
First O
- O
class O
score O
to O
date O
. O

Malone B-PERSON
was O
the O
nation O
's O
most O
recruited O
quarterback O
in O
1975 O
out O
of O
El O
Cajon O
Valley O
High O
School O
near O
San O
Diego O
, O
California O
. O

Lipson B-PERSON
has O
been O
involved O
with O
teams O
that O
have O
created O
a O
number O
of O
machines O
including O
: O

Barnard B-PERSON
is O
often O
referred O
to O
as O
Frank O
Barnard O
, O
as O
was O
his O
father O
Francis O
Jones O
Barnard O
, O
who O
as O
the O
founder O
of O
Barnard O
's O
Express O
, O
was O
one O
of O
BC O
's O
more O
notable O
pioneer O
entrepreneurs O
. O

When O
Yeo B-PERSON
joined O
the O
EDB O
in O
1986 O
, O
EDB O
had O
a O
few O
MNCs O
who O
had O
donated O
annual O
scholarships O
: O
Sundstrand O
- O
EDB O
Scholarship(1982 O
) O
; O
Minebea O
( O
1985 O
) O
. O

A O
week O
later O
Murphy O
's O
legal O
case O
against O
the O
BBC O
was O
resolved O
, O
with O
the O
BBC O
issuing O
a O
statement O
that O
Murphy B-PERSON
" O
was O
fully O
entitled O
to O
maintain O
his O
innocence O
of O
the O
charges O
against O
him O
and O
to O
test O
the O
evidence O
against O
him O
at O
his O
trial O
" O
. O

Murdoch B-PERSON
led O
Wimbledon O
to O
tenth O
in O
the O
First O
Division O
in O
the O
2002–03 O
season O
, O
despite O
a O
number O
of O
supporters O
boycotting O
Wimbledon O
's O
matches O
in O
protest O
against O
the O
proposed O
move O
. O

Curtis B-PERSON
estimates O
that O
Britain O
bears O
" O
significant O
responsibility O
" O
for O
the O
direct O
or O
indirect O
deaths O
of O
8.6 O
million O
to O
13.5 O
million O
people O
throughout O
the O
world O
since O
1945 O
. O

Speer B-PERSON
also O
competed O
in O
the O
WEC O
and O
Cage O
Warriors O
.. O

In O
1988 O
, O
Dome B-ORGANIZATION
would O
return O
to O
production O
car O
design O
, O
establishing O
a O
design O
studio O
called O
Jiotto O
Design O
to O
design O
cars O
with O
its O
own O
quarter O
- O
scale O
wind O
tunnel O
. O

Rasmussen B-PERSON
won O
the O
match O
in O
straight O
sets O
, O
15 O
- O
3 O
, O
15 O
- O
12 O
. O

In O
February O
2012 O
, O
Yamamoto B-PERSON
organized O
a O
relaunch O
of O
the O
Shimoda O
Conference O
, O
which O
had O
not O
been O
held O
in O
seventeen O
years O
. O

Diving O
from O
the O
Russian O
research O
vessel O
Keldysh O
, O
Kohler B-PERSON
made O
multiple O
dives O
to O
in O
the O
MIR O
submersibles O
to O
explore O
the O
" O
Titanic O
" O
's O
wreck O
site O
. O

The O
latter O
ambushed O
Mortimer B-PERSON
and O
only O
released O
him O
after O
the O
payment O
of O
a O
substantial O
ransom O
. O

Waugh B-PERSON
eventually O
finished O
the O
season O
with O
1460 O
runs O
and O
75 O
wickets O
, O
breaking O
the O
club O
runscoring O
record O
by O
more O
than O
200 O
runs O
. O

Wright B-PERSON
commanded O
the O
VI O
Corps O
again O
during O
Maj O
. O
Gen. O
Philip O
H. O
Sheridan O
's O
Shenandoah O
Valley O
campaign O
from O
August O
6 O
to O
October O
16 O
, O
1864 O
. O

In O
2006 O
, O
Fischer B-PERSON
received O
the O
Catholic O
Schools O
Distinguished O
Alumni O
Award O
from O
the O
Archdiocese O
of O
Louisville O
. O

In O
his O
role O
as O
Commissioner O
, O
Rennie B-PERSON
has O
been O
involved O
in O
a O
number O
of O
initiatives O
to O
improve O
the O
performance O
of O
the O
public O
service O
including O
projects O
called O
Better O
Public O
Services O
, O
the O
Performance O
Improvement O
Framework O
. O

Rennie B-PERSON
has O
several O
published O
articles O
in O
" O
Scientific O
American O
" O
, O
starting O
with O
the O
September O
1989 O
issue O
and O
as O
recently O
as O
the O
December O
2013 O
issue O
. O

In O
2015 O
Blanchard B-PERSON
continued O
with O
LDM O
but O
was O
promoted O
to O
a O
full O
- O
time O
drive O
in O
the O
team O
's O
No O
. O
3 O
Commodore O
. O

Athens B-LOCATION
has O
hosted O
the O
Summer O
Olympic O
Games O
twice O
, O
in O
1896 O
and O
2004 O
. O

Cooke B-PERSON
had O
entered O
the O
U.S. O
broadcasting O
industry O
in O
August O
1959 O
by O
acquiring O
Pasadena O
, O
California O
radio O
station O
KRLA O
1110 O
( O
now O
KRDC O
) O
through O
his O
brother O
, O
Donald O
Cooke O
, O
a O
U.S. O
citizen O
. O

Gladstone B-LOCATION
is O
a O
Canadian O
parish O
in O
Sunbury O
County O
, O
New O
Brunswick O
. O

In O
1898 O
the O
Missionary O
Oblates O
of O
Mary O
Immaculate O
commissioned O
Cavanagh B-PERSON
to O
design O
a O
new O
church O
on O
the O
site O
of O
a O
former O
Benedictine O
church O
in O
Fremantle O
. O

Hague B-PERSON
also O
became O
known O
for O
his O
coverage O
of O
the O
Meadowlands O
Grand O
Prix O
, O
the O
Indy O
car O
race O
held O
in O
the O
parking O
lot O
of O
the O
Meadowlands O
Sports O
Complex O
, O
and O
was O
recognized O
nationally O
for O
his O
coverage O
. O

The O
leading O
position O
of O
Athens B-LOCATION
may O
well O
have O
resulted O
from O
its O
central O
location O
in O
the O
Greek O
world O
, O
its O
secure O
stronghold O
on O
the O
Acropolis O
and O
its O
access O
to O
the O
sea O
, O
which O
gave O
it O
a O
natural O
advantage O
over O
inland O
rivals O
such O
as O
Thebes O
and O
Sparta O
. O

After O
the O
trial O
, O
Adams O
was O
whisked O
away O
to O
a O
safe O
house O
by O
Hoskins B-PERSON
and O
interviewed O
for O
two O
weeks O
. O

Tennyson B-PERSON
is O
most O
famous O
for O
his O
1939 O
book O
" O
Suffolk O
Scene O
" O
, O
which O
documents O
the O
author O
’s O
travels O
and O
experiences O
in O
Suffolk O
during O
the O
1930s O
. O

Like O
Oxford O
and O
Cambridge O
, O
Salamanca B-LOCATION
had O
a O
number O
of O
colleges O
( O
" O
Colegios O
Mayores O
" O
) O
. O

As O
of O
2014 O
, O
Fischer B-PERSON
was O
suffering O
from O
" O
dementia O
, O
cognitive O
decline O
, O
and O
severe O
memory O
loss O
" O
and O
was O
residing O
in O
an O
assisted O
- O
living O
facility O
. O

Townley B-PERSON
also O
missed O
another O
race O
when O
he O
skipped O
the O
Texas O
Motor O
Speedway O
truck O
race O
to O
treat O
an O
injured O
left O
ankle O
, O
with O
Cody O
Coughlin O
taking O
over O
the O
No O
. O
05 O
for O
the O
event O
. O

Malone B-PERSON
hosts O
a O
weekly O
radio O
show O
, O
" O
Back O
to O
the O
Country O
" O
, O
on O
WORT O
– O
FM O
community O
radio O
in O
Madison O
, O
and O
performs O
country O
music O
with O
his O
wife O
, O
Bobbie O
Malone O
, O
playing O
mandolin O
and O
guitar O
. O

Manson B-PERSON
stood O
at O
194 O
cm O
and O
was O
solidly O
built O
( O
108 O
kg O
) O
with O
a O
great O
overhead O
mark O
. O

Humphrey B-PERSON
is O
a O
member O
of O
Phi O
Beta O
Sigma O
. O

Bethlehem B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Bethlehem O
Township O
, O
Clark O
County O
, O
Indiana O
, O
United O
States O
, O
twenty O
- O
five O
miles O
up O
the O
Ohio O
River O
from O
Louisville O
, O
Kentucky O
. O

News B-ORGANIZATION
has O
over O
500 O
employees O
and O
approximately O
60 O
% O
of O
the O
magazine O
advertising O
market O
in O
Austria O
. O

Molloy B-PERSON
denied O
the O
allegations O
at O
the O
time O
, O
and O
challenged O
anyone O
to O
repeat O
them O
outside O
Parliament O
so O
he O
could O
take O
legal O
action O
( O
the O
original O
speech O
being O
subject O
to O
parliamentary O
privilege O
and O
thus O
not O
actionable O
) O
. O

Petrie O
linked O
up O
well O
with O
Sid O
Binks O
at O
centre O
- O
forward O
and O
Sammy O
Taylor O
at O
inside O
- O
right O
, O
scoring O
44 O
goals O
between O
them O
, O
of O
which O
Petrie B-PERSON
contributed O
16 O
. O

The O
British O
shaped O
the O
country O
until O
the O
20th O
century O
, O
and O
Kochi B-LOCATION
has O
always O
been O
an O
important O
harbour O
and O
trade O
center O
. O

Nolan B-PERSON
subsequently O
sued O
Comcast O
for O
wrongful O
termination O
, O
and O
lost O
. O

Despite O
the O
incident O
, O
McKenzie O
kept O
Beale B-PERSON
in O
the O
squad O
in O
Argentina O
, O
but O
did O
not O
name O
him O
in O
the O
match O
- O
day O
23 O
for O
the O
match O
against O
Argentina O
. O

Berlin B-LOCATION
further O
had O
volcanic O
activity O
in O
the O
Holocene O
, O
including O
a O
lava O
flow O
beneath O
an O
ice O
tower O
that O
is O
dated O
10,300 O
± O
2,700 O
years O
ago O
. O

Melbourne B-LOCATION
was O
founded O
in O
1835 O
, O
during O
the O
reign O
of O
King O
William O
IV O
, O
with O
the O
arrival O
of O
the O
schooner O
" O
Enterprize O
" O
near O
the O
present O
site O
of O
the O
Queen O
's O
Wharf O
, O
as O
a O
barely O
legal O
, O
speculative O
settlement O
that O
broke O
away O
from O
New O
South O
Wales O
. O

At O
the O
end O
of O
2011 O
, O
Smiley B-PERSON
collaborated O
on O
a O
track O
with O
former O
Aftermath O
- O
artist O
Bishop O
Lamont O
, O
called O
" O
Golddiggy O
" O
. O

Blanchard B-PERSON
saw O
Wheaton O
College O
" O
as O
an O
' O
arsenal O
' O
and O
' O
drill O
camp O
' O
for O
the O
hosts O
of O
righteousness O
in O
the O
moral O
warfare O
of O
the O
world O
. O
. O
. O
a O
means O
of O
training O
social O
activists O
. O
. O
. O
. O
" O

It O
later O
emerged O
that O
Wilkes O
reportedly O
gave O
Cunningham B-PERSON
more O
than O
$ O
630,000 O
in O
cash O
and O
favors O
. O

The O
likeness O
between O
the O
pictures O
of O
Martha B-PERSON
presented O
by O
Luke O
and O
John O
is O
very O
remarkable O
. O

Shortly O
after O
this O
visit O
, O
Prince O
Chutamani O
requested O
the O
medical O
services O
of O
Bradley B-PERSON
to O
care O
for O
the O
ailing O
Prince O
Mongkut O
. O

On O
31 O
August O
2017 O
, O
Oldham O
Athletic O
signed O
Doyle B-PERSON
on O
loan O
until O
1 O
January O
2018 O
. O

In O
the O
1990s O
, O
Emami B-ORGANIZATION
launches O
another O
flagship O
brand O
under O
the O
Himani O
Umbrella O
, O
Navratna O
Cool O
Oil O
, O
and O
expanded O
production O
by O
opening O
its O
second O
factory O
, O
at O
Pondicherry O
. O

Several O
communities O
nearby O
the O
town O
are O
often O
included O
colloquially O
in O
Llanelli B-LOCATION
. O

Between O
1986–98 O
, O
Rudy B-PERSON
received O
16 O
caps O
for O
the O
Poland O
national O
football O
team O
( O
three O
goals O
) O
. O

In O
2013 O
, O
Juniper B-PERSON
was O
awarded O
Honorary O
Doctor O
of O
Science O
Degrees O
from O
the O
universities O
of O
Bristol O
and O
Plymouth O
. O

Initially O
, O
Hank B-PERSON
was O
slated O
to O
host O
a O
quiz O
show O
based O
on O
his O
abandoned O
YouTube O
channel O
" O
Truth O
or O
Fail O
" O
, O
in O
which O
viewers O
would O
answer O
several O
questions O
via O
link O
annotations O
, O
jumping O
from O
video O
to O
video O
to O
find O
out O
answers O
and O
get O
more O
questions O
. O

One O
source O
lists O
Curtis B-PERSON
as O
the O
51st O
richest O
person O
ever O
, O
with O
a O
fortune O
of O
$ O
43.2 O
billion O
adjusted O
for O
inflation O
( O
to O
2008 O
dollars O
) O
, O
which O
according O
to O
this O
source O
made O
him O
richer O
than O
J. O
P. O
Morgan O
. O

Quinn B-PERSON
has O
since O
published O
several O
critical O
studies O
of O
Mormon O
hierarchy O
, O
including O
his O
three O
- O
volume O
work O
of O
" O
The O
Mormon O
Hierarchy O
: O
Origins O
of O
Power O
" O
, O
" O
The O
Mormon O
Hierarchy O
: O
Extensions O
of O
Power O
" O
, O
and O
" O
The O
Mormon O
Hierarchy O
: O
Wealth O
and O
Corporate O
Power O
" O
. O

After O
learning O
that O
Howard O
County O
had O
increased O
the O
appraised O
value O
of O
land O
donated O
in O
the O
competition O
, O
Rollins B-PERSON
sold O
of O
his O
own O
land O
to O
Boone O
County O
for O
$ O
25 O
an O
acre O
. O

Whitehall B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Dorchester O
County O
, O
Maryland O
, O
United O
States O
. O

In O
2000 O
, O
Clarke B-PERSON
founded O
Bruce O
Clarke O
Consultants O
, O
Inc. O
to O
work O
with O
defense O
contractors O
on O
technology O
integration O
issues O
. O

The O
2014 O
season O
started O
off O
in O
great O
style O
as O
Parramatta B-ORGANIZATION
won O
4 O
out O
of O
their O
first O
6 O
matches O
. O

Siedlce B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
administrative O
district O
of O
Gmina O
Chęciny O
, O
within O
Kielce O
County O
, O
Świętokrzyskie O
Voivodeship O
, O
in O
south O
- O
central O
Poland O
. O

While O
dean O
of O
the O
Schreyer O
Honors O
College O
, O
Brady B-PERSON
had O
a O
dynamic O
blog O
and O
podcast O
. O

However O
, O
the O
southern O
section O
from O
Napton O
to O
Oxford B-LOCATION
became O
something O
of O
a O
backwater O
, O
and O
carried O
mostly O
local O
traffic O
. O

By O
1929 O
, O
the O
Essex B-ORGANIZATION
was O
third O
in O
U.S. O
sales O
, O
behind O
Ford O
and O
Chevrolet O
. O

Becker B-PERSON
moved O
the O
resolution O
that O
women O
should O
be O
granted O
voting O
rights O
on O
the O
same O
terms O
as O
men O
. O

Toronto B-LOCATION
was O
an O
unincorporated O
rural O
community O
located O
in O
Woodside O
Township O
, O
Sangamon O
County O
, O
Illinois O
. O

In O
2007 O
Underwood B-PERSON
created O
a O
Mormon O
studies O
unit O
for O
the O
American O
Academy O
of O
Religion O
and O
served O
as O
co O
- O
chair O
. O

Hexham B-LOCATION
is O
a O
suburb O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Newcastle O
, O
about O
inland O
from O
the O
Newcastle O
CBD O
in O
New O
South O
Wales O
, O
Australia O
on O
the O
bank O
of O
the O
Hunter O
River O
. O

London O
's O
Maryland B-LOCATION
is O
therefore O
an O
unusual O
example O
of O
a O
place O
in O
Britain O
named O
after O
an O
American O
location O
, O
rather O
than O
vice O
versa O
. O

Surrey B-ORGANIZATION
play O
some O
matches O
at O
Woodbridge O
Road O
, O
Guildford O
, O
which O
holds O
4,500 O
spectators O
. O

Boyle O
underwent O
initial O
wrist O
surgery O
on O
September O
23 O
; O
he O
attempted O
to O
return O
on O
October O
29 O
, O
but O
after O
playing O
his O
first O
four O
games O
of O
the O
2007–08 O
season O
, O
Boyle B-PERSON
underwent O
additional O
surgery O
on O
the O
injured O
wrist O
, O
missing O
another O
36 O
games O
. O

Zenith B-ORGANIZATION
were O
always O
keen O
to O
promote O
themselves O
via O
competition O
. O

The O
official O
languages O
of O
Yanam B-LOCATION
are O
Telugu O
and O
French O
. O

After O
the O
merger O
, O
Penton B-ORGANIZATION
became O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
B2B O
media O
companies O
in O
the O
world O
. O

Pickett B-PERSON
was O
admitted O
to O
the O
bar O
in O
1890 O
and O
commenced O
practice O
in O
Waterloo O
, O
Iowa O
. O

As O
well O
as O
tending O
to O
spiritual O
matters O
, O
Flynn B-PERSON
quickly O
established O
the O
need O
for O
medical O
care O
for O
residents O
of O
the O
vast O
Australian O
outback O
, O
and O
established O
a O
number O
of O
bush O
hospitals O
. O

In O
this O
match O
, O
Parramatta B-ORGANIZATION
lost O
22–0 O
. O

Riley O
and O
Plaisted O
's O
racing O
sculls O
almost O
collided O
; O
this O
allowed O
Courtney B-PERSON
to O
take O
very O
small O
lead O
just O
before O
the O
turning O
stake O
. O

Jennings B-PERSON
won O
the O
championship O
to O
be O
crowned O
with O
the O
" O
Greatest O
of O
All O
Time O
" O
title O
. O

In O
2006 O
, O
Rollins B-PERSON
consulted O
on O
the O
campaign O
of O
Republican O
New O
York O
State O
Senate O
contender O
Kathleen O
Troia O
" O
KT O
" O
McFarland O
. O

Spode B-PERSON
was O
a O
pauper O
's O
son O
and O
also O
a O
pauper O
's O
orphan O
at O
the O
age O
of O
six O
. O

Dublin B-LOCATION
is O
a O
former O
community O
in O
Barton O
County O
, O
Missouri O
, O
United O
States O
, O
located O
on O
the O
Jasper O
County O
line O
, O
approximately O
one O
mile O
north O
of O
the O
current O
town O
of O
Jasper O
. O

Blake B-PERSON
was O
named O
after O
Nzinga O
of O
Ndongo O
and O
Matamba O
, O
a O
17th O
- O
century O
Queen O
and O
folk O
heroine O
of O
the O
Mbundu O
people O
of O
southwestern O
Africa O
. O

As O
of O
January O
2019 O
, O
Bergman B-PERSON
retired O
after O
28 O
years O
of O
teaching O
, O
capping O
a O
50-year O
career O
in O
journalism O
. O

Jennings B-PERSON
moved O
to O
the O
new O
state O
capital O
at O
Corydon O
, O
where O
he O
served O
the O
duration O
of O
his O
term O
as O
governor O
. O

In O
the O
1997 O
- O
1998 O
season O
, O
Bradley B-PERSON
won O
the O
silver O
medal O
on O
the O
novice O
level O
at O
Nationals O
. O

To O
close O
the O
gap O
, O
and O
to O
pay O
for O
the O
new O
programs O
he O
wanted O
to O
implement O
, O
Cavanagh B-PERSON
had O
pushed O
through O
the O
legislature O
income O
and O
commuter O
taxes O
for O
Detroit O
, O
but O
these O
proved O
unpopular O
with O
residents O
and O
businesses O
. O

In O
a O
game O
against O
Duke O
in O
2005 O
, O
Hester B-PERSON
broke O
six O
tackles O
while O
returning O
an O
81-yard O
punt O
. O

They O
currently O
use O
the O
one O
- O
word O
name O
Surrey B-ORGANIZATION
. O

In O
December O
1987 O
, O
desperate O
for O
cash O
, O
Bradford B-ORGANIZATION
transfer O
- O
listed O
22 O
players O
for O
a O
total O
of O
£ O
210,000 O
plus O
Phil O
Ford O
for O
£ O
120,000 O
. O

Roy B-PERSON
has O
played O
in O
the O
National O
Hockey O
League O
( O
NHL O
) O
with O
the O
Buffalo O
Sabres O
, O
Dallas O
Stars O
, O
Vancouver O
Canucks O
, O
St. O
Louis O
Blues O
, O
Nashville O
Predators O
and O
the O
Edmonton O
Oilers O
. O

One O
thing O
that O
also O
characterized O
the O
building O
in O
Grumbach B-LOCATION
may O
have O
been O
the O
French O
Revolution O
and O
its O
consequences O
, O
which O
destroyed O
feudalism O
, O
as O
symbolized O
by O
the O
" O
Schloss O
" O
. O

Turimex O
Internacional O
operates O
bus O
service O
from O
Austin B-LOCATION
to O
Nuevo O
Laredo O
and O
on O
to O
many O
destinations O
in O
Mexico O
. O

Darnall B-PERSON
was O
required O
to O
answer O
to O
the O
Privy O
Council O
on O
the O
accusation O
of O
treason O
, O
which O
he O
denied O
: O

Athens B-LOCATION
has O
its O
own O
high O
school O
Athens O
District O
High O
School O
, O
which O
is O
under O
the O
Upper O
Canada O
District O
School O
Board O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
live O
entertainment O
venue O
Joshua O
Bates O
Centre O
which O
features O
a O
series O
of O
live O
musical O
performances O
each O
year O
. O

In O
2009 O
, O
Maxie B-PERSON
joined O
NASCAR O
as O
Manager O
of O
Communications O
for O
East O
Regional O
Media O
Outreach O
. O

In O
the O
same O
month O
Quinn B-PERSON
increased O
his O
share O
holding O
in O
the O
Anglo O
Irish O
Bank O
to O
approximately O
5 O
% O
, O
for O
an O
equivalent O
value O
of O
€ O
570 O
million O
- O
financed O
through O
the O
group O
's O
equity O
and O
through O
a O
deal O
with O
the O
Swiss O
- O
based O
giant O
Credit O
Suisse O
. O

Berlin B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Bourbon O
County O
, O
Kansas O
, O
United O
States O
. O

That O
season O
, O
Tennyson B-PERSON
led O
the O
Timbers O
in O
scoring O
with O
18 O
goals O
and O
6 O
assists O
in O
24 O
games O
, O
which O
was O
good O
enough O
to O
lead O
the O
USL O
First O
Division O
in O
points O
and O
tied O
him O
with O
Fadi O
Afash O
and O
Eduardo O
Sebrango O
as O
joint O
goals O
leader O
. O

Killarney B-LOCATION
is O
a O
suburb O
of O
Bulawayo O
, O
Zimbabwe O
. O

Just O
7 O
miles O
east O
of O
the O
Bernardo B-LOCATION
interchange O
is O
Micah O
Village O
an O
Intentional O
Community O
. O

During O
the O
1920s O
a O
number O
of O
Greek O
refugees O
, O
expelled O
from O
Asia O
Minor O
after O
the O
Greco O
- O
Turkish O
War O
, O
swelled O
Athens O
's O
population O
; O
nevertheless O
it O
was O
most O
particularly O
following O
World O
War O
II O
, O
and O
from O
the O
1950s O
and O
1960s O
, O
that O
the O
population O
of O
the O
city O
exploded O
, O
and O
Athens B-LOCATION
experienced O
a O
gradual O
expansion O
. O

On O
September O
3 O
, O
2015 O
, O
Flynn B-PERSON
started O
the O
Jets O
' O
preseason O
week O
4 O
match O
- O
up O
against O
the O
Philadelphia O
Eagles O
, O
throwing O
10–14 O
for O
136 O
yards O
, O
2 O
touchdowns O
, O
and O
1 O
interception O
. O

Calico B-ORGANIZATION
implemented O
a O
CNC O
machining O
process O
and O
upgraded O
materials O
used O
in O
manufacture O
. O

Gerry O
was O
born O
on O
December O
6 O
, O
1813 O
in O
Waterford O
, O
Maine O
; O
he O
was O
the O
son O
of O
Peter O
and O
Mary O
" O
Polly O
" O
( O
Cutler O
) O
Gerry B-PERSON
. O

In O
1872 O
, O
Reid B-PERSON
was O
part O
of O
the O
Liberal O
Republican O
movement O
that O
opposed O
a O
second O
term O
for O
President O
Grant O
and O
that O
ultimately O
supported O
the O
ill O
- O
fated O
Greeley O
for O
the O
presidency O
. O

In O
1987 O
, O
NBC O
's O
then O
- O
parent O
company O
General O
Electric O
purchased O
CBS O
affiliate O
WTVJ O
, O
the O
area O
's O
number O
one O
news O
station O
at O
the O
time O
, O
from O
investment O
firm O
Kohlberg O
Kravis O
Roberts O
& O
Co. O
Sunbeam B-ORGANIZATION
immediately O
sought O
to O
block O
the O
purchase O
and O
spent O
over O
a O
year O
fighting O
NBC O
in O
court O
. O

In O
a O
hasty O
baptism O
, O
Sigvatr O
named O
Magnus B-PERSON
after O
the O
greatest O
king O
he O
knew O
of O
, O
also O
Olaf O
's O
greatest O
role O
model O
, O
" O
Karla O
Magnus O
" O
, O
or O
Charlemagne O
. O

In O
1970 O
, O
Galloway B-PERSON
became O
the O
first O
winner O
of O
the O
Peachtree O
Road O
Race O
in O
Atlanta O
, O
Georgia O
. O

Backus B-PERSON
was O
admitted O
to O
the O
bar O
in O
1833 O
and O
practiced O
for O
a O
short O
time O
in O
Norwich O
before O
moving O
to O
Michigan O
. O

Austin B-LOCATION
is O
home O
to O
the O
Circuit O
of O
the O
Americas O
( O
COTA O
) O
, O
a O
grade O
1 O
FIA O
specification O
motor O
racing O
facility O
which O
hosts O
the O
Formula O
One O
United O
States O
Grand O
Prix O
. O

Athens B-LOCATION
is O
built O
around O
a O
number O
of O
hills O
. O

The O
Fighting O
Irish O
, O
who O
never O
trailed O
in O
a O
single O
game O
that O
year O
, O
saw O
41 O
of O
its O
players O
go O
on O
to O
play O
professional O
football O
, O
including O
Leonard B-PERSON
. O

Although O
Hoskins B-PERSON
did O
not O
publicize O
herself O
or O
her O
work O
, O
she O
corresponded O
with O
many O
prominent O
contemporaries O
( O
including O
Robert O
Lowell O
, O
John O
Crowe O
Ransom O
, O
and O
Wallace O
Stevens O
) O
, O
all O
of O
whom O
regarded O
her O
work O
highly O
. O

Blake B-PERSON
was O
relegated O
from O
the O
Premier O
League O
five O
times O
, O
a O
record O
he O
holds O
jointly O
with O
Hermann O
Hreiðarsson O
. O

Lester B-PERSON
posted O
an O
11–13 O
record O
, O
logging O
205 O
innings O
pitched O
with O
an O
ERA O
of O
3.34 O
in O
his O
first O
year O
with O
the O
Chicago O
Cubs O
. O

Hayes O
McMullan O
's O
musical O
talents O
were O
unearthed O
following O
a O
chance O
encounter O
in O
1967 O
between O
Wardlow B-PERSON
and O
McMullan O
. O

Toronto B-LOCATION
is O
well O
served O
by O
road O
links O
to O
Newcastle O
and O
Sydney O
and O
is O
approximately O
8 O
minutes O
from O
the O
Sydney O
- O
Newcastle O
Freeway O
( O
M1 O
) O
. O

In O
Saskatoon O
's O
non O
- O
partisan O
municipal O
politics O
, O
Westmount B-LOCATION
lies O
within O
ward O
2 O
. O

Malone B-PERSON
scored O
two O
more O
goals O
, O
as O
the O
season O
progressed O
, O
against O
Stevenage O
and O
Huddersfield O
Town O
. O

In O
1871 O
the O
NBR O
completed O
the O
link O
to O
Gardrum O
Moss O
and O
the O
private O
line O
of O
the O
Duke O
of O
Hamilton O
, O
thereby O
giving O
California B-LOCATION
a O
freight O
link O
to O
Edinburgh O
and O
Glasgow O
by O
way O
of O
the O
Slamannan O
Junction O
Railway O
at O
Manuel O
. O

Bristol B-ORGANIZATION
first O
offered O
a O
diesel O
- O
engined O
chassis O
in O
1933 O
. O

Texas B-LOCATION
has O
a O
state O
school O
called O
Texas O
State O
School O
, O
which O
caters O
to O
students O
from O
Prep O
Year O
to O
Year O
10 O
. O

Dempsey B-PERSON
took O
over O
' O
B O
' O
Company O
, O
and O
spent O
a O
large O
amount O
of O
his O
time O
travelling O
, O
mainly O
by O
bicycle O
, O
around O
Europe O
, O
visiting O
old O
battlefields O
of O
old O
wars O
, O
as O
well O
as O
likely O
scenes O
of O
battle O
in O
any O
future O
conflicts O
. O

On O
5 O
June O
1942 O
, O
Becker B-PERSON
reported O
that O
" O
for O
an O
example O
, O
since O
December O
1941 O
, O
three O
vehicles O
were O
used O
to O
process O
97,000 O
, O
with O
no O
down O
- O
time O
on O
the O
vehicles O
. O
" O
. O

McNair B-PERSON
was O
played O
in O
the O
play O
and O
movie O
" O
1776 O
" O
by O
William O
Duell O
. O

In O
addition O
, O
Yeo B-PERSON
also O
pointed O
out O
that O
during O
the O
5 O
years O
of O
investment O
, O
more O
than O
25 O
companies O
started O
research O
centres O
in O
Singapore O
, O
including O
three O
corporate O
R&D O
laboratories O
run O
by O
Eli O
Lilly O
and O
Company O
, O
GlaxoSmithKline O
and O
Novartis O
. O

Cunningham B-PERSON
currently O
works O
for O
a O
pharmaceutical O
company O
. O

Elmer B-PERSON
reported O
the O
letter O
was O
never O
sent O
. O

As O
of O
April O
2017 O
, O
Schumacher B-PERSON
is O
competing O
in O
the O
NHRA O
Top O
Fuel O
class O
, O
of O
which O
he O
is O
an O
eight O
- O
time O
champion O
( O
breaking O
a O
record O
set O
by O
Joe O
Amato O
) O
, O
winning O
six O
years O
consecutively O
( O
2004–2009 O
) O
. O

After O
a O
disappointing O
season O
in O
1893 O
when O
their O
batting O
failed O
on O
Oval O
pitches O
rendered O
fiery O
by O
several O
dry O
winters O
and O
springs O
, O
Kingsmill O
Key O
took O
over O
and O
led O
Surrey B-ORGANIZATION
to O
further O
titles O
in O
1894 O
, O
1895 O
and O
1899 O
. O

Paris B-LOCATION
is O
also O
the O
northernmost O
community O
to O
participate O
in O
Southern O
Ontario O
's O
Green O
Energy O
Hub O
. O

On O
1 O
June O
2007 O
, O
it O
was O
confirmed O
that O
Clinton B-PERSON
had O
signed O
to O
the O
Brisbane O
Broncos O
for O
the O
2008 O
NRL O
season O
. O

In O
October O
2001 O
, O
Myra B-PERSON
made O
an O
appearance O
in O
the O
film O
" O
Max O
Keeble O
's O
Big O
Move O
" O
as O
Chelsea O
. O

At O
one O
point O
Ulysses O
S. O
Grant O
called O
Washburn B-PERSON
" O
one O
of O
the O
best O
administrative O
officers O
we O
have O
. O
" O

Boyle B-PERSON
scored O
164 O
goals O
and O
605 O
points O
over O
1,093 O
NHL O
games O
with O
four O
teams O
. O

Critics O
of O
Murphy B-PERSON
claim O
that O
the O
laws O
he O
passed O
helped O
to O
enable O
unsustainable O
growth O
in O
the O
hog O
industry O
, O
which O
later O
caused O
massive O
water O
pollution O
resulting O
in O
fish O
kills O
throughout O
eastern O
North O
Carolina O
. O

By O
the O
time O
he O
got O
to O
KCBQ O
in O
San O
Diego O
, O
early O
in O
1950 O
, O
Blanchard B-PERSON
had O
developed O
a O
formula O
of O
" O
... O
puns O
, O
parodies O
and O
gross O
- O
out O
gags O
, O
much O
of O
it O
delivered O
in O
a O
jive O
patois O
he O
called O
Zorch O
, O
with O
the O
occasional O
novelty O
record O
thrown O
in O
, O
[ O
he O
] O
became O
a O
huge O
hit O
... O
" O

As O
a O
result O
of O
the O
prior O
re O
- O
structuring O
, O
Aurora B-ORGANIZATION
delivered O
a O
bonus O
to O
customers O
with O
an O
average O
5 O
% O
drop O
in O
electricity O
prices O
. O

Thornthwaite B-PERSON
also O
assisted O
in O
having O
a O
North O
Shore O
peak O
named O
after O
longtime O
North O
Shore O
Rescue O
Team O
Leader O
, O
Tim O
Jones O
( O
Search O
and O
Rescue O
) O
. O

Analyzing O
seminal O
works O
by O
modern O
and O
postmodern O
philosophers O
such O
as O
Rousseau O
, O
Kant O
, O
Marx O
, O
Sartre O
, O
Arendt O
, O
Foucault O
, O
and O
Derrida O
, O
Ophir B-PERSON
submits O
that O
to O
be O
moral O
is O
to O
care O
for O
others O
, O
and O
to O
be O
committed O
to O
preventing O
their O
suffering O
and O
distress O
. O

Murphy B-PERSON
is O
now O
a O
GOP O
strategist O
, O
serving O
in O
2010 O
as O
advisor O
to O
Senate O
candidate O
Dr. O
Eric O
Wargotz O
of O
Maryland O
, O
according O
to O
Fox O
News O
. O

For O
the O
start O
of O
pre O
- O
season O
training O
for O
the O
2010 O
season O
Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
will O
have O
a O
centralised O
training O
facility O
based O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Chester O
's O
Padgate O
campus O
. O

After O
the O
Sabres O
were O
eliminated O
by O
the O
Senators O
, O
Roy B-PERSON
agreed O
to O
a O
six O
- O
year O
, O
$ O
24 O
million O
contract O
extension O
with O
the O
Sabres O
on O
July O
27 O
, O
2007 O
. O

There O
are O
several O
student O
- O
run O
publications O
at O
Commonwealth B-ORGANIZATION
. O

Following O
the O
set O
back O
of O
injuries O
experienced O
in O
2007 O
, O
Ellis B-PERSON
focused O
on O
qualifying O
for O
the O
2008 O
Summer O
Olympics O
in O
triathlon O
, O
but O
she O
fell O
short O
and O
failed O
to O
qualify O
. O

In O
2001 O
, O
his O
junior O
year O
, O
Burke B-PERSON
moved O
to O
shortstop O
and O
helped O
the O
Volunteers O
make O
an O
appearance O
in O
the O
College O
World O
Series O
by O
hitting O
.435 O
with O
20 O
home O
runs O
and O
49 O
stolen O
bases O
, O
being O
named O
to O
the O
CWS O
all O
- O
tournament O
team O
. O

As O
a O
backup O
to O
James O
in O
the O
season O
opener O
, O
Perkins B-PERSON
ran O
for O
80 O
yards O
against O
Virginia O
. O

Unlike O
other O
Mycenaean O
centers O
, O
such O
as O
Mycenae O
and O
Pylos O
, O
it O
is O
not O
known O
whether O
Athens B-LOCATION
suffered O
destruction O
in O
about O
1200 O
BC O
, O
an O
event O
often O
attributed O
to O
a O
Dorian O
invasion O
, O
and O
the O
Athenians O
always O
maintained O
that O
they O
were O
pure O
Ionians O
with O
no O
Dorian O
element O
. O

Drumheller B-LOCATION
is O
a O
town O
within O
the O
Red O
Deer O
River O
valley O
in O
the O
badlands O
of O
east O
- O
central O
Alberta O
, O
Canada O
. O

In O
mid O
- O
September O
2019 O
, O
Purdue B-ORGANIZATION
filed O
for O
bankruptcy O
in O
White O
Plains O
, O
New O
York O
, O
a O
few O
days O
after O
reaching O
a O
tentative O
settlement O
with O
state O
and O
local O
governments O
that O
were O
suing O
the O
company O
over O
the O
cost O
of O
the O
opioid O
epidemic O
. O

On O
October O
23 O
, O
2018 O
the O
Diamondbacks O
signed O
Escobar B-PERSON
to O
a O
three O
- O
year O
contract O
worth O
a O
reported O
$ O
21 O
million O
. O

During O
his O
time O
with O
the O
bankruptcy O
court O
, O
Leonard B-PERSON
was O
also O
active O
in O
the O
National O
Conference O
of O
Bankruptcy O
Judges O
. O

In O
the O
1988 O
Canadian O
federal O
election O
, O
both O
Harper O
and O
Manning O
were O
Reform O
Party O
candidates O
– O
Manning B-PERSON
running O
in O
the O
federal O
riding O
of O
Yellowhead O
against O
former O
Prime O
Minister O
Joe O
Clark O
. O

Wellington B-LOCATION
has O
a O
humid O
subtropical O
climate O
( O
" O
Cfa O
" O
) O
with O
hot O
summers O
and O
cool O
winters O
, O
and O
uniform O
rainfall O
throughout O
the O
year O
. O

Cory B-PERSON
is O
the O
namesake O
of O
Mount O
Cory O
, O
in O
Alberta O
. O

Ellis B-PERSON
started O
out O
for O
Otago O
in O
the O
NPC O
in O
1991 O
when O
he O
was O
playing O
for O
the O
club O
side O
University O
, O
and O
he O
was O
selected O
for O
the O
NZ O
Colts O
. O

In O
1998 O
, O
Parramatta B-ORGANIZATION
and O
Canterbury O
played O
against O
each O
other O
in O
the O
preliminary O
final O
with O
the O
winners O
to O
play O
the O
Brisbane O
Broncos O
in O
the O
grand O
final O
. O

In O
response O
, O
Boyle B-PERSON
published O
a O
letter O
in O
which O
he O
criticised O
the O
Trust O
's O
" O
cowardly O
rebuke O
of O
my O
jokes O
about O
Palestine O
" O
and O
reprinted O
the O
jokes O
in O
question O
. O

As O
a O
canon O
at O
the O
Segeberg O
Abbey O
in O
Holstein O
, O
Meinhard B-PERSON
was O
possibly O
inspired O
by O
Vicelinus O
missionary O
work O
among O
the O
Slavs O
. O

According O
to O
the O
arrest O
report O
, O
Malone B-PERSON
had O
1.3 O
grams O
of O
cocaine O
in O
a O
pocket O
. O

During O
the O
Super O
League O
XXIV O
season O
, O
Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
reached O
the O
Challenge O
Cup O
final O
against O
St O
Helens O
and O
won O
the O
match O
18 O
- O
4 O
at O
Wembley O
Stadium O
. O

In O
1961 O
, O
Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
reached O
the O
RL O
Championship O
final O
held O
at O
Odsal O
, O
but O
Leeds O
had O
total O
control O
over O
the O
match O
and O
ran O
out O
25–10 O
. O

The O
Chicago O
Bears O
selected O
Dempsey B-PERSON
in O
the O
thirteenth O
round O
( O
166th O
pick O
overall O
) O
of O
the O
1950 O
NFL O
Draft O
, O
and O
he O
played O
in O
thirty O
- O
nine O
games O
for O
the O
Bears O
from O
to O
. O

Fischer B-PERSON
would O
bounce O
back O
however O
, O
winning O
his O
next O
10 O
fights O
to O
amass O
a O
21–1–1 O
record O
. O

In O
time O
, O
however O
, O
one O
old O
Indian O
chief O
started O
to O
become O
suspicious O
, O
which O
Brady B-PERSON
and O
Wetzel O
noticed O
. O

Bethany B-LOCATION
is O
a O
neighborhood O
of O
Louisville O
, O
Kentucky O
located O
on O
Dixie O
Highway O
( O
US O
31W O
) O
by O
Bethany O
Cemetery O
. O

When O
casting O
his O
bid O
for O
the O
bridge O
, O
McCulloch B-PERSON
doubled O
the O
estimated O
cost O
of O
dismantling O
the O
structure O
, O
which O
was O
US$ O
1.2 O
million O
, O
bringing O
the O
price O
to O
US$ O
2.4 O
million O
. O

Quinn B-PERSON
caused O
anger O
and O
controversy O
when O
he O
refused O
to O
give O
up O
his O
ministers O
pension O
worth O
€ O
41,656 O
while O
sitting O
as O
a O
TD O
in O
2009 O
. O

Ellis B-PERSON
also O
placed O
4th O
in O
the O
Omnium O
. O

Although O
Hoffman B-PERSON
lost O
the O
debate O
, O
the O
sell O
- O
out O
event O
brought O
together O
many O
people O
with O
an O
interest O
in O
Christopher O
Marlowe O
, O
as O
a O
result O
of O
which O
the O
UK O
's O
Marlowe O
Society O
— O
although O
concerned O
more O
with O
Marlowe O
as O
a O
poet O
/ O
dramatist O
in O
his O
own O
right O
than O
with O
the O
authorship O
theory O
— O
came O
into O
existence O
just O
a O
week O
or O
two O
later O
. O

His O
total O
was O
surpassed O
by O
Rutter O
, O
who O
defeated O
Jennings B-PERSON
in O
the O
finals O
of O
the O
" O
Jeopardy O
! O
" O

On O
Saturday O
16 O
September O
2006 O
the O
stadium O
played O
host O
to O
' O
The O
Battle O
of O
Belle O
Vue O
' O
when O
11,000 O
fans O
from O
Trinity B-ORGANIZATION
and O
Castleford O
watched O
the O
match O
which O
would O
decide O
who O
was O
relegated O
from O
Super O
League O
. O

The O
primary O
economic O
activity O
in O
the O
Somerset B-LOCATION
region O
is O
agricultural O
production O
( O
120.8 O
million O
in O
2006 O
) O
. O

Normandy B-LOCATION
has O
many O
local O
clubs O
( O
especially O
sport O
) O
set O
up O
throughout O
the O
village O
. O

In O
the O
1970s O
, O
Pickett B-PERSON
requested O
that O
the O
funds O
be O
used O
to O
honor O
women O
scientists O
. O

Also O
in O
2002 O
, O
Reid B-PERSON
announced O
the O
creation O
of O
the O
BC O
Early O
Childhood O
Development O
Legacy O
Fund O
, O
which O
supports O
community O
initiatives O
to O
support O
children O
under O
the O
age O
of O
6 O
. O

Yeo B-PERSON
also O
supported O
a O
campaign O
led O
by O
the O
Duchess O
of O
Hamilton O
for O
slaughterhouse O
reform O
and O
spoke O
at O
a O
number O
of O
public O
meetings O
to O
demand O
an O
end O
to O
what O
were O
described O
as O
cruel O
methods O
of O
slaughtering O
animals O
for O
food O
and O
calling O
for O
the O
compulsory O
introduction O
of O
mechanically O
operated O
humane O
- O
killers O
. O

Kenyon B-PERSON
played O
three O
Tests O
on O
the O
1951/52 O
tour O
to O
India O
, O
two O
more O
in O
1953 O
, O
with O
three O
more O
appearances O
in O
1955 O
, O
but O
life O
in O
the O
fast O
lane O
did O
not O
seem O
to O
suit O
his O
temperament O
. O

In O
his O
memoirs O
, O
written O
many O
years O
after O
the O
event O
, O
Libby B-PERSON
claims O
to O
have O
conceived O
a O
buttstock O
for O
the O
Lewis O
machine O
guns O
used O
by O
observers O
, O
that O
was O
then O
fabricated O
overnight O
by O
the O
gunnery O
sergeant O
of O
his O
unit O
and O
widely O
adopted O
as O
a O
standard O
fitting O
. O

Prior O
to O
the O
game O
Clarke B-PERSON
announced O
that O
it O
would O
be O
his O
last O
alumni O
game O
. O

Redwood B-PERSON
has O
stated O
since O
then O
: O
" O
I O
have O
never O
spoken O
or O
written O
against O
civil O
partnerships O
and O
gay O
marriage O
and O
am O
not O
proposing O
any O
change O
to O
current O
laws O
. O

Joseph O
Giovannini O
, O
recalling O
Govan O
's O
technically O
unrealizable O
onetime O
plan O
to O
hang O
Jeff O
Koons O
' O
" O
Train O
" O
sculpture O
from O
the O
facade O
of O
the O
Ahmanson O
Gallery O
, O
has O
accused O
Govan B-PERSON
of O
" O
driving O
the O
institution O
over O
a O
cliff O
into O
an O
equivalent O
mid O
- O
air O
wreck O
of O
its O
own O
" O
. O

At O
Best O
in O
the O
World O
' O
16 O
, O
Moose B-PERSON
teamed O
with O
War O
Machine O
but O
lost O
against O
Bullet O
Club O
. O

Nolan B-PERSON
agreed O
and O
the O
band O
began O
to O
tour O
. O

In O
1996 O
, O
McKay B-PERSON
hired O
Tony O
Dungy O
as O
head O
coach O
, O
and O
in O
1999 O
the O
Bucs O
played O
in O
the O
NFC O
Championship O
Game O
. O

The O
album O
featured O
the O
traditional O
song O
" O
James O
Connolly O
" O
which O
Dempsey B-PERSON
had O
become O
known O
for O
singing O
at O
recent O
protests O
to O
water O
charges O
introduced O
by O
the O
Irish O
government O
. O

Then O
, O
" O
an O
agonizing O
scream O
pierce[d O
] O
the O
air O
" O
which O
prompted O
commentator O
Robin O
Roberts O
to O
cry O
" O
Shea O
Ralph O
, O
oh O
goodness O
, O
oh O
no O
" O
, O
recognizing O
that O
Ralph B-PERSON
had O
yet O
again O
torn O
an O
ACL O
. O

On O
December O
22 O
, O
2005 O
, O
Washburn B-PERSON
signed O
a O
four O
- O
year O
contract O
worth O
$ O
37.5 O
million O
with O
the O
Seattle O
Mariners O
. O

At O
the O
same O
time O
Curtis B-PERSON
produced O
recordings O
of O
Paul O
and O
Barry O
Ryan O
for O
their O
stepfather O
, O
Harold O
Davidson O
. O

Libby B-PERSON
is O
the O
Senate O
Majority O
Leader O
and O
represents O
Lewiston O
, O
Maine O
's O
second O
largest O
city O
, O
in O
the O
Maine O
Senate O
. O

Nolan B-PERSON
owns O
two O
restaurants O
called O
Britannia O
Arms O
in O
San O
Jose O
, O
California O
He O
and O
his O
wife O
Diana O
have O
one O
daughter O
, O
Jordan O
, O
and O
one O
son O
, O
Dylan O
. O

Carlisle B-ORGANIZATION
also O
celebrated O
40 O
consecutive O
years O
of O
dividend O
increases O
for O
shareholders O
. O

On O
September O
27 O
, O
2016 O
, O
Annapurna B-ORGANIZATION
launched O
a O
television O
production O
division O
, O
Annapurna O
Television O
, O
which O
is O
headed O
by O
former O
HBO O
executive O
Sue O
Naegle O
( O
with O
her O
label O
, O
Naegle O
Ink O
, O
now O
part O
of O
the O
division O
) O
. O

The O
town O
of O
Macclesfield B-LOCATION
was O
named O
after O
the O
Earl O
of O
Macclesfield O
, O
to O
whom O
George O
Davenport O
was O
a O
steward O
in O
England O
. O

Noah B-PERSON
is O
a O
highly O
important O
figure O
in O
Islam O
and O
he O
is O
seen O
as O
one O
of O
the O
most O
significant O
of O
all O
prophets O
. O

Flynn B-PERSON
collaborated O
with O
New O
York O
Police O
Department O
Detective O
Giuseppe O
" O
Joe O
" O
Petrosino O
, O
who O
was O
murdered O
in O
1909 O
in O
Palermo O
, O
Sicily O
, O
where O
he O
was O
tracing O
the O
backgrounds O
of O
the O
gangsters O
plaguing O
New O
York O
City O
. O

Taranaki B-LOCATION
is O
unusual O
in O
that O
it O
has O
experienced O
at O
least O
five O
of O
its O
major O
eruptions O
by O
the O
method O
of O
cone O
collapse O
. O

Born O
at O
Manorbier O
Castle O
in O
Pembrokeshire O
, O
Wales O
, O
Gerald B-PERSON
was O
of O
mixed O
Norman O
and O
Welsh O
descent O
. O

Tamm B-PERSON
has O
published O
in O
scientific O
journals O
and O
presented O
research O
to O
a O
broader O
public O
in O
other O
venues O
, O
including O
the O
newspaper O
" O
Postimees O
" O
, O
Radio O
Kuku O
's O
program O
" O
Falling O
Apple O
" O
( O
" O
Kukkuv O
õun O
" O
– O
28 O
August O
2010 O
) O
, O
and O
Eesti O
Televisioon O
's O
program O
" O
Good O
Vision O
" O
( O
15 O
October O
2009 O
, O
20 O
October O
2011 O
, O
17 O
January O
2012 O
) O
. O

Denmark B-LOCATION
post O
office O
was O
established O
in O
1882 O
. O

Although O
he O
exhibited O
at O
the O
Scottish O
Royal O
Academy O
, O
Doyle B-PERSON
was O
not O
as O
successful O
an O
artist O
as O
he O
wanted O
, O
and O
suffered O
from O
depression O
and O
alcoholism O
. O

At O
the O
1818 O
general O
election O
, O
Blair B-PERSON
bought O
a O
seat O
in O
Parliament O
, O
in O
the O
rotten O
borough O
of O
Saltash O
in O
Devon O
. O

Mansfield B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
East O
Ayrshire O
in O
Scotland O
. O

By O
1974 O
, O
the O
group O
of O
" O
D&D O
" O
players O
sometimes O
included O
over O
20 O
people O
, O
so O
Kuntz B-PERSON
became O
the O
co O
- O
dungeon O
- O
master O
, O
allowing O
each O
dungeon O
master O
to O
referee O
groups O
of O
only O
a O
dozen O
players O
. O

In O
his O
final O
game O
at O
Tiger O
Stadium O
, O
Flynn B-PERSON
and O
the O
Tigers O
lost O
to O
Arkansas O
, O
seemingly O
losing O
any O
chance O
at O
the O
national O
title O
. O

Between O
1988 O
and O
2006 O
, O
Heine B-PERSON
undertook O
studies O
in O
different O
countries O
, O
including O
Ivory O
Coast O
, O
Belgium O
, O
the O
UK O
and O
the O
Netherlands O
. O

Wellington B-LOCATION
is O
a O
Canadian O
parish O
in O
Kent O
County O
, O
New O
Brunswick O
. O

Cyrus B-PERSON
competed O
at O
the O
NWAACC O
conference O
decathlon O
in O
2008 O
, O
finishing O
fourth O
with O
5,995 O
points O
. O

As O
an O
envoy O
of O
O’Neill O
, O
Pato B-PERSON
has O
delivered O
the O
Country O
Statement O
for O
Papua O
New O
Guinea O
on O
several O
occasions O
at O
the O
United O
Nations O
General O
Assembly O
, O
most O
recently O
on O
29 O
September O
2018 O
. O

Carrington B-PERSON
is O
a O
member O
of O
Alpha O
Phi O
Alpha O
fraternity O
. O

Xinyuan B-ORGANIZATION
has O
traditionally O
engaged O
principally O
in O
residential O
real O
estate O
development O
and O
the O
provision O
of O
property O
management O
services O
, O
focusing O
on O
Tier O
II O
cities O
in O
China O
. O

In O
2010 O
, O
Betty B-PERSON
received O
LifeTime O
Achievement O
Award O
at O
Europa O
Dallas O
. O

Malta B-LOCATION
is O
located O
at O
( O
42.309305 O
, O
-113.370498 O
) O
. O

Warrington B-ORGANIZATION
made O
it O
to O
the O
final O
of O
the O
Regal O
Trophy O
in O
1994 O
but O
lost O
40–10 O
to O
Wigan O
at O
McAlpine O
Stadium O
, O
Huddersfield O
, O
they O
also O
came O
close O
to O
winning O
the O
Championship O
finishing O
third O
on O
points O
difference O
behind O
Wigan O
and O
Bradford O
. O

Delegated O
operational O
responsibility O
by O
No O
. O
1 O
TAF O
's O
new O
Air O
Officer O
Commanding O
, O
Air O
Commodore O
Frederick O
Scherger O
, O
Murdoch B-PERSON
received O
much O
of O
the O
credit O
for O
the O
" O
excellent O
" O
planning O
of O
the O
RAAF O
's O
role O
in O
Operation O
Oboe O
Six O
, O
the O
invasion O
of O
Labuan O
. O
