Throughout O
the O
20th O
century O
, O
Coutts B-ORGANIZATION
opened O
more O
branches O
. O

Plymouth B-LOCATION
has O
a O
historic O
downtown O
district O
, O
which O
promotes O
a O
mix O
of O
retail O
, O
office O
and O
service O
uses O
. O

The O
Pride B-ORGANIZATION
was O
one O
of O
several O
professional O
teams O
to O
play O
in O
Nashua O
, O
and O
one O
of O
five O
to O
have O
played O
at O
Holman O
Stadium O
: O

Yale O
eventually O
split O
and O
part O
of O
it O
became O
the O
Palestra O
Itália O
of O
Minas O
, O
a O
team O
which O
was O
created O
to O
compete O
with O
many O
of O
the O
bigger O
teams O
in O
Belo O
Horizonte O
like O
America O
, O
Atlético O
, O
and O
Yale B-ORGANIZATION
itself O
. O

Irina B-LOCATION
is O
a O
town O
and O
commune O
in O
Madagascar O
. O

Originally O
from O
Diamond O
Creek O
, O
Victoria O
, O
Coventry B-PERSON
played O
his O
early O
football O
for O
the O
Diamond O
Creek O
Football O
Club O
in O
the O
Heidelberg O
District O
Football O
League O
( O
HDFL O
) O
. O

Perkins B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Delta O
County O
, O
Michigan O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Bali B-ORGANIZATION
merged O
with O
Hanes O
Corporation O
in O
1969 O
. O

It O
was O
part O
of O
the O
village O
Obidim O
with O
the O
old O
name O
" O
Obidimski O
hanove O
" O
until O
1965 O
year O
, O
when O
it O
was O
separated O
as O
different O
village O
and O
named O
Mesta B-LOCATION
. O

Starting O
in O
1993 O
, O
Sunderland B-PERSON
covered O
Pac-10 O
basketball O
for O
ESPN O
. O

In O
2011 O
, O
Miller B-LOCATION
was O
the O
site O
of O
the O
only O
gay O
pride O
parade O
in O
Northwest O
Indiana O
. O

Thelma B-LOCATION
is O
located O
at O
an O
elevation O
of O
636 O
feet O
. O

In O
2012 O
Zaire B-PERSON
released O
his O
first O
solo O
album O
, O
titled O
“ O
Warrior O
King O
” O
. O

A O
graduate O
from O
University O
of O
Delhi O
, O
Dibang B-PERSON
grew O
up O
in O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
in O
north O
- O
east O
India O
. O

On O
November O
20 O
, O
Valencia B-PERSON
was O
designated O
for O
assignment O
along O
with O
four O
other O
Red O
Sox O
players O
. O

Sunderland B-LOCATION
is O
within O
the O
Copeland O
UK O
Parliamentary O
constituency O
, O
Trudy O
Harrison O
is O
the O
Member O
of O
parliament O
. O

The O
newly O
redesigned O
Suburban B-ORGANIZATION
and O
Yukon O
XL O
were O
showcased O
to O
the O
public O
for O
the O
first O
time O
on O
September O
27 O
, O
2013 O
, O
at O
the O
State O
Fair O
of O
Texas O
. O

The O
line O
through O
Ivanhoe B-LOCATION
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
transcontinental O
east O
- O
west O
rail O
corridor O
connecting O
Sydney O
to O
Perth O
. O

The O
name O
was O
changed O
to O
Kiwanis B-ORGANIZATION
a O
year O
later O
. O

Beginning O
in O
the O
early O
1840s O
, O
Juba B-PERSON
began O
a O
series O
of O
dance O
competitions O
known O
as O
challenge O
dances O
. O

With O
the O
introduction O
of O
pasteurization O
and O
refrigerated O
rail O
cars O
, O
Stroh B-ORGANIZATION
was O
able O
to O
ship O
some O
of O
his O
beer O
as O
far O
as O
Florida O
and O
Massachusetts O
. O

Mercury O
Rev O
properly O
began O
in O
1989 O
, O
with O
Grasshopper B-PERSON
moving O
to O
electric O
guitar O
and O
the O
band O
playing O
along O
to O
footage O
of O
TV O
wildlife O
documentaries O
. O

Potash B-PERSON
is O
also O
known O
for O
his O
consistent O
in O
game O
references O
to O
the O
consumption O
of O
hot O
dogs O
. O

The O
IRS O
also O
challenged O
this O
valuation O
by O
prosecuting O
the O
estate O
of O
Frederick O
Kohler O
, O
who O
had O
recently O
died O
holding O
975 O
shares O
, O
but O
Kohler B-ORGANIZATION
won O
the O
lawsuit O
. O

In O
April O
2013 O
, O
Constantin O
von O
Bülow O
, O
a O
senior O
vice O
president O
of O
Oaktree O
Capital O
Management O
, O
became O
the O
new O
CEO O
of O
Bavaria B-ORGANIZATION
. O

When O
Ferguson O
and O
Andes O
left O
Spirit O
to O
form O
Jo O
Jo O
Gunne O
due O
to O
the O
slow O
sales O
of O
" O
Sardonicus O
" O
, O
and O
then O
his O
dear O
friend O
Hendrix O
died O
, O
a O
depressed O
California B-PERSON
left O
Spirit O
. O

He O
served O
as O
chairman O
and O
president O
of O
Milwaukee O
- O
based O
Diana O
Corp. O
( O
formerly O
Farm O
House O
Foods O
) O
, O
which O
previously O
acquired O
a O
47 O
% O
stake O
in O
Casablanca B-ORGANIZATION
. O

Packard B-LOCATION
is O
located O
at O
the O
intersection O
of O
Country O
Trunk O
Highway O
JJ O
and O
Chapin O
Road O
, O
at O
an O
elevation O
of O
. O

A O
partial O
list O
of O
Gulf B-ORGANIZATION
and O
Western O
's O
holdings O
between O
1958 O
and O
1982 O
, O
with O
year O
of O
acquisition O
in O
parentheses O
: O

Over O
the O
years O
, O
Haworth B-ORGANIZATION
has O
partnered O
with O
numerous O
designers O
, O
such O
as O
A.G. O
Fronzoni O
, O
Albert O
Holz O
and O
Andreas O
Struppler O
. O

Kapunda B-LOCATION
was O
home O
to O
several O
notable O
manufacturers O
of O
farm O
and O
mining O
machinery O
: O
Robert O
Cameron O
, O
Joseph O
Mellors O
, O
James O
Rowe O
and O
Adamson O
Brothers O
. O

Also O
in O
2006 O
, O
Rackham B-ORGANIZATION
released O
a O
sci O
- O
fi O
squad O
level O
wargame O
called O
" O
AT-43 O
" O
. O

Subsequent O
to O
the O
meeting O
, O
Corm B-PERSON
secured O
the O
Ford O
Motor O
Company O
dealership O
for O
the O
entire O
Greater O
Middle O
East O
region O
at O
a O
time O
when O
Ford O
Motor O
Company O
was O
the O
only O
car O
maker O
in O
the O
world O
. O

In O
1936 O
, O
on O
the O
25th O
anniversary O
of O
his O
graduation O
from O
Harvard O
, O
Tunis B-PERSON
wrote O
" O
Was O
College O
Worthwhile O
? O
" O
, O
a O
condemnation O
of O
the O
Ivy O
League O
school O
and O
of O
his O
classmates O
that O
became O
a O
best O
seller O
. O

Cawood B-LOCATION
being O
within O
the O
Liberty O
of O
Cawood O
, O
Wistow O
, O
and O
Otley O
made O
the O
village O
administratively O
independent O
from O
the O
surrounding O
West O
Riding O
of O
Yorkshire O
. O

Atlas B-PERSON
officially O
retired O
in O
1984 O
, O
but O
remained O
active O
in O
the O
meteorology O
research O
community O
, O
in O
particular O
in O
radar O
meteorology O
. O

Their O
most O
successful O
hit O
" O
Winter O
" O
was O
recorded O
with O
Atlanta B-PERSON
. O

In O
" O
Increasing O
Risk O
I O
: O
A O
definition O
" O
, O
Rothschild B-PERSON
and O
Stiglitz O
introduced O
the O
important O
decision O
theory O
concept O
of O
the O
mean O
- O
preserving O
spread O
, O
which O
leads O
to O
a O
partial O
ordering O
of O
probability O
distributions O
according O
to O
degree O
of O
risk O
. O

Its O
sole O
barangay O
is O
Bayas B-LOCATION
. O

Nile B-PERSON
has O
a O
degree O
in O
physiotherapeutic O
massage O
. O

However O
, O
Jericho B-PERSON
lies O
about O
knowing O
Isherwood O
's O
whereabouts O
, O
but O
Deathstroke O
orders O
his O
son O
to O
find O
Isherwood O
and O
to O
call O
Adeline O
, O
which O
he O
does O
. O

In O
July O
2016 O
, O
Mumbai B-ORGANIZATION
signed O
former O
Royal O
Wahingdoh O
and O
Salgaocar O
FC O
coach O
Santosh O
Kashyap O
as O
their O
Head O
Coach O
. O

Ennis B-LOCATION
is O
the O
only O
incorporated O
city O
in O
the O
United O
States O
that O
still O
elects O
its O
City O
Marshal O
. O

On O
July O
11 O
, O
Villarreal B-PERSON
was O
sent O
back O
up O
to O
the O
Sidewinders O
, O
where O
he O
went O
3–3 O
with O
a O
4.36 O
ERA O
. O

Daniel B-LOCATION
is O
located O
at O
( O
42.865172 O
, O
−110.070921 O
) O
. O

After O
the O
initial O
boom O
ended O
in O
1875 O
, O
Warren B-LOCATION
was O
known O
for O
its O
significant O
Chinese O
population O
. O

Shrewsbury B-PERSON
set O
a O
number O
of O
batting O
records O
for O
Nottinghamshire O
. O

Washburn B-LOCATION
is O
located O
at O
( O
36.29 O
, O
-83.59 O
) O
. O

At O
that O
time O
, O
Ciężkowice B-LOCATION
was O
inhabited O
by O
the O
German O
settlers O
( O
see O
Walddeutsche O
) O
, O
and O
German O
language O
name O
of O
the O
town O
, O
" O
Hardenberg O
" O
was O
also O
used O
in O
documents O
. O

Unlike O
many O
other O
Smoky O
Mountain O
communities O
, O
such O
as O
Cades O
Cove O
and O
the O
Sugarlands O
, O
only O
part O
of O
Cosby B-LOCATION
was O
incorporated O
into O
the O
national O
park O
. O

Edison B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Mercer O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Fiskars O
sold O
Silva B-ORGANIZATION
of O
Sweden O
to O
Karnell O
AB O
in O
2011 O
. O

The O
2016 O
Australian O
census O
which O
was O
conducted O
in O
August O
2016 O
reports O
that O
Bruce B-LOCATION
had O
a O
population O
of O
eight O
people O
. O

Tottenham B-LOCATION
lies O
in O
a O
wheat O
- O
growing O
area O
. O

The O
earliest O
recorded O
Viking O
raid O
on O
Sussex B-LOCATION
took O
place O
in O
895 O
and O
it O
was O
particularly O
difficult O
for O
a O
scattered O
farming O
community O
to O
meet O
these O
sudden O
attacks O
. O

In O
2010 O
, O
Bachmann B-ORGANIZATION
released O
several O
Garden O
Scale O
models O
of O
Thomas O
& O
Friends O
characters O
. O

In O
the O
state O
legislature O
Platina B-LOCATION
is O
located O
in O
the O
4th O
Senate O
District O
, O
represented O
by O
Republican O
Jim O
Nielsen O
, O
and O
in O
the O
2nd O
Assembly O
District O
, O
represented O
by O
Democrat O
Wesley O
Chesbro O
. O

In O
1997 O
, O
Swinburne B-ORGANIZATION
opened O
a O
campus O
at O
Lilydale O
, O
Victoria O
. O

Whitson B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
on O
the O
outskirts O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Newport O
, O
South O
Wales O
. O

Melvin B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Choctaw O
County O
, O
Alabama O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Cynthia B-LOCATION
is O
a O
hamlet O
in O
central O
Alberta O
, O
Canada O
within O
Brazeau O
County O
. O

Bristol B-PERSON
won O
a O
silver O
medal O
at O
the O
1975 O
Pan O
American O
Games O
in O
the O
welterweight O
division O
, O
defeating O
Lucien O
Haime O
of O
Suriname O
, O
Carlos O
Burga O
of O
Peru O
and O
Pedro O
Gamarro O
of O
Venezuela O
before O
losing O
to O
Clinton O
Jackson O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
final O
. O

Beren B-ORGANIZATION
is O
a O
political O
party O
in O
Kyrgyzstan O
. O

In O
the O
16th O
century O
, O
Württemberg B-LOCATION
became O
one O
of O
three O
competing O
southwest O
Imperial O
states O
vying O
for O
greater O
status O
in O
the O
region O
and O
the O
Empire O
at O
large O
. O

Bristol B-PERSON
trained O
at O
the O
Police O
Athletic O
League O
of O
New O
York O
City O
's O
Wynn O
Center O
in O
Brooklyn O
, O
New O
York O
where O
his O
trainer O
was O
former O
pro O
boxer O
Richie O
Hill O
. O

Vincent B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Valley O
Township O
, O
Osborne O
County O
, O
Kansas O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

Northeast B-PERSON
was O
appointed O
as O
Kent O
club O
captain O
on O
30 O
September O
2015 O
. O

Lauren B-ORGANIZATION
is O
licensed O
as O
a O
contractor O
in O
39 O
states O
. O

Prior O
to O
the O
Victorian O
era O
Shanklin B-LOCATION
was O
merely O
a O
small O
agricultural O
and O
fishing O
community O
, O
the O
latter O
nestling O
at O
the O
foot O
of O
the O
chine O
, O
and O
it O
was O
not O
until O
the O
early O
19th O
century O
that O
it O
began O
to O
grow O
. O

Winter O
was O
the O
first O
to O
write O
of O
Juba B-PERSON
as O
a O
man O
who O
introduced O
elements O
of O
African O
dance O
to O
the O
Western O
lexicon O
and O
thus O
fostered O
the O
creation O
of O
a O
distinct O
American O
dance O
idiom O
. O

In O
those O
days O
, O
Hunter B-LOCATION
had O
six O
saloons O
, O
a O
blacksmith O
shop O
, O
restaurants O
, O
two O
stores O
and O
40 O
to O
50 O
homes O
. O

In O
1998 O
, O
Carpenter B-ORGANIZATION
was O
sold O
to O
Spartan O
Motors O
, O
a O
Michigan O
- O
based O
manufacturer O
of O
chassis O
for O
fire O
apparatus O
and O
high O
- O
end O
recreational O
vehicles O
. O

The O
injury O
would O
ultimately O
sideline O
Hills B-PERSON
for O
the O
best O
part O
of O
two O
years O
— O
as O
the O
player O
missed O
the O
whole O
of O
the O
2010–11 O
season O
, O
as O
well O
as O
over O
three O
quarters O
of O
the O
2011–12 O
campaign O
. O

Heartbroken O
at O
their O
betrayal O
, O
he O
thrusts O
Excalibur B-PERSON
into O
the O
ground O
between O
the O
sleeping O
couple O
. O

Shrewsbury B-PERSON
missed O
most O
of O
the O
1874 O
season O
with O
rheumatic O
fever O
, O
and O
did O
not O
make O
his O
first O
- O
class O
debut O
until O
May O
1875 O
for O
Nottinghamshire O
against O
Derbyshire O
. O

Vauxhall B-LOCATION
is O
an O
inner O
city O
district O
of O
Liverpool O
, O
Merseyside O
, O
England O
. O

Starting O
from O
1978 O
, O
Atlantic B-ORGANIZATION
also O
commercialized O
science O
fiction O
toy O
soldier O
lines O
, O
some O
of O
which O
based O
on O
Japanese O
anime O
such O
as O
" O
Captain O
Harlock O
" O
and O
" O
Grendizer O
" O
. O

In O
2006 O
, O
Milne O
was O
declared O
Entrepreneur O
of O
the O
Year O
by O
the O
CBI O
, O
and O
Wolfson B-ORGANIZATION
named O
Company O
of O
the O
Year O
. O

Heir O
to O
a O
great O
tobacco O
fortune O
, O
Lorillard B-PERSON
owned O
no O
less O
than O
of O
undeveloped O
land O
in O
New O
York O
's O
Orange O
and O
Rockland O
counties O
, O
across O
the O
Hudson O
River O
and O
about O
an O
hour O
's O
train O
ride O
from O
the O
city O
. O

Trinity O
Holdings O
, O
the O
management O
of O
the O
Vehicle O
Division O
of O
Hestair O
Engineering O
with O
the O
backing O
of O
banking O
institutions O
, O
bought O
Dennis B-ORGANIZATION
from O
Hestair O
. O

In O
2008 O
, O
Sable B-PERSON
wrote O
Image O
comics O
' O
' O
Hazed O
" O
, O
an O
original O
graphic O
novel O
, O
illustrated O
by O
Robbi O
Rodriguez O
. O

Decades O
ago O
, O
students O
used O
the O
tunnel O
during O
the O
winter O
when O
overcrowding O
forced O
Washburn B-ORGANIZATION
to O
hold O
classes O
in O
Ramsey O
. O

After O
1878 O
, O
Cherokee B-LOCATION
was O
connected O
to O
the O
world O
’s O
first O
long O
distance O
telephone O
line O
which O
ran O
from O
French O
Corral O
to O
the O
Bowman O
Lake O
area O
. O

In O
his O
junior O
year O
at O
Indiana O
, O
the O
2011–12 O
season O
, O
Watford B-PERSON
averaged O
12.6 O
points O
, O
5.8 O
rebounds O
and O
28.4 O
minutes O
per O
game O
. O

Hampshire B-LOCATION
is O
protected O
by O
the O
Hampshire O
Fire O
Department O
, O
division O
of O
the O
Maury O
County O
Fire O
Department O
. O

The O
Firefly O
was O
a O
45 O
cc O
" O
clip O
on O
" O
engined O
bicycle O
built O
from O
1953 O
to O
1955 O
under O
licence O
from O
Miller O
, O
who O
were O
suppliers O
of O
electrical O
components O
to O
Vincent B-ORGANIZATION
. O

Buckley B-LOCATION
is O
situated O
in O
north O
east O
Wales O
approximately O
6 O
miles O
from O
the O
border O
with O
England O
to O
the O
East O
. O

Metz B-LOCATION
is O
located O
along O
U.S. O
Route O
250 O
north O
- O
northwest O
of O
Mannington O
. O

Nummi B-LOCATION
is O
one O
of O
the O
oldest O
suburbs O
of O
Turku O
. O

Following O
the O
success O
of O
the O
first O
generation O
of O
off O
- O
road O
CATs O
, O
Schumacher B-ORGANIZATION
continued O
to O
produce O
many O
successful O
off O
and O
on O
- O
road O
electric O
cars O
. O

As O
a O
blackface O
minstrel O
, O
and O
thus O
parodist O
, O
Juba B-PERSON
may O
have O
incorporated O
conscious O
parodies O
of O
such O
dances O
into O
his O
act O
. O

Burnley B-LOCATION
is O
also O
home O
to O
Burnley O
Rugby O
Club O
( O
formerly O
Calder O
Vale O
Rugby O
Club O
1926–2001 O
) O
. O

The O
branch O
stretched O
from O
Rangiora O
through O
Bennetts O
Junction O
( O
where O
the O
Eyreton O
Branch O
joined O
) O
, O
Oxford B-LOCATION
and O
Sheffield O
. O

The O
five O
" O
Gāhs O
" O
begin O
with O
the O
declaration O
in O
Middle O
Persian O
, O
that O
" O
Ohrmazd O
is O
Lord O
" O
and O
incorporate O
the O
Gathic O
verse O
" O
Whom O
, O
Mazda B-PERSON
hast O
thou O
appointed O
my O
protector O
" O
. O

Influenced O
by O
Gandhian O
ideals O
, O
MGR B-PERSON
joined O
the O
Indian O
National O
Congress O
. O

Essex B-LOCATION
lies O
on O
Old O
National O
Trails O
Highway O
– O
part O
of O
the O
old O
Route O
66 O
– O
just O
south O
of O
Interstate O
40 O
in O
the O
Mojave O
Desert O
. O

Faulkner B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Charles O
County O
, O
Maryland O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Convinced O
that O
the O
process O
could O
be O
industrialized O
, O
he O
wrote O
to O
Liebig B-PERSON
to O
suggest O
opening O
a O
manufacturing O
plant O
in O
South O
America O
. O

Philips B-PERSON
enjoyed O
writing O
poetry O
and O
he O
was O
especially O
pleased O
with O
his O
" O
Epistle O
from O
Windemere O
to O
Richd O
. O

This O
led O
to O
a O
collaboration O
with O
Caldera B-ORGANIZATION
to O
develop O
OpenLinux O
. O

Katherine B-LOCATION
is O
also O
the O
closest O
major O
town O
to O
RAAF O
Base O
Tindal O
located O
17 O
km O
southeast O
and O
provides O
education O
, O
health O
, O
local O
government O
services O
and O
employment O
opportunities O
for O
the O
families O
of O
Defence O
personnel O
stationed O
there O
. O

Gorton B-LOCATION
was O
home O
to O
the O
world O
- O
famous O
Belle O
Vue O
Zoological O
Gardens O
from O
1836 O
until O
its O
closure O
in O
the O
1980s O
. O

Bieber B-LOCATION
is O
a O
river O
of O
Hesse O
, O
Germany O
. O

Seguin B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Sheridan O
County O
, O
Kansas O
, O
United O
States O
, O
located O
in O
Logan O
Township O
about O
10 O
miles O
west O
of O
the O
county O
seat O
in O
Hoxie O
. O

Banksia B-LOCATION
is O
also O
serviced O
by O
State O
Transit O
routes O
400 O
and O
410 O
that O
run O
between O
Burwood O
and O
Bondi O
Junction O
via O
Eastgardens O
. O

To O
manufacture O
spirulina O
nutritional O
products O
Hills B-PERSON
started O
the O
Light O
Force O
company O
in O
Santa O
Cruz O
, O
California O
, O
which O
was O
one O
of O
the O
early O
models O
for O
multi O
- O
level O
marketing O
. O

In O
December O
2006 O
, O
Nixon B-ORGANIZATION
was O
acquired O
by O
Billabong O
International O
for O
approximately O
US$ O
55 O
million O
and O
a O
deferred O
payment O
of O
approximately O
US$ O
76 O
million O
in O
FY O
2012 O
. O

Vigo B-LOCATION
is O
located O
at O
, O
about O
southwest O
of O
Terre O
Haute O
, O
the O
county O
seat O
. O

The O
ruined O
castle O
at O
Nicastro B-LOCATION
served O
as O
the O
place O
of O
imprisonment O
of O
Frederick O
II O
's O
son O
Henry O
. O

Tirupati B-PERSON
was O
the O
first O
RedFM O
Idol O
, O
a O
talent O
hunt O
held O
by O
Vancouver O
radio O
channels O
REDFM O
93.1 O
in O
2005 O
. O

Young O
and O
Barcelona B-PERSON
met O
in O
the O
mid-1940s O
. O

GNU B-PERSON
was O
named O
one O
of O
four O
" O
must O
- O
see O
" O
ensembles O
at O
the O
inaugural O
Festival O
Day O
. O

The O
ancient O
windows O
were O
donated O
to O
Pomfret B-ORGANIZATION
in O
1947 O
in O
memory O
of O
John O
Grant O
Fitch O
‘ O
42 O
, O
an O
alumnus O
killed O
in O
1945 O
in O
Germany O
during O
World O
War O
II O
. O

Sutherland B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Dinwiddie O
County O
, O
Virginia O
, O
United O
States O
. O

The O
O'Neill B-ORGANIZATION
is O
the O
recipient O
of O
two O
Tony O
Awards O
, O
the O
1979 O
Special O
Award O
and O
the O
2010 O
Regional O
Theatre O
Award O
, O
and O
the O
2015 O
National O
Medal O
of O
Arts O
presented O
on O
September O
22 O
, O
2016 O
by O
President O
Obama O
. O

Opel B-PERSON
eventually O
moved O
to O
Trinidad O
and O
then O
subsequently O
returned O
home O
to O
Barbados O
. O

Shrewsbury B-PERSON
finished O
the O
season O
with O
an O
innings O
of O
65 O
not O
out O
against O
Surrey O
in O
a O
low O
scoring O
match O
. O

Normandy B-ORGANIZATION
ceased O
to O
exist O
when O
it O
was O
taken O
over O
by O
the O
Newmont O
Mining O
Corporation O
in O
February O
2002 O
, O
and O
became O
Newmont O
Asia O
Pacific O
instead O
. O

Havas B-PERSON
was O
the O
anchorman O
of O
the O
Nap O
TV O
's O
only O
program O
, O
Nap O
- O
kelte O
from O
1989 O
. O

Stryker B-PERSON
founded O
Galacticomm O
in O
1985 O
, O
and O
created O
MajorBBS O
which O
supported O
real O
- O
time O
teleconference O
, O
gaming O
, O
discussion O
forums O
, O
user O
profiles O
( O
registry O
) O
, O
and O
file O
transfer O
sections O
. O

Intellectuals O
booze O
" O
( O
" O
" O
) O
- O
a O
phrase O
attributed O
by O
Jaguar B-PERSON
to O
the O
journalist O
Paulo O
Francis O
- O
which O
is O
reproduced O
in O
one O
of O
the O
strips O
as O
being O
spoken O
by O
BD O
. O

The O
movie O
features O
Oppel O
as O
narrator O
, O
and O
includes O
interviews O
with O
John O
Waters O
, O
Divine O
, O
Danny O
Nicoletta O
, O
and O
others O
in O
the O
San O
Francisco O
scene O
who O
knew O
Opel B-PERSON
. O

The O
remaining O
Republic B-ORGANIZATION
stores O
were O
subsequently O
merged O
with O
USC O
. O

" O
It O
's O
night O
and O
day O
" O
from O
UNC O
- O
Greensboro O
, O
said O
Valencia B-PERSON
. O

At O
that O
time O
Hoboken B-LOCATION
was O
part O
of O
Wilrijk O
, O
in O
the O
Duchy O
of O
Brabant O
. O

While O
the O
paper O
issued O
an O
apology O
for O
its O
use O
of O
the O
pejorative O
term O
, O
Virgin B-PERSON
indicated O
that O
the O
paper O
should O
do O
more O
than O
just O
apologize O
, O
suggesting O
setting O
up O
a O
scholarship O
, O
or O
a O
program O
designed O
to O
address O
racism O
and O
discrimination O
. O

SMS B-PERSON
is O
another O
Ukrainian O
female O
pop O
- O
music O
band O
that O
added O
some O
competition O
to O
the O
already O
existing O
Nu O
Virgos O
. O

Wainwright B-LOCATION
is O
a O
town O
in O
east O
- O
central O
Alberta O
, O
Canada O
, O
southeast O
of O
Edmonton O
. O

Kazan B-LOCATION
had O
trade O
relations O
with O
Moscow O
, O
Crimea O
, O
Turkey O
and O
other O
regions O
. O

Polesie B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
administrative O
district O
of O
Gmina O
Krzywiń O
, O
within O
Kościan O
County O
, O
Greater O
Poland O
Voivodeship O
, O
in O
west O
- O
central O
Poland O
. O

Murray O
was O
organising O
meetings O
between O
Illawarra O
players O
and O
Super O
League O
officials O
, O
as O
Super O
League O
had O
intentions O
of O
either O
getting O
the O
Steelers O
or O
possibly O
a O
new O
Illawarra B-ORGANIZATION
club O
. O

Shrewsbury B-PERSON
had O
held O
the O
record O
for O
over O
15 O
years O
; O
only O
Clem O
Hill O
and O
Wally O
Hammond O
have O
held O
the O
record O
for O
longer O
. O

Disney B-PERSON
edited O
, O
with O
biographical O
preface O
, O
the O
" O
Discourses O
" O
of O
his O
cousin O
, O
Samuel O
Disney O
, O
LL.B. O
, O
1788 O
; O
and O
, O
with O
Charles O
Butler O
, O
he O
edited O
" O
A O
New O
Translation O
of O
the O
Book O
of O
Psalms O
" O
, O
1807 O
, O
from O
the O
manuscript O
of O
Alexander O
Geddes O
. O

After O
June O
25 O
, O
1880 O
, O
the O
Winchester B-PERSON
family O
left O
Monson O
, O
Maine O
and O
by O
1881 O
had O
relocated O
to O
Forestburg O
, O
in O
Sanborn O
County O
in O
Dakota O
Territory O
, O
where O
Charles O
taught O
school O
at O
upper O
Forestburg O
from O
its O
opening O
on O
November O
7 O
, O
1881 O
, O
until O
a O
permanent O
replacement O
started O
on O
December O
26 O
, O
1881 O
. O

A O
stop O
on O
the O
Florida O
, O
Alabama O
and O
Gulf O
Railroad O
, O
Baker B-LOCATION
was O
platted O
in O
1910 O
and O
grew O
up O
around O
the O
timber O
and O
turpentine O
industries O
. O

In O
May O
1991 O
, O
Carpenter B-ORGANIZATION
purchased O
the O
tooling O
, O
product O
rights O
, O
and O
intellectual O
property O
of O
Crown O
Coach O
, O
a O
California O
- O
based O
manufacturer O
that O
had O
closed O
its O
doors O
two O
months O
prior O
. O

Anatoli B-LOCATION
is O
a O
small O
village O
in O
the O
Ierapetra O
municipality O
of O
the O
prefecture O
of O
Lasithi O
in O
eastern O
Crete O
. O

Ruff B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Mathews O
County O
, O
in O
the O
U. O
S. O
state O
of O
Virginia O
. O

In O
so O
doing O
, O
Juba B-PERSON
ensured O
that O
blackface O
dance O
was O
more O
authentically O
African O
than O
the O
other O
elements O
of O
the O
minstrel O
show O
. O

Another O
member O
of O
the O
Rich O
family O
, O
Robert O
F. O
Rich O
, O
headed O
Woolrich B-ORGANIZATION
for O
many O
years O
and O
was O
also O
a O
longtime O
Republican O
member O
of O
the O
U.S. O
House O
of O
Representatives O
. O

In O
what O
Michelle O
Nolan O
in O
" O
Ball O
Tales O
" O
calls O
a O
" O
remarkable O
book O
" O
, O
Tunis B-PERSON
uses O
his O
only O
non O
- O
Dodgers O
baseball O
novel O
to O
emphasize O
a O
favorite O
theme O
when O
the O
young O
protagonist O
admits O
to O
his O
father O
" O
it O
's O
better O
to O
lose O
, O
much O
as O
it O
hurts O
, O
than O
to O
play O
dirty O
" O
. O

Moss B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Clay O
County O
, O
Tennessee O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Clydesdale B-LOCATION
is O
a O
constituency O
of O
the O
Scottish O
Parliament O
( O
Holyrood O
) O
. O

Lauer B-LOCATION
is O
a O
small O
island O
in O
the O
Hvaler O
municipality O
in O
South O
- O
East O
Norway O
. O

Nyker B-LOCATION
has O
one O
of O
Bornholm O
's O
four O
round O
churches O
, O
Ny O
Kirke O
; O
the O
names O
of O
both O
church O
and O
village O
mean O
" O
new O
church O
" O
. O

Henry O
Burr O
, O
William O
F. O
Denny O
, O
Byron O
G. O
Harlan O
, O
Ada O
Jones O
, O
Billy O
Murray O
, O
Vess O
Ossman O
, O
Steve O
Porter O
, O
Cal O
Stewart O
, O
and O
Bert O
Williams O
among O
many O
other O
early O
recording O
pioneers O
had O
their O
recordings O
leased O
to O
Aretino B-ORGANIZATION
. O

During O
the O
2017 O
season O
, O
the O
Yankees O
were O
fined O
after O
a O
phone O
conversation O
between O
Rothschild B-PERSON
and O
replay O
room O
officials O
. O

Povey O
had O
been O
part O
of O
the O
backroom O
set O
up O
at O
Reading B-ORGANIZATION
since O
2001 O
and O
held O
responsibility O
for O
the O
design O
and O
build O
of O
the O
club O
website O
, O
public O
relations O
, O
marketing O
and O
commercial O
activities O
. O

Clara O
Southmayd O
Ludlow O
was O
born O
on O
December O
26 O
, O
1852 O
at O
Easton O
, O
Pennsylvania O
, O
the O
eldest O
child O
of O
Jacob O
Rapalje O
and O
Anna O
Mary O
( O
Hunt O
) O
Ludlow B-PERSON
. O

Lindisfarne B-LOCATION
became O
the O
base O
for O
Christian O
evangelism O
in O
the O
North O
of O
England O
and O
also O
sent O
a O
successful O
mission O
to O
Mercia O
. O

Trinity B-LOCATION
was O
the O
site O
of O
medical O
research O
, O
including O
the O
introduction O
of O
the O
smallpox O
vaccine O
to O
the O
new O
world O
in O
1798 O
by O
John O
Clinch O
, O
a O
boyhood O
friend O
and O
medical O
colleague O
of O
Edward O
Jenner O
. O

After O
remaining O
a O
family O
- O
owned O
company O
into O
the O
late O
1980s O
, O
Carpenter B-ORGANIZATION
was O
sold O
and O
relocated O
in O
1995 O
to O
the O
former O
Wayne O
Corporation O
facilities O
in O
Richmond O
, O
Indiana O
. O

Athletically O
, O
Driscoll B-ORGANIZATION
competed O
in O
the O
Suburban O
Catholic O
Conference O
. O

Motherwell B-LOCATION
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
established O
clubs O
in O
the O
top O
division O
of O
the O
Scottish O
football O
league O
system O
, O
having O
been O
in O
the O
top O
flight O
continuously O
since O
the O
mid-80s O
. O

Sable B-PERSON
has O
opened O
for O
well O
- O
known O
artists O
like O
Meiko O
and O
Sara O
Bareilles O
. O

Today O
, O
Borg B-LOCATION
is O
the O
location O
of O
Lofotr O
, O
a O
living O
museum O
of O
the O
Viking O
chieftain O
's O
village O
. O

Patton B-LOCATION
is O
east O
of O
Alderson O
. O

Sunderland B-PERSON
continued O
to O
take O
part O
in O
public O
life O
, O
and O
was O
active O
in O
communicating O
with O
the O
court O
of O
Hanover O
about O
the O
steps O
to O
be O
taken O
in O
view O
of O
the O
approaching O
death O
of O
the O
queen O
. O

Moss B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Jasper O
County O
, O
Mississippi O
. O

Peck B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
on O
the O
Sedgwick O
County O
and O
Sumner O
County O
border O
in O
Kansas O
, O
United O
States O
. O

During O
the O
long O
centuries O
of O
Byzantine O
rule O
, O
Andros B-LOCATION
was O
relatively O
obscure O
. O

While O
in O
Sparta O
, O
Nikon B-PERSON
constructed O
three O
churches O
and O
a O
monastery O
and O
continued O
his O
preaching O
and O
teachings O
, O
which O
were O
reportedly O
confirmed O
by O
miracles O
. O

In O
1885 O
Shrewsbury B-PERSON
topped O
the O
batting O
averages O
for O
the O
first O
time O
scoring O
1130 O
runs O
at O
56.50 O
with O
four O
centuries O
, O
including O
carrying O
his O
bat O
for O
224 O
not O
out O
at O
Lord O
's O
. O

The O
silo O
was O
repainted O
with O
the O
Cambria B-ORGANIZATION
logo O
. O

During O
the O
2012 O
- O
2013 O
school O
year O
, O
Caedmon B-ORGANIZATION
celebrated O
the O
50th O
anniversary O
of O
its O
founding O
. O

Reason B-ORGANIZATION
is O
engaged O
in O
several O
transportation O
policy O
endeavors O
. O

In O
2010 O
, O
Chambon B-PERSON
was O
awarded O
the O
Gairdner O
Foundation O
International O
Award O
" O
for O
the O
elucidation O
of O
fundamental O
mechanisms O
of O
transcription O
in O
animal O
cells O
and O
to O
the O
discovery O
of O
the O
nuclear O
receptor O
superfamily O
" O
. O

Albion B-PERSON
became O
a O
pioneer O
in O
inspiring O
MBAs O
to O
leverage O
business O
principles O
to O
build O
a O
better O
world O
. O

Amsterdam B-PERSON
was O
awarded O
a O
B.A. O
from O
Carleton O
University O
( O
Ottawa O
, O
Canada O
) O
in O
1975 O
and O
a O
LL.B. O
from O
Queen O
's O
University O
( O
Kingston O
, O
Canada O
) O
in O
1978 O
. O

Cummins B-LOCATION
has O
about O
of O
land O
. O

Borthwick B-LOCATION
is O
a O
hamlet O
, O
parish O
and O
stream O
in O
Midlothian O
, O
Scotland O
. O

Oman B-PERSON
joined O
as O
a O
lieutenant O
in O
1942 O
and O
served O
in O
the O
United O
States O
Army O
during O
World O
War O
II O
and O
the O
Korean O
War O
, O
conducting O
studies O
on O
medical O
entomology O
and O
the O
biological O
control O
of O
insects O
. O

Emmaus B-LOCATION
is O
governed O
under O
a O
council O
/ O
mayor O
system O
, O
with O
the O
Borough O
Council O
retaining O
the O
vast O
majority O
of O
governmental O
authority O
. O

Reagan B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Henderson O
County O
, O
Tennessee O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Since O
1938 O
, O
Dunfermline B-LOCATION
has O
also O
been O
home O
to O
the O
' O
Kinema O
Ballroom O
' O
a O
ballroom O
/ O
dancehall O
which O
has O
evolved O
into O
a O
famous O
live O
music O
performance O
venue O
and O
nightclub O
which O
has O
hosted O
many O
internationally O
acclaimed O
artists O
. O

As O
of O
2018 O
, O
Zaragoza B-PERSON
is O
now O
working O
on O
" O
The O
Valleyfolk O
" O
, O
a O
YouTube O
channel O
and O
production O
company O
he O
co O
- O
founded O
with O
fellow O
founding O
" O
SourceFed O
" O
members O
Joe O
Bereta O
, O
Elliott O
Morgan O
, O
and O
Lee O
Newton O
. O

Unlike O
other O
places O
of O
the O
same O
name O
, O
Aston B-LOCATION
does O
not O
mean O
" O
eastern O
farm O
or O
village O
, O
" O
but O
instead O
originates O
from O
the O
Old O
English O
words O
" O
tun O
" O
" O
farm O
, O
village O
, O
and O
estate O
" O
with O
an O
uncertain O
first O
element O
. O

Founded O
in O
1966 O
, O
Driscoll B-ORGANIZATION
brought O
Catholic O
secondary O
education O
to O
Addison O
, O
Illinois O
. O

Assuming O
all O
of O
the O
Jubas O
are O
the O
same O
person O
, O
the O
record O
suggests O
that O
Juba B-PERSON
worked O
day O
and O
night O
for O
11 O
years O
— O
from O
1839 O
to O
1850 O
. O

Ellis B-LOCATION
is O
located O
in O
central O
Wisconsin O
approximately O
six O
miles O
northeast O
of O
Stevens O
Point O
, O
approximately O
four O
miles O
north O
of O
Custer O
, O
and O
approximately O
six O
miles O
southwest O
of O
Rosholt O
, O
where O
State O
Road O
66 O
and O
Portage O
County O
Road O
J O
to O
the O
south O
meets O
with O
Ellis O
Road O
. O

Miller B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Madison O
Township O
, O
Morgan O
County O
, O
in O
the O
U.S. O
state O
of O
Indiana O
. O

The O
Free O
Hanseatic O
City O
of O
Bremen O
and O
the O
bishop O
of O
Münster O
also O
frequently O
warred O
with O
the O
counts O
of O
Oldenburg B-LOCATION
. O

Currie B-LOCATION
has O
two O
Scout O
Groups O
- O
the O
31st O
Pentland O
which O
has O
run O
continuously O
since O
1924 O
and O
the O
42nd O
Pentland O
. O

After O
Plouffe O
was O
placed O
on O
the O
DL O
, O
Valencia B-PERSON
returned O
to O
the O
Twins O
roster O
on O
July O
27 O
. O

A O
post O
office O
called O
Leonard B-LOCATION
has O
been O
in O
operation O
since O
1884 O
. O

When O
introduced O
by O
interviewer O
Karen O
Bowerman O
as O
internet O
expert O
Guy O
Kewney O
, O
Goma B-PERSON
realised O
there O
had O
been O
a O
misunderstanding O
and O
was O
visibly O
shocked O
. O

Buckley B-LOCATION
falls O
within O
the O
Rochdale O
county O
constituency O
, O
which O
is O
represented O
by O
Simon O
Danczuk O
MP O
, O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Labour O
Party O
. O

Macdonald B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Manitoba O
northwest O
of O
Portage O
la O
Prairie O
. O

Yalata B-LOCATION
is O
governed O
at O
the O
local O
level O
by O
the O
Aboriginal O
Council O
of O
Yalata O
, O
one O
of O
the O
five O
local O
government O
bodies O
in O
South O
Australia O
classified O
as O
Aboriginal O
Councils O
( O
AC O
) O
. O

Dunfermline B-LOCATION
is O
the O
principal O
shopping O
centre O
serving O
the O
western O
area O
of O
Fife O
and O
is O
the O
region O
's O
second O
largest O
town O
centre O
by O
floorspace O
. O

Lute B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
administrative O
district O
of O
Gmina O
Modliborzyce O
, O
within O
Janów O
Lubelski O
County O
, O
Lublin O
Voivodeship O
, O
in O
eastern O
Poland O
. O

Prior O
to O
this O
merger O
, O
Wakefield B-LOCATION
and O
the O
Bronx O
were O
politically O
part O
of O
Westchester O
County O
( O
the O
Bronx O
later O
attained O
independent O
county O
status O
on O
April O
19 O
, O
1912 O
, O
which O
makes O
it O
the O
62nd O
and O
youngest O
county O
in O
the O
state O
) O
. O

Walt O
Disney O
Imagineering O
created O
" O
The O
Empress O
Lilly O
" O
, O
a O
paddle O
steamer O
replica O
, O
at O
Walt O
Disney O
World O
in O
Disney O
Springs O
and O
Disney B-PERSON
christened O
it O
on O
May O
1 O
, O
1977 O
. O

Bollinger B-ORGANIZATION
secured O
the O
contract O
to O
build O
approximately O
fifty O
Marine O
Protector O
cutters O
. O

Vincent B-ORGANIZATION
has O
a O
contract O
to O
transport O
inmates O
around O
New O
Zealand O
for O
the O
Corrections O
Department O
. O

Durban B-PERSON
was O
brought O
up O
in O
Bracken O
Road O
, O
Margam O
, O
Port O
Talbot O
. O

The O
aircraft O
exploded O
on O
its O
second O
test O
flight O
, O
before O
Opel B-PERSON
had O
had O
a O
chance O
to O
pilot O
it O
himself O
, O
so O
he O
commissioned O
a O
new O
aircraft O
, O
also O
called O
the O
RAK.1 O
, O
from O
Julius O
Hatry O
, O
and O
flew O
it O
at O
Frankfurt O
- O
am O
- O
Main O
on O
30 O
September O
1929 O
. O

Lewin B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
administrative O
district O
of O
Gmina O
Sadkowice O
, O
within O
Rawa O
County O
, O
Łódź O
Voivodeship O
, O
in O
central O
Poland O
. O

At O
the O
, O
Somerset B-LOCATION
had O
a O
population O
of O
approximately O
3,900 O
.. O

Flynn B-LOCATION
is O
located O
between O
Tillyard O
Drive O
, O
Kingsford O
Smith O
Drive O
and O
Ginninderra O
Drive O
and O
is O
next O
to O
the O
suburbs O
of O
Charnwood O
, O
Fraser O
, O
Melba O
, O
Latham O
and O
Spence O
. O

On O
February O
23 O
, O
2018 O
, O
Logic B-PERSON
released O
a O
single O
titled O
" O
44 O
More O
" O
. O

Bethlehem B-ORGANIZATION
released O
the O
first O
albums O
recorded O
by O
singers O
Chris O
Connor O
( O
the O
dual O
releases O
" O
Chris O
Connor O
Sings O
Lullabys O
for O
Lovers O
" O
and O
" O
Chris O
Connor O
Sings O
Lullabys O
of O
Birdland O
" O
) O
in O
1954 O
, O
Nina O
Simone O
( O
" O
Little O
Girl O
Blue O
" O
) O
in O
1958 O
, O
and O
singer O
/ O
actress O
Julie O
London O
. O

In O
May O
2018 O
, O
the O
Huffington O
Post O
reported O
that O
Clay O
Johnson O
, O
former O
director O
of O
Sunlight O
Labs O
, O
had O
been O
accused O
of O
sexual O
misconduct O
and O
mistreatment O
by O
multiple O
women O
during O
his O
employment O
at O
Sunlight B-ORGANIZATION
and O
left O
after O
a O
staff O
insurrection O
. O

In O
July O
2014 O
, O
Watford B-PERSON
joined O
the O
Detroit O
Pistons O
for O
the O
Orlando O
Summer O
League O
and O
the O
Golden O
State O
Warriors O
for O
the O
Las O
Vegas O
Summer O
League O
. O

After O
captaining O
the O
Kiwis O
at O
the O
2016 O
Rugby O
League O
Four O
Nations O
tournament O
, O
Bromwich B-PERSON
was O
named O
the O
New O
Zealand O
Rugby O
League O
's O
Kiwis O
player O
of O
the O
year O
for O
2016 O
. O

Corona B-LOCATION
also O
has O
a O
significant O
Chinese O
population O
. O

Sunderland B-LOCATION
has O
a O
community O
of O
small O
businesses O
that O
focus O
primarily O
on O
the O
needs O
of O
surrounding O
rural O
families O
. O

Juniper B-PERSON
has O
advised O
companies O
including O
Danone O
, O
Interserve O
and O
Skanska O
, O
assisting O
with O
their O
sustainability O
strategies O
. O

Since O
the O
redevelopment O
of O
former O
brownfield O
areas O
of O
heavy O
industry O
into O
affluent O
riverside O
housing O
areas O
, O
and O
the O
founding O
of O
the O
St O
Peters O
Campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
Sunderland O
to O
the O
immediate O
south O
of O
the O
area O
, O
Roker B-LOCATION
has O
undergone O
rapid O
demographic O
change O
. O

During O
the O
second O
half O
of O
the O
20th O
century O
, O
Darnley B-LOCATION
experienced O
total O
transformation O
from O
being O
a O
modest O
semi O
- O
rural O
community O
to O
becoming O
a O
significant O
part O
of O
Glasgow O
's O
response O
to O
a O
post O
- O
war O
housing O
shortage O
. O

When O
Haase O
was O
reelected O
in O
2007 O
, O
it O
was O
the O
only O
time O
that O
Labor O
had O
won O
government O
at O
an O
election O
without O
winning O
Kalgoorlie B-LOCATION
. O

With O
employment O
at O
2.0 O
% O
, O
Stockport B-LOCATION
has O
the O
lowest O
rate O
of O
unemployment O
of O
all O
Greater O
Manchester O
's O
boroughs O
. O

Wendy O
was O
a O
separate O
parish O
until O
1957 O
when O
it O
was O
merged O
with O
neighbouring O
Shingay O
to O
form O
the O
present O
civil O
parish O
of O
Shingay O
cum O
Wendy B-LOCATION
. O

Campaigning O
on O
a O
platform O
of O
equality O
for O
all O
citizens O
regardless O
of O
religion O
, O
ethnic O
background O
, O
or O
nationality O
, O
Tami B-ORGANIZATION
won O
three O
seats O
, O
taken O
by O
Abuhatzira O
, O
President O
of O
Sephardi O
Federation O
of O
Israel O
and O
former O
Mapai O
and O
Alignment O
MK O
and O
Minister O
Aharon O
Uzan O
, O
and O
another O
former O
NRP O
member O
, O
Ben O
- O
Zion O
Rubin O
. O

Under O
Clough O
, O
Durban B-PERSON
was O
moved O
from O
Inside O
- O
forward O
to O
an O
attacking O
midfield O
role O
and O
was O
handed O
the O
captaincy O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
a O
5–1 O
win O
over O
his O
former O
club O
Cardiff O
City O
. O

Cotillion B-ORGANIZATION
is O
also O
responsible O
for O
launching O
the O
career O
of O
Luther O
Vandross O
, O
who O
was O
in O
a O
three O
- O
member O
group O
called O
Luther O
( O
the O
rights O
now O
lay O
with O
his O
estate O
as O
he O
had O
bought O
them O
back O
when O
he O
was O
alive O
preventing O
reissues O
) O
. O

Nani B-LOCATION
is O
a O
town O
in O
Ghazni O
Province O
, O
Afghanistan O
. O

Emmaus B-LOCATION
is O
located O
in O
the O
Allentown O
- O
Bethlehem O
- O
Easton O
, O
PA O
- O
NJ O
Metropolitan O
Statistical O
Area O
, O
which O
is O
in O
the O
New O
York O
City O
- O
Newark O
, O
New O
Jersey O
, O
NY O
- O
NJ O
- O
CT O
- O
PA O
Combined O
Statistical O
Area O
. O

Meanwhile O
, O
Etienne O
get O
a O
lecture O
from O
her O
employer O
about O
how O
she O
compromised O
her O
mission O
by O
getting O
so O
close O
to O
Jericho B-PERSON
and O
then O
gets O
a O
call O
from O
Rose O
, O
who O
is O
traveling O
to O
see O
her O
brother O
to O
prevent O
the O
vision O
she O
saw O
. O

In O
1992 O
, O
they O
closed O
their O
Holy O
Loch O
base O
, O
and O
Dunoon B-LOCATION
suffered O
an O
economic O
downturn O
. O

His O
description O
of O
Marloes B-LOCATION
is O
as O
follows O
: O

Cadbury B-PERSON
never O
worked O
in O
the O
family O
business O
. O

According O
to O
his O
IMDb O
profile O
, O
Zaragoza B-PERSON
became O
involved O
with O
filmmaking O
in O
2009 O
, O
receiving O
a O
sound O
department O
credit O
for O
" O
Cloudy O
with O
a O
Chance O
of O
Meatballs O
" O
. O

Unlike O
other O
towns O
in O
the O
Cuyuna O
Range O
, O
rather O
than O
having O
its O
population O
decline O
by O
thirty O
or O
forty O
percent O
, O
Manganese B-LOCATION
lost O
its O
entire O
population O
. O

Ever O
since O
Nixon O
Public O
School O
was O
closed O
due O
to O
the O
provincial O
government O
cutbacks O
on O
education O
, O
Nixon B-LOCATION
has O
become O
a O
bedroom O
community O
for O
people O
who O
can O
afford O
to O
live O
in O
a O
single O
- O
family O
house O
. O

Earley B-LOCATION
is O
also O
served O
by O
Reading O
Buses O
who O
provide O
a O
number O
of O
bus O
services O
to O
and O
from O
the O
centre O
of O
Reading O
, O
namely O
the O
4 O
, O
X4 O
, O
19a O
, O
19b O
, O
19c O
; O
and O
the O
21 O
, O
a O
24-hour O
service O
. O

Beginning O
in O
1997 O
, O
Zoran B-ORGANIZATION
established O
itself O
as O
a O
leading O
provider O
of O
MPEG-2 O
technology O
for O
DVD O
and O
Super O
Video O
CD O
applications O
. O

William B-LOCATION
lies O
south O
of O
Fairfax O
and O
the O
Fairfax O
Stone O
and O
north O
of O
Thomas O
. O

The O
JROTC O
program O
at O
Everglades B-ORGANIZATION
has O
maintained O
an O
Honor O
Unit O
with O
Distinction O
( O
HUD O
) O
status O
since O
2007 O
and O
has O
sent O
cadets O
to O
several O
competitive O
national O
conventions O
including O
the O
George O
C. O
Marshal O
Leadership O
Symposium O
, O
and O
the O
JROTC O
Academic O
Bowl O
. O

Donald B-LOCATION
is O
a O
town O
in O
Victoria O
, O
Australia O
, O
located O
on O
the O
Richardson O
River O
, O
at O
the O
junction O
of O
Sunraysia O
Highway O
and O
Borung O
Highway O
, O
in O
the O
Shire O
of O
Buloke O
. O

For O
20 O
long O
years O
TVR B-PERSON
was O
repeatedly O
insisting O
through O
his O
‘ O
Dinamalar O
’ O
daily O
that O
the O
train O
service O
between O
Trivandrum O
- O
Kanyakumari O
- O
Tirunelveli O
was O
essential O
for O
the O
development O
of O
that O
area O
. O

Following O
a O
period O
of O
absence O
from O
the O
public O
scene O
, O
Asia B-PERSON
has O
attended O
several O
events O
since O
the O
start O
of O
2009 O
. O

Since O
Malcolm O
Walker O
's O
return O
to O
the O
company O
, O
Iceland B-ORGANIZATION
has O
reduced O
the O
workforce O
by O
500 O
jobs O
at O
the O
Deeside O
head O
office O
, O
with O
approximately O
300 O
jobs O
moved O
in O
September O
as O
a O
result O
of O
a O
relocation O
of O
a O
distribution O
warehouse O
from O
Deeside O
to O
Warrington O
. O

In O
July O
2009 O
, O
Andy O
Brannan O
joined O
Wolfson B-ORGANIZATION
as O
Chief O
Commercial O
Officer O
. O

Neither O
of O
the O
Milano B-PERSON
brothers O
( O
nor O
six O
of O
the O
others O
originally O
arrested O
) O
were O
charged O
due O
to O
lack O
of O
evidence O
. O

Sunderland B-PERSON
developed O
into O
one O
of O
Loyola O
's O
top O
volleyball O
players O
, O
earning O
All O
- O
America O
honors O
. O

A O
post O
office O
was O
established O
in O
the O
community O
in O
1929 O
and O
it O
was O
named O
Edsel B-LOCATION
for O
the O
postmaster O
's O
nephew O
. O

Hubertus B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Richfield O
and O
the O
town O
of O
Erin O
in O
Washington O
County O
, O
Wisconsin O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Passy B-LOCATION
was O
the O
home O
of O
Benjamin O
Franklin O
during O
the O
nine O
years O
that O
he O
lived O
in O
France O
during O
the O
American O
Revolutionary O
War O
. O

Richard B-LOCATION
is O
a O
small O
village O
in O
Douglas O
No O
. O
436 O
, O
Saskatchewan O
, O
Canada O
. O

Devine B-PERSON
subsequently O
created O
a O
NASDAQ O
and O
TSX O
publicly O
traded O
company O
, O
Devine O
Entertainment O
, O
which O
established O
itself O
as O
a O
multiple O
Emmy O
Award O
and O
Gemini O
Award O
winning O
corporation O
. O

Arbuthnot O
, O
owned O
by O
the O
Arbuthnot O
family O
, O
was O
the O
largest O
bank O
in O
the O
Presidency B-LOCATION
until O
its O
crash O
in O
1906 O
. O

Wheelwright B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
town O
of O
Hardwick O
, O
Worcester O
County O
, O
Massachusetts O
, O
United O
States O
, O
about O
northwest O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Worcester O
, O
Massachusetts O
. O

Blair B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Doniphan O
County O
, O
Kansas O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

Since O
2007 O
, O
SANParks O
has O
undertaken O
to O
re O
- O
establish O
Cecilia B-LOCATION
as O
a O
conservation O
area O
integrated O
with O
the O
Table O
Mountain O
National O
Park O
. O

While O
owner O
of O
CFSB O
Corporation O
, O
now O
known O
as O
Stone O
Capital O
, O
Inc. O
, O
Fail B-PERSON
acquired O
one O
such O
package O
of O
15 O
insolvent O
thrifts O
, O
the O
Pard O
/ O
Rose O
package O
. O

Hampshire B-PERSON
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
76 O
on O
1 O
March O
2017 O
, O
after O
a O
long O
illness O
. O

Prime O
Minister O
Henri O
Lopès O
and O
his O
government O
resigned O
after O
a O
meeting O
of O
the O
Congolese O
Labour O
Party O
's O
Central O
Committee O
in O
December O
1975 O
, O
and O
Goma B-PERSON
was O
appointed O
to O
replace O
him O
at O
the O
head O
of O
a O
new O
government O
, O
composed O
of O
14 O
members O
, O
on O
18 O
December O
1975 O
. O

Valencia B-PERSON
led O
all O
players O
in O
the O
tournament O
in O
runs O
( O
7 O
) O
, O
home O
runs O
( O
3 O
) O
, O
RBIs O
( O
9 O
) O
, O
walks O
( O
5 O
) O
, O
and O
slugging O
percentage O
( O
1.000 O
) O
, O
while O
batting O
.375 O
with O
a O
.500 O
on O
base O
percentage O
in O
16 O
at O
bats O
, O
and O
playing O
first O
base O
and O
DH O
. O

Wiltshire B-PERSON
returned O
to O
Yeovil O
in O
April O
2017 O
ahead O
of O
the O
FA O
WSL O
Spring O
Series O
. O

Sunbeam B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Logan O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
. O

On O
February O
25 O
, O
2007 O
, O
Pence B-PERSON
formally O
endorsed O
former O
Congresswoman O
Anne O
Northup O
over O
Fletcher O
in O
the O
2007 O
governor O
's O
race O
. O

The O
thrust O
to O
bring O
the O
telephone O
service O
to O
Mink B-LOCATION
began O
when O
a O
resident O
of O
the O
community O
, O
Alice O
Louise O
Johnson O
Bolton O
( O
1921 O
- O
2014 O
) O
, O
a O
retired O
teacher O
's O
assistant O
, O
spoke O
out O
at O
a O
town O
hall O
meeting O
in O
Natchitoches O
in O
2003 O
called O
by O
Foster O
Campbell O
, O
one O
of O
the O
five O
members O
of O
the O
Louisiana O
Public O
Service O
Commission O
. O

Kraft B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Natchitoches O
Parish O
, O
Louisiana O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Disney B-PERSON
executive O
produced O
" O
The O
Trials O
of O
Spring O
" O
( O
2015 O
) O
, O
which O
includes O
a O
feature O
- O
length O
documentary O
and O
six O
short O
films O
.. O

Their O
entry O
suggests O
the O
name O
" O
Bois O
Juba O
" O
is O
a O
probable O
clerical O
error O
for O
" O
Boz O
's O
Juba O
" O
, O
the O
sobriquet O
by O
which O
Juba B-PERSON
was O
best O
known O
in O
England O
. O

In O
total O
, O
Drumheller B-LOCATION
has O
absorbed O
at O
least O
13 O
other O
communities O
in O
its O
history O
, O
some O
of O
which O
are O
now O
recognized O
as O
neighbourhoods O
or O
districts O
within O
the O
town O
. O

Under O
his O
management O
, O
Dublin B-ORGANIZATION
contested O
the O
Leinster O
Final O
, O
but O
lost O
by O
2 O
goals O
to O
Kilkenny O
. O

Primary O
sources O
show O
that O
Juba B-PERSON
performed O
in O
dance O
competitions O
, O
minstrel O
shows O
, O
and O
variety O
theaters O
in O
the O
Northeastern O
United O
States O
beginning O
in O
the O
mid-1840s O
. O

Shrewsbury B-PERSON
finished O
the O
Test O
series O
with O
301 O
runs O
at O
50.16 O
and O
made O
£ O
150 O
from O
the O
tour O
, O
the O
figure O
reduced O
by O
the O
boycotting O
of O
several O
matches O
by O
the O
1884 O
Australians O
. O

Rosewater B-PERSON
has O
designed O
at O
least O
one O
card O
for O
every O
Magic O
expansion O
since O
" O
" O
. O

In O
2018 O
, O
Stryker B-PERSON
donated O
$ O
20 O
million O
to O
Kalamazoo O
College O
to O
establish O
a O
10-year O
scholarship O
program O
for O
students O
of O
color O
, O
first O
- O
generation O
students O
and O
those O
from O
lower O
- O
income O
families O
. O

Since O
leaving O
TSR O
, O
Wham B-PERSON
has O
designed O
many O
more O
games O
, O
including O
collaborating O
with O
James O
M. O
Ward O
on O
the O
board O
game O
" O
Dragon O
Lairds O
" O
, O
published O
in O
April O
2008 O
, O
and O
" O
Feudality O
" O
published O
by O
Z O
- O
man O
Games O
Inc. O
in O
2011 O
. O

In O
1993 O
Sunderland B-PERSON
began O
doing O
pre O
- O
game O
hosting O
for O
the O
Lakers O
. O

Holden B-LOCATION
was O
located O
from O
Melbourne O
; O
beyond O
Sydenham O
station O
and O
before O
Diggers O
Rest O
station O
, O
close O
to O
Holden O
Road O
. O

Ivanhoe B-LOCATION
or O
Ivanhoe O
Station O
is O
a O
pastoral O
lease O
and O
cattle O
station O
located O
just O
north O
of O
Kununurra O
in O
the O
Kimberley O
region O
of O
Western O
Australia O
. O

Among O
a O
number O
of O
villages O
specified O
in O
the O
document O
, O
there O
is O
Brzostek B-LOCATION
( O
spelled O
" O
Brestek O
" O
) O
. O

Renault B-PERSON
wrote O
many O
works O
on O
his O
activities O
in O
the O
Resistance O
. O

Albion B-PERSON
received O
his O
post O
- O
secondary O
degrees O
from O
Harvard O
University O
, O
including O
a O
BA O
in O
Economics O
, O
a O
joint O
MA O
/ O
MBA O
and O
a O
joint O
PhD O
/ O
DBA O
in O
Business O
Economics O
from O
Harvard O
University O
and O
Harvard O
Business O
School O
. O

Large O
queues O
of O
blind O
, O
crippled O
and O
sick O
beggars O
rushed O
to O
Marianka B-LOCATION
with O
their O
prayers O
to O
drink O
and O
wash O
themselves O
in O
the O
blessed O
stream O
. O

Aziziye B-LOCATION
lies O
in O
the O
western O
part O
of O
Erzurum O
at O
. O

The O
American O
Council O
of O
Trustees O
and O
Alumni O
later O
praised O
the O
work O
of O
Dragas B-PERSON
and O
the O
Board O
, O
stating O
that O
“ O
If O
students O
are O
to O
receive O
a O
quality O
and O
affordable O
education O
in O
Virginia O
, O
it O
is O
the O
trustees O
who O
are O
going O
to O
have O
to O
press O
for O
, O
measure O
, O
and O
demand O
results O
. O
" O

Cadbury B-PERSON
continued O
to O
develop O
the O
business O
, O
but O
also O
took O
a O
role O
in O
civil O
affairs O
. O

On O
July O
17 O
, O
2009 O
it O
was O
announced O
that O
Evidence B-PERSON
had O
signed O
a O
deal O
with O
Minneapolis O
- O
based O
hip O
- O
hop O
label O
Rhymesayers O
Entertainment O
, O
with O
a O
YouTube O
video O
showing O
Evidence O
signing O
the O
contract O
to O
release O
his O
next O
album O
. O

Carlisle B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Fayette O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Zenith B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Monroe O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Burnley B-LOCATION
has O
a O
small O
gay O
scene O
, O
centred O
on O
the O
Guys O
as O
Dolls O
showbar O
in O
St O
James O
Street O
. O

Stanmore B-LOCATION
was O
a O
parliamentary O
electorate O
in O
Christchurch O
, O
New O
Zealand O
from O
1881 O
to O
1887 O
. O

According O
to O
MLB.com O
, O
Humber B-PERSON
received O
a O
combined O
$ O
3.7 O
million O
signing O
bonus O
and O
contract O
from O
the O
Mets O
. O

Bud B-LOCATION
is O
a O
fishing O
village O
in O
Hustadvika O
Municipality O
in O
Møre O
og O
Romsdal O
county O
in O
western O
Norway O
. O

In O
2005 O
, O
Force B-PERSON
won O
5 O
events O
, O
but O
only O
finished O
third O
in O
the O
championship O
standings O
, O
32 O
points O
behind O
champion O
Gary O
Scelzi O
, O
and O
24 O
points O
behind O
Ron O
Capps O
, O
both O
of O
Don O
Schumacher O
Racing O
[ O
DSR O
] O
. O

Croker B-PERSON
owned O
many O
shares O
of O
the O
New O
York O
Auto O
- O
Truck O
Company O
, O
a O
company O
which O
would O
have O
benefited O
from O
the O
arrangement O
. O

Congress B-PERSON
was O
on O
the O
ballot O
in O
Ohio O
, O
where O
he O
received O
4,029 O
votes O
. O

Nor O
is O
it O
at O
all O
clear O
, O
for O
lack O
of O
any O
proof O
, O
that O
the O
lore O
handed O
down O
in O
the O
village O
itself O
about O
the O
village O
’s O
founding O
has O
any O
truth O
to O
it O
; O
this O
would O
have O
the O
listener O
believe O
that O
Grumbach B-LOCATION
was O
founded O
by O
the O
Knights O
Templar O
. O

In O
September O
2019 O
, O
Valencia B-PERSON
obtained O
Israeli O
citizenship O
and O
joined O
Team O
Israel O
for O
the O
2019 O
European O
Baseball O
Championship O
in O
Germany O
from O
September O
7–15 O
, O
2019 O
. O

Some O
channels O
on O
the O
Swedish O
DTT O
are O
free O
- O
to O
- O
air O
, O
but O
most O
of O
the O
channels O
require O
subscription O
from O
Boxer B-ORGANIZATION
. O

Somerset B-LOCATION
is O
located O
on O
County O
Highway O
5 O
southeast O
of O
Harrisburg O
. O

Göksu B-PERSON
became O
international O
playing O
for O
the O
Turkey O
Girls O
' O
U-15 O
national O
team O
in O
the O
2010 O
Summer O
Youth O
Olympics O
qualifying O
round O
match O
against O
Georgia O
on O
October O
12 O
, O
2009 O
. O

Sussex B-LOCATION
is O
located O
in O
south O
central O
New O
Brunswick O
, O
between O
the O
province O
's O
three O
largest O
cities O
, O
Saint O
John O
, O
Moncton O
, O
and O
Fredericton O
. O

Ramin B-LOCATION
is O
a O
municipality O
in O
the O
Vorpommern O
- O
Greifswald O
district O
, O
in O
Mecklenburg O
- O
Vorpommern O
, O
Germany O
. O

Today O
, O
Leeds B-LOCATION
is O
home O
to O
the O
Northampton O
Veterans O
Affairs O
Medical O
Center O
, O
and O
Chartpak O
, O
manufacturer O
of O
art O
and O
graphics O
supplies O
, O
which O
includes O
Koh O
- O
i O
- O
Noor O
Hardtmuth O
. O

Milan B-LOCATION
is O
east O
- O
northeast O
of O
Abbotsford O
. O

Following O
the O
1938 O
Anschluss O
, O
Marburg B-PERSON
was O
forced O
to O
emigrate O
to O
the O
United O
States O
as O
a O
refugee O
. O

Toulouse B-PERSON
joined O
the O
Microsoft O
Security O
Response O
Center O
( O
MSRC O
) O
in O
November O
2002 O
. O

After O
injury O
problems O
restricted O
his O
1973 O
season O
, O
for O
the O
next O
three O
years O
Knights B-PERSON
was O
rated O
the O
best O
centre O
half O
- O
back O
in O
the O
game O
. O

During O
the O
2015 O
season O
, O
Thames B-PERSON
became O
the O
first O
player O
in O
KBO O
history O
to O
hit O
for O
the O
cycle O
twice O
in O
one O
season O
. O

The O
Mets O
selected O
Humber B-PERSON
with O
the O
third O
overall O
selection O
in O
the O
2004 O
MLB O
draft O
. O

Voss B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
El O
Dorado O
County O
, O
California O
. O

In O
1967 O
, O
McCulloch B-ORGANIZATION
discontinued O
its O
line O
of O
outboard O
boat O
engines O
which O
it O
began O
after O
the O
1956 O
purchase O
of O
Scott O
- O
Atwater O
Manufacturing O
Company O
of O
Minneapolis O
, O
Minnesota O
- O
the O
manufacturer O
of O
Scott O
- O
Atwater O
outboard O
boat O
engines O
. O

Prior O
to O
the O
Plantations O
of O
Ireland O
, O
Ballyboy B-LOCATION
was O
ruled O
by O
O'Molloy O
in O
a O
territory O
known O
as O
Firceall O
which O
was O
allied O
to O
the O
Kingdom O
of O
Meath O
. O

In O
1956 O
, O
Mack O
Trucks O
bought O
Beck B-ORGANIZATION
and O
closed O
it O
in O
1958 O
. O

Ellis B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Gage O
County O
, O
Nebraska O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

Rustenburg B-ORGANIZATION
was O
founded O
in O
1894 O
and O
divided O
into O
Junior O
and O
High O
Schools O
in O
1932 O
. O

In O
1996 O
, O
Valencia B-PERSON
pitched O
for O
the O
Boca O
Raton O
Babe O
Ruth O
League O
12-and O
- O
under O
all O
- O
star O
baseball O
team O
that O
won O
the O
Florida O
state O
championship O
. O

While O
players O
from O
Fingal O
are O
eligible O
for O
the O
main O
Dublin B-ORGANIZATION
team O
, O
non O
- O
Fingal O
players O
can O
not O
play O
for O
Fingal O
. O

The O
horse O
racing O
club O
, O
the O
Wimmera O
Racing O
Club O
, O
schedules O
around O
six O
race O
meetings O
a O
year O
at O
Donald B-LOCATION
including O
the O
Donald O
Cup O
meeting O
in O
November O
. O

On O
March O
9 O
, O
Sky B-PERSON
was O
part O
of O
an O
infamous O
triple O
threat O
match O
which O
included O
Brittney O
Savage O
and O
Spyra O
Andover O
and O
was O
mentioned O
by O
Botchamania O
. O

According O
to O
Pappus O
, O
Carpus B-PERSON
made O
use O
of O
mathematics O
for O
practical O
applications O
. O

Kovar B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Bastrop O
County O
, O
Texas O
, O
United O
States O
. O

In O
1832 O
the O
constituency O
was O
divided O
between O
the O
new O
constituencies O
of O
Aberdeen B-LOCATION
and O
Montrose O
Burghs O
. O

From O
1841 O
until O
1871 O
, O
Lazenby B-LOCATION
had O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
Middlesbrough O
to O
Redcar O
line O
. O

The O
school O
has O
distributed O
hundreds O
of O
waste O
compost O
units O
, O
teaching O
people O
to O
segregate O
waste O
, O
and O
the O
students O
of O
Pallikoodam B-ORGANIZATION
have O
often O
cleaned O
up O
the O
nearby O
Kalathipady O
road O
, O
Karipal O
Hospital O
area O
. O

Jasper B-LOCATION
was O
the O
site O
of O
a O
siding O
of O
the O
Southern O
Pacific O
Railroad O
's O
Cascade O
Line O
( O
now O
part O
of O
the O
Union O
Pacific O
Railroad O
) O
, O
which O
was O
named O
for O
local O
resident O
Jasper O
B. O
Hills O
, O
the O
son O
of O
Cornelius O
Joel O
Hills O
, O
who O
settled O
at O
the O
locale O
in O
1846 O
. O

In O
the O
, O
Albion B-LOCATION
had O
a O
population O
of O
2,296 O
people O
. O

Sirius B-PERSON
recruited O
Timothy O
Leary O
to O
be O
a O
contributing O
editor O
for O
" O
Mondo O
2000 O
" O
and O
has O
taught O
an O
online O
course O
in O
Leary O
's O
philosophy O
for O
the O
Maybe O
Logic O
Academy O
. O

According O
to O
the O
Bank O
of O
Montreal O
's O
fourth O
quarter O
2018 O
report O
, O
Guelph B-LOCATION
was O
the O
leading O
city O
in O
Canada O
in O
terms O
of O
job O
growth O
and O
low O
unemployment O
. O

Aston B-LOCATION
has O
one O
of O
the O
highest O
rates O
of O
unemployment O
in O
the O
city O
, O
with O
57.8 O
% O
of O
residents O
classed O
as O
economically O
active O
compared O
to O
the O
city O
average O
of O
69.3 O
% O
and O
national O
average O
of O
77 O
% O
. O

Chenab B-ORGANIZATION
is O
also O
equipped O
with O
a O
stitching O
unit O
for O
ready O
- O
made O
garments O
. O

As O
with O
most O
of O
the O
British O
Isles O
, O
Forfar B-LOCATION
has O
an O
oceanic O
climate O
( O
Köppen O
: O
" O
Cfb O
" O
) O
. O

Silex B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Martin O
Township O
, O
Pope O
County O
, O
Arkansas O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Caerphilly B-LOCATION
hosted O
the O
National O
Eisteddfod O
in O
1950 O
. O

Order O
book O
value O
aside O
, O
it O
was O
also O
said O
in O
Parliament O
that O
Churchill B-ORGANIZATION
had O
lost O
over O
£ O
1 O
M O
in O
the O
previous O
two O
years O
. O

Hunter B-ORGANIZATION
was O
an O
all O
- O
girls O
school O
for O
its O
first O
105 O
years O
, O
with O
the O
official O
name O
" O
Hunter O
College O
High O
School O
for O
Intellectually O
Gifted O
Young O
Ladies O
" O
. O

Shrewsbury B-PERSON
topped O
the O
domestic O
batting O
averages O
. O

Perceval O
throws O
Excalibur B-PERSON
into O
the O
pool O
, O
where O
the O
Lady O
of O
the O
Lake O
catches O
it O
. O

Jericho B-PERSON
intervenes O
and O
threats O
Ra O
's O
al O
Ghul O
to O
stop O
or O
he O
'll O
kill O
everyone O
with O
a O
psychic O
blast O
. O

In O
1892 O
Shrewsbury B-PERSON
scored O
his O
tenth O
and O
final O
double O
century O
during O
a O
match O
against O
Middlesex O
. O

She O
was O
born O
Texas O
Anna O
Smith O
, O
in O
Rich O
Valley O
, O
Smyth O
County O
, O
Virginia O
, O
the O
daughter O
of O
Alexander O
King O
Smith O
and O
his O
wife O
Sarah O
Louvenia O
( O
née O
Hammonds O
) O
; O
the O
name O
Texas B-PERSON
was O
taken O
from O
that O
of O
an O
aunt O
. O

Planning O
for O
such O
a O
place O
began O
in O
1959 O
, O
under O
the O
leadership O
of O
Wynne B-PERSON
and O
the O
Great O
Southwest O
Corporation O
, O
along O
with O
the O
backing O
of O
various O
New O
York O
City O
investors O
. O

A O
post O
office O
called O
Perkins B-LOCATION
has O
been O
in O
operation O
since O
1890 O
. O

Lyons B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Burleson O
County O
, O
Texas O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Otto B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Macon O
County O
, O
North O
Carolina O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Blackburn B-LOCATION
is O
a O
rapidly O
growing O
commuter O
town O
northwest O
of O
Aberdeen O
, O
Scotland O
, O
and O
is O
situated O
in O
Aberdeenshire O
. O

Hunter B-ORGANIZATION
was O
started O
in O
1973 O
in O
Alachua O
, O
Florida O
, O
as O
a O
sailboat O
manufacturer O
. O

Fischer B-ORGANIZATION
was O
a O
brewery O
in O
Schiltigheim O
, O
France O
. O

Kirk B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Mingo O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Following O
law O
school O
, O
Oman B-PERSON
served O
as O
law O
clerk O
to O
C. O
Stanley O
Blair O
, O
U.S. O
District O
Court O
Judge O
for O
the O
District O
of O
Maryland O
. O

On O
15 O
March O
1928 O
, O
Opel B-PERSON
tested O
his O
first O
rocket O
- O
powered O
car O
, O
the O
RAK.1 O
, O
and O
achieved O
a O
top O
speed O
of O
75 O
km O
/ O
h O
( O
47 O
mph O
) O
in O
it O
, O
proving O
the O
feasibility O
of O
the O
concept O
of O
rocket O
propulsion O
. O

In O
November O
2004 O
, O
union O
supporters O
gathered O
outside O
Nova O
's O
Shinjuku O
Honko O
school O
, O
protesting O
dismissals O
of O
five O
teachers O
, O
three O
of O
whom O
had O
been O
working O
at O
Nova B-ORGANIZATION
for O
more O
than O
10 O
years O
. O

Villarreal B-PERSON
finished O
the O
season O
with O
2 O
wins O
and O
no O
losses O
, O
5 O
strikeouts O
, O
and O
a O
5.27 O
earned O
run O
average O
. O

If O
the O
Zero B-ORGANIZATION
followed O
his O
original O
target O
through O
the O
turn O
, O
he O
would O
come O
into O
a O
position O
to O
be O
fired O
on O
by O
the O
target O
's O
wingman O
. O

Buron B-LOCATION
was O
the O
site O
of O
two O
major O
battles O
, O
one O
on O
June O
7 O
, O
1944 O
, O
and O
another O
during O
Operation O
Charnwood O
on O
July O
8 O
, O
1944 O
when O
the O
Highland O
Light O
Infantry O
of O
Canada O
liberated O
the O
town O
from O
defending O
elements O
of O
the O
12th O
SS O
Panzer O
Division O
. O

Lorient B-PERSON
has O
most O
notably O
served O
as O
a O
springboard O
club O
for O
several O
present O
- O
day O
internationals O
such O
as O
Laurent O
Koscielny O
, O
André O
- O
Pierre O
Gignac O
, O
Michaël O
Ciani O
, O
Kevin O
Gameiro O
, O
Karim O
Ziani O
, O
Bakari O
Koné O
, O
Matteo O
Guendouzi O
, O
and O
Seydou O
Keita O
. O

Peckham O
is O
buried O
in O
the O
Peckham B-PERSON
family O
plot O
at O
Albany O
Rural O
Cemetery O
, O
along O
with O
his O
wife O
, O
Annie O
Aertsen O
Keasbey O
( O
1826 O
, O
Salem O
, O
New O
Jersey O
– O
October O
30 O
, O
1916 O
) O
, O
whom O
he O
married O
in O
1855 O
. O

The O
minor O
River O
Redlake O
passes O
Jay B-LOCATION
and O
then O
joins O
the O
Clun O
just O
south O
of O
Jay O
Bridge O
. O

Lari B-LOCATION
is O
further O
divided O
into O
5 O
Wards O
: O
Lari O
/ O
Kirenga O
, O
Kijabe O
, O
Kamburu O
- O
Kamuchege O
, O
Kinale O
and O
Nyanduma O
Wards O
. O

In O
2011 O
, O
literacy O
rate O
of O
Kalla B-LOCATION
village O
was O
71.47 O
% O
compared O
to O
67.02 O
% O
of O
Andhra O
Pradesh O
. O

Stoa B-PERSON
finished O
the O
season O
scoring O
40 O
points O
with O
the O
Monsters O
, O
co O
- O
leading O
the O
AHL O
with O
23 O
goals O
among O
rookies O
. O

Macula B-PERSON
played O
six O
Série O
A O
games O
for O
Remo O
in O
1994 O
, O
and O
seven O
Série O
A O
games O
for O
Bahia O
in O
1995 O
. O

Clients O
included O
law O
firms O
like O
Skadden O
, O
Arps O
and O
investment O
banks O
like O
Drexel O
Burnham O
Lambert O
( O
which O
hired O
Kroll B-PERSON
in O
1982 O
to O
perform O
due O
diligence O
on O
persons O
and O
companies O
that O
it O
was O
underwriting O
) O
. O

Stryker B-PERSON
also O
serves O
on O
the O
Advisory O
Council O
of O
METI O
( O
Messaging O
Extraterrestrial O
Intelligence O
) O
. O

Bogdan O
- O
Piteşti O
declared O
Vermont B-PERSON
" O
one O
of O
the O
most O
accomplished O
" O
among O
Romanian O
painters O
, O
and O
bought O
many O
of O
his O
works O
. O

Humphrey B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Wood O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
. O

In O
the O
early O
18th O
century O
, O
the O
Angel B-LOCATION
was O
the O
largest O
coaching O
house O
in O
a O
row O
of O
several O
along O
Islington O
High O
Street O
. O

Maggie B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
west O
- O
central O
Craig O
County O
, O
Virginia O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Gamaliel B-ORGANIZATION
also O
conducts O
numerous O
half O
- O
day O
, O
full O
- O
day O
, O
and O
weekend O
trainings O
for O
local O
communities O
. O

Azalea B-LOCATION
is O
the O
hometown O
of O
decathlete O
and O
Olympian O
Tom O
Pappas O
. O

The O
dispute O
over O
Sonnenberg B-LOCATION
was O
settled O
by O
a O
treaty O
in O
1221 O
, O
in O
which O
Nassau O
obtained O
the O
land O
on O
which O
the O
castle O
is O
built O
as O
a O
fief O
for O
30 O
Marks O
. O

Pollok B-ORGANIZATION
were O
reigning O
champions O
of O
the O
West O
Premier O
League O
at O
the O
time O
, O
and O
took O
part O
in O
the O
2007–08 O
Scottish O
Cup O
. O

After O
struggling O
to O
regain O
lost O
market O
share O
, O
Carpenter B-ORGANIZATION
was O
closed O
by O
Spartan O
in O
early O
2001 O
. O

Some O
students O
were O
able O
to O
finish O
their O
programs O
elsewhere O
when O
Holden B-ORGANIZATION
was O
shut O
down O
, O
although O
there O
was O
concern O
about O
the O
ability O
to O
transfer O
credits O
. O

Kirkpatrick B-LOCATION
is O
the O
location O
of O
the O
Scott O
Township O
Hall O
. O

Fischer B-ORGANIZATION
produced O
Desperados O
, O
a O
pale O
lager O
flavored O
with O
tequila O
. O

The O
journal O
also O
published O
a O
review O
of O
" O
The O
Emperor O
of O
Scent O
" O
, O
calling O
Chandler O
Burr O
's O
book O
about O
Turin B-PERSON
and O
his O
theory O
" O
giddy O
and O
overwrought O
. O
" O

Shrewsbury B-PERSON
top O
scored O
with O
44 O
in O
a O
low O
- O
scoring O
match O
which O
England O
won O
. O

Emery O
was O
originally O
from O
Boston O
, O
and O
around O
1900 O
he O
wrote O
to O
Harvard O
University O
to O
ask O
permission O
to O
use O
the O
Harvard B-ORGANIZATION
name O
for O
his O
new O
secondary O
school O
, O
and O
received O
permission O
from O
the O
university O
's O
then O
- O
President O
, O
Charles O
W. O
Eliot O
. O

The O
following O
day O
, O
Goma B-PERSON
was O
interviewed O
on O
Channel O
4 O
's O
T4 O
block O
about O
his O
experience O
. O

Dancer O
Mark O
Knowles O
has O
echoed O
this O
assertion O
, O
calling O
Juba B-PERSON
" O
America O
's O
first O
real O
tap O
dancer O
" O
. O

On O
10 O
February O
2011 O
, O
Oman B-PERSON
joined O
Shamrock O
Rovers O
. O

Villarreal B-PERSON
missed O
most O
of O
due O
to O
a O
sore O
elbow O
, O
and O
later O
elbow O
surgery O
. O

In O
1982 O
, O
Genie B-ORGANIZATION
moved O
its O
headquarters O
to O
Redmond O
, O
Washington O
. O

Carman B-LOCATION
was O
a O
provincial O
electoral O
division O
in O
the O
Canadian O
province O
of O
Manitoba O
. O

Juba B-PERSON
made O
another O
unexpected O
foray O
into O
electoral O
politics O
in O
the O
provincial O
election O
of O
1981 O
, O
running O
as O
an O
independent O
candidate O
in O
his O
old O
riding O
of O
Logan O
. O

Buckinghamshire B-LOCATION
is O
notable O
for O
its O
open O
countryside O
and O
natural O
features O
, O
including O
the O
Chiltern O
Hills O
Area O
of O
Outstanding O
Natural O
Beauty O
, O
Stowe O
Landscaped O
Gardens O
near O
Buckingham O
, O
and O
the O
River O
Thames O
. O

In O
2009 O
, O
former O
Clare O
manager O
, O
Anthony O
Daly O
was O
appointed O
manager O
of O
Dublin B-ORGANIZATION
. O

Torun B-PERSON
has O
been O
praised O
for O
her O
ability O
to O
shape O
solid O
materials O
into O
seemingly O
flexible O
forms O
, O
so O
that O
metal O
flows O
like O
water O
around O
the O
wearer O
's O
neck O
and O
shoulders O
. O

Chicago B-ORGANIZATION
also O
signed O
FB O
/ O
LB O
Bob O
McMillen O
, O
who O
would O
play O
with O
the O
team O
until O
2007 O
and O
became O
the O
Rush O
's O
head O
coach O
in O
2011 O
. O

Tao B-LOCATION
is O
a O
commune O
in O
the O
Cercle O
of O
Koutiala O
in O
the O
Sikasso O
Region O
of O
southern O
Mali O
. O

Sunderland B-PERSON
escaped O
in O
disguise O
to O
Rotterdam O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
, O
where O
he O
lay O
low O
for O
some O
time O
, O
before O
being O
officially O
arrested O
, O
and O
immediately O
released O
, O
by O
the O
Dutch O
authorities O
. O

Braithwaite B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Plaquemines O
Parish O
, O
Louisiana O
, O
United O
States O
. O

In O
a O
tradition O
thought O
to O
date O
back O
to O
at O
least O
the O
13th O
century O
, O
once O
a O
year O
on O
the O
Tuesday O
after O
Easter O
, O
called O
" O
Sembley O
Tuesday O
" O
the O
freeholders O
of O
the O
town O
were O
required O
to O
assemble O
on O
the O
Wicker B-LOCATION
with O
their O
horses O
and O
arms O
before O
the O
Lord O
of O
the O
Manor O
. O

Cagliari O
remained O
Roman O
Catholic O
despite O
the O
Arianism O
prevalent O
at O
the O
time O
and O
many O
African O
bishops O
fled O
the O
Arian O
Vandals O
to O
come O
to O
Cagliari B-LOCATION
. O

In O
various O
places O
in O
Friesland O
, O
patriots O
called O
for O
civilians O
and O
soldiers O
to O
liberate O
Lemmer B-LOCATION
. O

Ringo B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Crawford O
County O
, O
Kansas O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

The O
Waikato B-ORGANIZATION
mascot O
is O
a O
cow O
called O
Mooloo O
. O

The O
Rhode O
Island O
Reds O
, O
a O
charter O
member O
of O
the O
AHL O
, O
moved O
to O
Binghamton B-ORGANIZATION
in O
1977 O
and O
played O
there O
until O
1997 O
, O
known O
variously O
as O
the O
Binghamton O
Dusters O
( O
1977–1980 O
) O
, O
the O
Binghamton O
Whalers O
( O
1980–1990 O
) O
, O
and O
the O
Binghamton O
Rangers O
( O
1990–1997 O
) O
. O

Kansas B-PERSON
is O
an O
American O
rock O
band O
that O
became O
popular O
in O
the O
1970s O
initially O
on O
album O
- O
oriented O
rock O
charts O
and O
later O
with O
hit O
singles O
such O
as O
" O
Carry O
On O
Wayward O
Son O
" O
and O
" O
Dust O
in O
the O
Wind O
" O
. O

In O
September O
2004 O
, O
Braeburn B-ORGANIZATION
took O
over O
the O
management O
of O
Mombasa O
International O
School O
, O
based O
in O
Shanzu O
, O
north O
of O
Mombasa O
. O

Ford O
is O
a O
Metropolitan O
Borough O
of O
Sefton O
ward O
in O
the O
Bootle O
Parliamentary O
constituency O
that O
covers O
the O
northern O
part O
of O
the O
locality O
of O
Litherland O
and O
all O
of O
Ford B-LOCATION
. O

Elvira B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Clinton O
County O
, O
Iowa O
, O
United O
States O
. O

The O
following O
season O
was O
in O
complete O
contrast O
, O
as O
Shrewsbury B-PERSON
scored O
seven O
fifties O
and O
no O
century O
, O
reaching O
1,000 O
runs O
in O
a O
season O
for O
the O
first O
time O
. O

The O
Houston O
Astros O
claimed O
Humber B-PERSON
off O
waivers O
on O
November O
30 O
, O
2012 O
. O

Hindustan B-LOCATION
was O
platted O
in O
August O
18 O
, O
1853 O
by O
Charles O
G. O
Carr O
. O

Hexham B-PERSON
was O
in O
early O
youth O
attached O
as O
a O
page O
to O
the O
service O
of O
Sir O
Francis O
Vere O
; O
he O
was O
with O
Vere O
throughout O
the O
siege O
of O
Ostend O
in O
1601 O
, O
and O
his O
narrative O
of O
that O
event O
is O
printed O
at O
the O
end O
of O
Sir O
Francis O
Vere O
's O
" O
Commentaries O
" O
( O
1657 O
) O
. O

In O
the O
early O
years O
of O
federation O
the O
seat O
consisted O
of O
little O
more O
than O
Bendigo B-LOCATION
itself O
, O
but O
on O
later O
boundaries O
the O
seat O
has O
included O
towns O
such O
as O
Echuca O
, O
Castlemaine O
, O
Maryborough O
and O
Seymour O
. O

Helin B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
administrative O
district O
of O
Gmina O
Bielawy O
, O
within O
Łowicz O
County O
, O
Łódź O
Voivodeship O
, O
in O
central O
Poland O
. O

Schlegel B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
and O
a O
former O
municipality O
in O
the O
district O
Saale O
- O
Orla O
- O
Kreis O
, O
in O
Thuringia O
, O
Germany O
. O

On O
the O
night O
of O
the O
verdict O
, O
Amsterdam B-PERSON
was O
accosted O
by O
plainclothes O
security O
agents O
in O
the O
middle O
of O
the O
night O
at O
his O
hotel O
room O
, O
who O
attempted O
to O
arrest O
him O
before O
he O
could O
call O
his O
colleagues O
in O
the O
media O
. O

In O
about O
1952 O
Harbin B-PERSON
appeared O
in O
a O
minor O
part O
as O
a O
magician O
in O
the O
film O
" O
The O
Limping O
Man O
" O
, O
produced O
by O
Cy O
Endfield O
. O

As O
well O
as O
the O
town O
's O
Country O
Park O
, O
The O
North O
Lanarkshire O
Heritage O
Centre O
, O
formerly O
the O
Motherwell O
Heritage O
Centre O
on O
High O
Road O
, O
situated O
next O
to O
the O
town O
's O
railway O
station O
, O
is O
a O
building O
that O
displays O
the O
history O
of O
Motherwell B-LOCATION
from O
the O
Roman O
era O
. O

Like O
most O
mountain O
communities O
, O
Cosby B-LOCATION
was O
subject O
to O
raids O
throughout O
the O
war O
, O
especially O
from O
Confederate O
marauders O
crossing O
the O
mountains O
from O
North O
Carolina O
. O

In O
September O
2004 O
, O
Renfrew B-LOCATION
experienced O
massive O
flooding O
due O
to O
rainfall O
caused O
by O
the O
remnants O
of O
Hurricane O
Ivan O
. O

On O
October O
31 O
, O
2016 O
, O
Watford B-PERSON
was O
reacquired O
by O
the O
Fort O
Wayne O
Mad O
Ants O
. O

Gülek B-LOCATION
was O
a O
village O
in O
the O
first O
half O
of O
the O
20th O
century O
. O

Interstate O
80 O
exit O
49 O
provides O
access O
to O
Clive B-LOCATION
. O

Julia B-LOCATION
is O
a O
village O
in O
the O
administrative O
district O
of O
Gmina O
Ślesin O
, O
within O
Konin O
County O
, O
Greater O
Poland O
Voivodeship O
, O
in O
west O
- O
central O
Poland O
. O

In O
the O
initial O
days O
after O
the O
launch O
, O
the O
newspaper O
did O
not O
find O
favour O
with O
the O
government O
, O
but O
TVR B-PERSON
persisted O
. O

Cunningham B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Hardy O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Oman B-PERSON
made O
his O
first O
start O
on O
14 O
March O
2015 O
against O
Dungannon O
Swifts O
and O
was O
yellow O
carded O
for O
a O
challenge O
on O
Jamie O
Glackin O
. O

After O
his O
release O
from O
Portsmouth O
, O
Berlin B-PERSON
signed O
for O
Crawley O
Town O
on O
a O
short O
- O
term O
deal O
from O
Portsmouth O
in O
November O
2007 O
, O
lasting O
less O
than O
a O
month O
before O
being O
allowed O
to O
move O
on O
. O

Yasuda B-LOCATION
is O
on O
the O
Gomen O
- O
Nahari O
train O
line O
, O
third O
stop O
from O
the O
last O
heading O
east O
. O

Carpenter B-LOCATION
is O
a O
small O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Copiah O
County O
, O
Mississippi O
, O
United O
States O
. O

Located O
in O
the O
Shasta O
Cascade O
area O
of O
Northern O
California O
, O
Castella B-LOCATION
sees O
many O
visitors O
and O
has O
a O
number O
of O
summer O
homes O
in O
the O
area O
. O

Jordan B-ORGANIZATION
was O
itself O
acquired O
by O
the O
Orkla O
Group O
in O
2012 O
. O

He O
made O
the O
acquaintance O
of O
George O
I O
in O
1706 O
, O
but O
when O
the O
elector O
became O
king O
, O
Sunderland B-PERSON
only O
secured O
the O
comparatively O
unimportant O
position O
of O
Lord O
Lieutenant O
of O
Ireland O
. O

In O
2018/19 O
, O
the O
Bison B-ORGANIZATION
had O
a O
major O
squad O
rebuild O
, O
with O
just O
7 O
players O
remaining O
at O
the O
club O
from O
the O
previous O
season O
. O

After O
the O
merger O
, O
CSR O
executed O
substantial O
layoffs O
involving O
former O
Zoran B-ORGANIZATION
employees O
. O

During O
his O
time O
as O
a O
co O
- O
host O
of O
the O
Xbox O
podcast O
" O
Major O
Nelson O
Radio O
, O
" O
Toulouse B-PERSON
was O
the O
public O
face O
for O
the O
rules O
governing O
behavior O
on O
the O
Xbox O
Live O
service O
and O
often O
explained O
and O
clarified O
policies O
. O

Vinje B-LOCATION
became O
a O
site O
of O
heavy O
battles O
during O
World O
War O
II O
, O
at O
the O
Battle O
of O
Vinjesvingen O
when O
Norwegian O
forces O
held O
out O
for O
over O
a O
month O
against O
superior O
German O
forces O
. O

Patagonia B-ORGANIZATION
considers O
itself O
an O
" O
activist O
company O
" O
. O

Valencia B-PERSON
batted O
.371 O
vs. O
left O
- O
handed O
pitching O
, O
leading O
the O
American O
League O
, O
and O
ranked O
third O
in O
slugging O
percentage O
at O
.639 O
( O
minimum O
100 O
plate O
appearances O
) O
. O

Since O
Buckley B-LOCATION
is O
located O
approximately O
above O
sea O
level O
, O
snowfall O
is O
more O
frequent O
in O
winter O
months O
in O
comparison O
to O
the O
lower O
lying O
ground O
in O
neighbouring O
areas O
. O

Barber B-LOCATION
is O
a O
town O
in O
the O
north O
of O
the O
island O
of O
Curaçao O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
Antilles O
. O

On O
12 O
January O
2018 O
, O
Fano B-ORGANIZATION
introduced O
the O
Standard O
Series O
bass O
guitar O
, O
JM4-FB O
. O

Everytime O
a O
team O
wins O
an O
event O
, O
they O
are O
awarded O
money O
toward O
a O
charity O
of O
their O
team O
's O
choice O
, O
which O
will O
be O
one O
of O
three O
provided O
by O
Wagner B-ORGANIZATION
leadership O
. O

Chloe B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Calhoun O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
, O
United O
States O
. O

In O
August O
1999 O
, O
the O
area O
around O
Barak B-LOCATION
was O
occupied O
by O
Uzbekistan O
, O
cutting O
it O
off O
from O
Kyrgyz O
territory O
. O

Municipally O
, O
Sutherland B-LOCATION
lies O
within O
Ward O
1 O
, O
currently O
represented O
by O
Darren O
Hill O
who O
was O
first O
elected O
in O
2006 O
. O

Dewsbury B-PERSON
studied O
both O
scripture O
and O
other O
religious O
texts O
from O
an O
early O
age O
. O

Hoya B-ORGANIZATION
acquired O
the O
camera O
company O
Pentax O
in O
2007 O
, O
for O
the O
price O
of O
US$ O
1 O
billion O
, O
about O
10 O
% O
more O
than O
Pentax O
was O
valued O
at O
the O
time O
. O

2000 O
saw O
Headland B-PERSON
only O
play O
2 O
games O
in O
the O
first O
half O
of O
the O
season O
, O
but O
he O
ended O
up O
playing O
9 O
games O
including O
both O
of O
Brisbane O
's O
final O
round O
games O
. O

The O
earliest O
mention O
of O
the O
village O
is O
in O
the O
Domesday O
Book O
of O
1086 O
, O
when O
Whitstone B-LOCATION
was O
called O
' O
Witestan O
' O
, O
and O
was O
held O
by O
Ralph O
from O
the O
Count O
of O
Mortain O
. O

In O
February O
2019 O
, O
Twist O
and O
Pulse B-PERSON
made O
up O
part O
of O
a O
team O
on O
ITV1 O
's O
" O
Tenable O
" O
. O

Plymouth B-LOCATION
was O
an O
early O
settlement O
in O
Mississippi O
in O
present O
- O
day O
Lowndes O
County O
. O

Republic B-ORGANIZATION
was O
merged O
into O
Sports O
Direct O
's O
USC O
brand O
. O

Juba B-PERSON
seems O
to O
have O
presented O
varied O
styles O
at O
different O
tempos O
during O
a O
single O
performance O
. O

With O
the O
closure O
of O
the O
post O
office O
mail O
operations O
from O
Bowmanville O
set O
up O
Courtice O
's O
mail O
delivery O
on O
RR2 O
and O
RR3 O
Bowmanville O
and O
later O
an O
RR6 O
was O
established O
as O
Courtice B-LOCATION
grew O
. O

Bromwich B-PERSON
played O
in O
the O
Storm O
's O
under-20s O
24 O
- O
22 O
grand O
final O
win O
over O
the O
West O
Tigers O
. O

Israel O
sought O
to O
establish O
security O
settlements O
along O
its O
borders O
, O
and O
Eyal B-LOCATION
was O
established O
on O
what O
was O
then O
the O
Jordanian O
border O
. O

Less O
happily O
, O
Juba B-PERSON
reinforced O
the O
racist O
caricature O
of O
the O
naturally O
musical O
black O
among O
white O
audiences O
. O

December O
2016 O
saw O
Pegasus B-PERSON
create O
a O
depiction O
of O
Charlie O
Chaplin O
with O
the O
message O
" O
Dream O
Big O
" O
in O
the O
Cheshire O
town O
of O
Congleton O
, O
which O
is O
visible O
in O
the O
town O
's O
Swan O
Bank O
. O

The O
works O
attributed O
to O
Polyaenus B-PERSON
include O
: O

Peterborough B-LOCATION
was O
also O
home O
to O
the O
short O
- O
lived O
newspaper O
, O
" O
Petersburg O
Enterprise O
and O
Northern O
Advocate O
" O
( O
20 O
January O
- O
2 O
August O
1912 O
) O
, O
which O
was O
printed O
by O
William O
John O
Myers O
and O
Walter O
A. O
Wade O
. O

Hampshire B-PERSON
has O
been O
active O
on O
the O
stage O
, O
taking O
the O
lead O
roles O
in O
many O
leading O
plays O
. O

Middlesex B-LOCATION
was O
a O
constituency O
of O
the O
House O
of O
Commons O
of O
the O
Parliament O
of O
England O
, O
then O
of O
the O
Parliament O
of O
Great O
Britain O
from O
1707 O
to O
1800 O
, O
then O
of O
the O
Parliament O
of O
the O
United O
Kingdom O
from O
1801 O
until O
abolished O
in O
1885 O
. O

In O
1821 O
, O
the O
municipality O
of O
Pol O
en O
Panheel O
, O
covering O
the O
village O
of O
Panheel O
and O
the O
hamlet O
Pol O
, O
merged O
with O
Heel B-LOCATION
to O
form O
a O
municipality O
called O
Heel O
en O
Panheel O
. O

Regarding O
Surakiart O
's O
road O
map O
for O
reconciliation O
with O
Myanmar O
, O
Asda B-PERSON
noted O
that O
" O
It O
was O
clear O
to O
diplomats O
, O
even O
junior O
officers O
, O
at O
the O
Foreign O
Ministry O
that O
the O
Thai O
road O
map O
was O
doomed O
from O
the O
very O
beginning O
" O
. O

Antony B-LOCATION
is O
a O
station O
of O
the O
Paris O
RER O
. O

Many O
students O
from O
Buckley B-LOCATION
also O
attend O
Argoed O
High O
School O
, O
located O
in O
nearby O
Bryn O
- O
y O
- O
Baal O
, O
or O
the O
Alun O
School O
, O
in O
Mold O
. O

Lorient B-PERSON
was O
defeated O
by O
Bordeaux O
in O
the O
final O
. O

Around O
the O
turn O
of O
the O
20th O
century O
, O
over O
100,000 O
sheep O
were O
sheared O
at O
Cisco B-LOCATION
before O
being O
shipped O
to O
market O
. O

Clive B-LOCATION
was O
a O
parliamentary O
electorate O
in O
the O
Hawke O
's O
Bay O
Region O
of O
New O
Zealand O
from O
1861 O
to O
1881 O
. O

Juba B-PERSON
may O
have O
capitalized O
on O
the O
free O
publicity O
given O
him O
by O
Dickens O
as O
he O
made O
the O
jump O
from O
the O
saloon O
to O
the O
stage O
. O

Among O
the O
bishops O
of O
Massa B-LOCATION
were O
Antonio O
da O
Massa O
Marittima O
( O
1430 O
) O
, O
a O
former O
minister O
general O
of O
the O
Franciscans O
, O
and O
legate O
of O
Pope O
Boniface O
IX O
; O
Leonardo O
Dati O
( O
1467 O
) O
, O
author O
of O
poetic O
satires O
. O

From O
2010 O
, O
Pierrot B-PERSON
has O
been O
increasingly O
active O
in O
board O
game O
development O
. O

Sugar O
was O
born O
in O
Washington O
, O
D.C. O
on O
June O
7 O
, O
1936 O
to O
Harold O
Randolph O
Sugar O
and O
Anne O
Edith O
( O
Rosensweig O
) O
Sugar B-PERSON
. O

Although O
Neptune B-PERSON
has O
been O
out O
of O
prison O
since O
July O
2006 O
, O
the O
IACHR O
found O
that O
the O
violations O
of O
his O
rights O
continue O
because O
the O
case O
has O
not O
been O
dismissed O
, O
and O
he O
could O
be O
returned O
to O
prison O
at O
any O
time O
. O

Modena B-LOCATION
was O
originally O
called O
Madisonville O
, O
and O
it O
was O
platted O
under O
the O
latter O
name O
in O
1856 O
. O

After O
spending O
about O
a O
decade O
in O
private O
sole O
practice O
as O
well O
as O
a O
brief O
stint O
with O
the O
United O
States O
Department O
of O
Housing O
and O
Urban O
Development O
, O
Calabria B-PERSON
became O
a O
Wake O
County O
District O
Court O
judge O
in O
1996 O
, O
and O
won O
election O
to O
the O
North O
Carolina O
Court O
of O
Appeals O
in O
2002 O
. O

Rochdale B-LOCATION
today O
is O
a O
predominantly O
residential O
town O
. O

Cranston B-PERSON
played O
his O
final O
season O
with O
the O
Edinburgh O
Capitals O
in O
the O
British O
National O
League O
during O
the O
1998–99 O
season O
. O

However O
, O
Atlas B-PERSON
left O
the O
camp O
in O
1982 O
following O
an O
altercation O
with O
the O
15-year O
- O
old O
Tyson O
after O
Tyson O
had O
been O
sexually O
inappropriate O
with O
an O
11-year O
- O
old O
female O
relative O
of O
Atlas O
' O
( O
Tyson O
said O
he O
had O
grabbed O
the O
girl O
's O
buttocks O
) O
. O

Legislative O
approval O
for O
separation O
was O
obtained O
in O
1807 O
, O
and O
Little O
Cambridge O
renamed O
itself O
Brighton B-LOCATION
. O

Raleigh B-PERSON
is O
buried O
in O
the O
churchyard O
of O
the O
parish O
church O
of O
St. O
Lawrence O
at O
North O
Hinksey O
, O
near O
Oxford O
. O

The O
sorcerer O
Merlin O
retrieves O
Excalibur B-PERSON
from O
the O
Lady O
of O
the O
Lake O
for O
Uther O
Pendragon O
, O
who O
secures O
a O
brief O
alliance O
with O
the O
Duke O
of O
Cornwall O
. O

It O
is O
located O
on O
State O
Highway O
1 O
approximately O
halfway O
between O
Balclutha O
and O
Gore O
( O
the O
section O
of O
State O
Highway O
1 O
between O
Clinton B-LOCATION
and O
Gore O
is O
known O
as O
" O
The O
Presidential O
Highway O
" O
, O
after O
Bill O
Clinton O
and O
Al O
Gore O
, O
though O
the O
names O
are O
a O
coincidence O
) O
, O
and O
the O
Main O
South O
Line O
railway O
passes O
through O
the O
town O
. O

The O
people O
of O
Afognak B-LOCATION
traded O
services O
and O
goods O
with O
other O
settlements O
in O
Southeast O
Alaska O
and O
the O
Aleutian O
chain O
. O

Cambridge B-PERSON
began O
as O
a O
light O
lyric O
soprano O
, O
then O
developed O
into O
a O
full O
lyric O
soprano O
, O
and O
more O
recently O
begun O
to O
develop O
into O
a O
spinto O
soprano O
, O
a O
more O
powerful O
voice O
that O
can O
handle O
more O
dramatic O
climaxes O
. O

Laar B-LOCATION
is O
a O
community O
in O
the O
district O
of O
Grafschaft O
Bentheim O
in O
Lower O
Saxony O
. O

1970s O
solo O
albums O
of O
Peter O
Hammill O
, O
Tony O
Banks O
and O
Steve O
Hackett O
were O
also O
on O
Charisma B-ORGANIZATION
. O

In O
1998 O
, O
Andrew O
Childs O
took O
over O
the O
running O
of O
Hannibal B-ORGANIZATION
. O

Another O
recent O
work O
by O
Oman B-PERSON
was O
" O
International O
Legal O
Experience O
and O
the O
Mormon O
Theology O
of O
the O
State O
, O
1945–2012 O
" O
published O
in O
the O
Iowa O
Law O
Review O
. O

Cloone B-LOCATION
has O
a O
mild O
climate O
like O
most O
of O
Ireland O
, O
with O
cool O
summers O
and O
mild O
winters O
. O

Leeds B-LOCATION
is O
also O
home O
to O
Leeds O
Elementary O
School O
. O

Ninigret O
in O
turn O
attempted O
to O
use O
colonial O
institutions O
to O
get O
back O
at O
Wyandanch B-PERSON
and O
accused O
the O
Montaukett O
sachem O
before O
the O
English O
. O

Jericho B-PERSON
sometimes O
uses O
the O
American O
manual O
alphabet O
letter O
" O
J O
" O
as O
his O
sign O
name O
in O
order O
to O
signal O
to O
his O
allies O
that O
he O
has O
taken O
possession O
of O
a O
person O
. O

Today O
, O
Wolverton B-LOCATION
is O
a O
thriving O
focus O
for O
the O
northern O
edge O
of O
Milton O
Keynes O
. O

Sky B-PERSON
has O
also O
appeared O
in O
GQ O
, O
Esquire O
Magazine O
, O
Supermodels O
Unlimited O
, O
and O
STUFF O
. O

Adrian B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
on O
W O
County O
Road O
59 O
in O
Big O
Spring O
township O
, O
in O
southwestern O
Seneca O
County O
, O
Ohio O
, O
United O
States O
, O
roughly O
three O
miles O
( O
five O
kilometres O
) O
south O
- O
southeast O
of O
Frenchtown O
. O

Since O
the O
14th O
century O
, O
Kraśnik B-LOCATION
was O
surrounded O
by O
a O
rampart O
, O
and O
ca O
. O

Albion B-LOCATION
was O
the O
location O
of O
the O
free O
Albion O
Ferry O
terminal O
which O
, O
until O
completion O
of O
the O
tolled O
Golden O
Ears O
Bridge O
in O
2009 O
, O
connected O
Maple O
Ridge O
to O
Langley O
via O
ferry O
across O
the O
Fraser O
River O
. O

From O
1798 O
to O
1814 O
, O
when O
the O
Palatinate O
was O
part O
of O
the O
French O
Republic O
( O
until O
1804 O
) O
and O
then O
part O
of O
the O
Napoleonic O
Empire O
, O
Otterbach B-LOCATION
was O
incorporated O
into O
the O
canton O
of O
Otterberg O
. O

Kovar B-LOCATION
is O
served O
by O
the O
Smithville O
Independent O
School O
District O
8 O
miles O
towards O
the O
north O
on O
Highway O
95 O
. O

The O
major O
shopping O
hub O
of O
Box O
Hill O
is O
two O
train O
stops O
away O
, O
while O
three O
buses O
connect O
Blackburn B-LOCATION
to O
Forest O
Hill O
. O

The O
dismal O
form O
continued O
in O
the O
I O
- O
League O
as O
Mumbai B-ORGANIZATION
lost O
their O
first O
three O
matches O
in O
a O
row O
. O

After O
college O
Athens B-PERSON
continued O
to O
interview O
inmates O
about O
their O
criminal O
lives O
and O
social O
experiences O
. O

McNair B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Lake O
County O
, O
Minnesota O
, O
United O
States O
. O

In O
the O
9th O
century O
, O
Sussex B-LOCATION
was O
ruled O
by O
the O
West O
Saxons O
. O

Many O
tourists O
visit O
Rothenberg B-LOCATION
because O
of O
the O
wonderful O
natural O
setting O
and O
because O
of O
so O
many O
possibilities O
for O
sports O
such O
as O
swimming O
, O
riding O
bikes O
, O
riding O
horses O
, O
hiking O
, O
gliding O
( O
with O
a O
flex O
- O
wing O
or O
with O
a O
glider O
) O
. O

Cherry B-ORGANIZATION
was O
founded O
by O
Walter O
Cherry O
in O
1953 O
in O
the O
basement O
of O
a O
restaurant O
in O
Highland O
Park O
, O
Illinois O
, O
USA O
. O

Wrexham B-LOCATION
( O
) O
is O
a O
constituency O
of O
the O
National O
Assembly O
for O
Wales O
. O

Sahara B-PERSON
is O
famous O
as O
a O
mainstay O
of O
Toho O
special O
- O
effects O
movies O
and O
the O
" O
Ultraman O
" O
series O
. O

GNU B-PERSON
has O
been O
the O
featured O
performer O
at O
other O
Real O
Men O
Sing O
events O
in O
the O
Midwest O
as O
well O
. O

Villarreal B-PERSON
returned O
in O
2005 O
, O
and O
ended O
up O
having O
another O
season O
shortened O
by O
an O
arm O
injury O
. O

Valencia B-PERSON
earned O
Florida O
State O
League O
( O
FSL O
) O
" O
Player O
of O
the O
Week O
" O
honors O
, O
batting O
.379 O
( O
11–29 O
) O
with O
two O
home O
runs O
, O
three O
runs O
scored O
, O
and O
10 O
RBIs O
for O
the O
week O
of O
July O
16 O
. O

The O
following O
month O
, O
officials O
of O
the O
two O
states O
signed O
a O
protocol O
to O
ease O
restrictions O
on O
Barak B-LOCATION
residents O
. O

Yorkshire B-LOCATION
and O
the O
Humber O
( O
European O
Parliament O
constituency O
) O

Makino B-ORGANIZATION
separated O
from O
the O
Mikado O
Company O
he O
had O
founded O
in O
1919 O
into O
an O
independent O
production O
company O
, O
Makino O
Film O
Productions O
, O
and O
from O
1923 O
continued O
his O
work O
as O
a O
director O
and O
producer O
. O

In O
the O
1860s O
, O
many O
black O
traveling O
musicians O
began O
performing O
on O
Beale B-LOCATION
. O

Villarreal B-PERSON
played O
the O
entire O
season O
with O
the O
Double O
- O
A O
El O
Paso O
Diablos O
, O
where O
he O
logged O
a O
6–9 O
record O
with O
a O
4.41 O
ERA O
and O
108 O
strikeouts O
. O

In O
2013 O
Coutts B-ORGANIZATION
replaced O
its O
purple O
' O
World O
' O
charge O
card O
, O
which O
had O
been O
designed O
by O
Boateng O
, O
with O
the O
new O
‘ O
Silk O
’ O
Charge O
card O
. O

Dennis B-ORGANIZATION
and O
Duple O
had O
developed O
the O
Dart O
, O
a O
midibus O
bought O
by O
London O
Transport O
as O
a O
one O
- O
man O
operated O
bus O
to O
replace O
their O
AEC O
Routemasters O
. O

Ralph B-LOCATION
is O
an O
unincorporated O
community O
in O
Webster O
County O
, O
West O
Virginia O
. O

After O
a O
series O
of O
one O
- O
off O
Dance O
compilations O
including O
" O
Cold O
Sweat O
" O
and O
" O
Trance O
Dance O
" O
, O
Dino B-ORGANIZATION
launched O
a O
new O
Dance O
series O
called O
" O
Energy O
Rush O
" O
in O
late O
1992 O
which O
out O
- O
lasted O
the O
" O
Hardcore O
" O
series O
by O
many O
years O
. O

Nixon B-LOCATION
traditionally O
belongs O
to O
the O
humid O
continental O
climate O
zone O
, O
even O
with O
the O
recent O
mild O
winters O
and O
warmer O
dry O
summers O
. O

" O
The O
work O
also O
revealed O
the O
main O
disputed O
areas O
as O
being O
the O
enclaves O
of O
Barak B-LOCATION
and O
Sokh O
and O
the O
areas O
of O
Gava O
and O
Gavasay O
. O

Considered O
the O
leading O
forward O
in O
the O
competition O
in O
the O
late O
1920s O
and O
early O
1930s O
, O
Coventry B-PERSON
played O
a O
key O
part O
in O
Collingwood O
's O
four O
consecutive O
premierships O
from O
1927 O
to O
1930 O
, O
each O
captained O
by O
his O
brother O
. O

From O
nearby O
Tyler O
, O
Texas O
, O
Tomlin O
competed O
against O
Humber B-PERSON
in O
high O
school O
, O
and O
the O
two O
train O
together O
during O
offseasons O
. O
